[
  {
    "question": "What is the cost?",
    "answer": "Individual Tax Return Form\n1040A Form\n1040EZ Form\nSEC Release IA-1092\n11th District Cost of Funds Index (COFI)\n125% Loan\n12B-1 Fee\n12B-1 Fund\n12B-1 Plan\n130-30 Strategy\n18-Hour City\n183-Day Rule\n1979 Energy Crisis\n2-1 Buydown\n2-2-8 Adjustable-Rate Mortgage (2/28 ARM): Meaning, How It Works\n2000 Investor Limit: What It is, How It Works, Example\n2011 U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms-beginning-with-num-4769350",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Julia Kagan?",
    "answer": "Replacement Cost\nThe Bottom Line\nUnderstanding Actual Cash Value: Definition, Examples, and Replacement Cost\nBy\nJulia Kagan\nFull Bio\nJulia Kagan is a financial/consumer journalist and former senior editor, personal finance, of Investopedia",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ebony Howard?",
    "answer": "Learn about our\neditorial policies\nUpdated September 07, 2025\nReviewed by\nEbony Howard\nReviewed by\nEbony Howard\nFull Bio\nEbony Howard is a certified public accountant and a QuickBooks ProAdvisor tax expert",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Suzanne?",
    "answer": "Learn about our\nFinancial Review Board\nFact checked by\nSuzanne Kvilhaug\nFact checked by\nSuzanne Kvilhaug\nFull Bio\nSuzanne is a content marketer, writer, and fact-checker",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What?",
    "answer": "Learn about our\neditorial policies\nPart of the Series\nComplete Guide to Homeowners Insurance\nWhat Is Homeowners Insurance and How Does It Work",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The 80% Rule?",
    "answer": "Homeowners Insurance Basics\nBeginner's Overview\nHow Much to Buy\nThe 80% Rule\nIs Home Insurance Tax Deductible",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about deductible?",
    "answer": "Homeowners Insurance Basics\nBeginner's Overview\nHow Much to Buy\nThe 80% Rule\nIs Home Insurance Tax Deductible",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about policy?",
    "answer": "Know Your Terms\nHO5 Policy vs",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does coverage include?",
    "answer": "Water Exclusion Clause\nBest Home Insurance Companies\nGetting the Best Quotes on Homeowners Insurance\nHow to Save on Homeowners Insurance\nInsurance for Natural Disasters\nHazard Insurance\nFlood Insurance\nLender-Required Flood Insurance\nWindstorm Insurance\nHurricane Deductible\nInsurance for Special Situations\nCatastrophe Insurance\nDoes Homeowners Insurance Cover Renovations",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the requirements?",
    "answer": "Water Exclusion Clause\nBest Home Insurance Companies\nGetting the Best Quotes on Homeowners Insurance\nHow to Save on Homeowners Insurance\nInsurance for Natural Disasters\nHazard Insurance\nFlood Insurance\nLender-Required Flood Insurance\nWindstorm Insurance\nHurricane Deductible\nInsurance for Special Situations\nCatastrophe Insurance\nDoes Homeowners Insurance Cover Renovations",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Insure Your Second Home\nVacant Home Insurance: Do You Need It?",
    "answer": "How to Insure Your Second Home\nVacant Home Insurance: Do You Need It",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Home Warranties?",
    "answer": "Vandalism and Malicious Mischeif\nAirbnb Insurance\nHome Warranties\nIs a Home Warranty Worth It",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Actual cash value (ACV)?",
    "answer": "Actual cash value (ACV) is calculated by taking the\nreplacement cost\nof a damaged or stolen property and subtracting\ndepreciation",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This valuation method?",
    "answer": "This valuation method is commonly used in insurance claims to determine the payout a policyholder receives after a loss",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about claim?",
    "answer": "This valuation method is commonly used in insurance claims to determine the payout a policyholder receives after a loss",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about coverage?",
    "answer": "Unlike replacement cost coverage, ACV considers depreciation, which often results in a lower compensation amount",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Actual Cash Value (ACV)?",
    "answer": "Key Takeaways\nActual Cash Value (ACV) is calculated by subtracting depreciation from the replacement cost of a property at the time of loss",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In property and casualty insurance, ACV?",
    "answer": "In property and casualty insurance, ACV is commonly used to determine compensation for damaged or stolen goods",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In the case of an automobile that?",
    "answer": "In the case of an automobile that is totaled in an accident, for example, the insurance company would typically\npay the actual cash value of the vehicle\nafter determining its replacement cost and subtracting factors such as depreciation and wear and tear",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Actual cash value?",
    "answer": "Actual cash value\u00a0is used in valuing insured property in the property and casualty insurance industry",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about insured?",
    "answer": "Actual cash value\u00a0is used in valuing insured property in the property and casualty insurance industry",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is ACV?",
    "answer": "ACV is found by subtracting depreciation from the replacement cost",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Depreciation?",
    "answer": "Depreciation is based on how much of the item's life remains",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This concept?",
    "answer": "This concept is different from the\nbook value\nused by accountants in financial statements or for tax purposes",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For instance, if a\u00a0camera?",
    "answer": "For instance, if a\u00a0camera is stolen, a replacement cost policy will reimburse you the full cost of replacing it with a new camera of like kind",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Understanding Actual Cash Value (ACV)?",
    "answer": "The Bottom Line\nUnderstanding Actual Cash Value (ACV) is crucial for policyholders who want to optimize their insurance coverage",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While ACV?",
    "answer": "While ACV is regularly used in the property and casualty insurance industry to value insured properties, opting for replacement cost coverage might be more beneficial as it provides reimbursement for the current cost of replacing damaged items",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Wildfire Insurance: Ensure Your Home?",
    "answer": "Related Articles\nWildfire Insurance: Ensure Your Home Is Protected\nRenters Insurance Guide: Protect Your Belongings & Liabilit\nUnderstanding Valued Policy Law: Full Coverage for Total Loss\nUnderstanding Floater Insurance: Coverage for Movable Valuables\nDoes Homeowners Insurance Cover Roof Replacement",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Why Property Insurance?",
    "answer": "Mortgage Insurance: Key Differences Explained\nWhy Property Insurance is Essential for Financial Security\nUnderstanding Abandonment Clauses in Property Insurance\nUnderstanding Absolute Pollution Exclusion in Commercial Insurance\nIs Homeowners Insurance Tax Deductible",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is a Home Warranty?",
    "answer": "What Is a Home Warranty",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Investopedia?",
    "answer": "Coverage, Costs, and Qualifications Explained\nAll-Risks Insurance Explained: Comprehensive Coverage Details\nInvestopedia\nNewsletter Sign Up\nFollow Us\nNews\nInvesting\nSimulator\nBanking\nPersonal Finance\nEconomy\nReviews\nDictionary\nAbout Us\nEditorial Process\nCareers\nContact Us\nPrivacy Policy\nTerms of Service\nAdvertise\nYour Privacy Choices\n#\nA\nB\nC\nD\nE\nF\nG\nH\nI\nJ\nK\nL\nM\nN\nO\nP\nQ\nR\nS\nT\nU\nV\nW\nX\nY\nZ\nInvestopedia\nis part of the\nPeople Inc",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/actual-cash-value.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is She?",
    "answer": "She is currently a full-time staff writer at Investopedia and one of the country's top experts on how to earn as much as possible on the money you hold in the bank",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Amanda Bellucco-Chatham?",
    "answer": "Learn about our\neditorial policies\nUpdated January 12, 2026\nFact checked by\nAmanda Bellucco-Chatham\nFact checked by\nAmanda Bellucco-Chatham\nFull Bio\nAmanda Bellucco-Chatham is an editor, writer, and fact-checker with years of experience researching personal finance topics",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The best high-yield savings account rate?",
    "answer": "Learn about our\neditorial policies\nThe best high-yield savings account rate is 5",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A high-yield savings account?",
    "answer": "A high-yield savings account is great because it pays more interest, while still giving you the flexibility to withdraw your money when needed",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where more than one financial institution has the same rate, we rank them in order of the lowest monthly deposit requirement, the lowest minimum balance requirement, and the lowest opening deposit requirement?",
    "answer": "Where more than one financial institution has the same rate, we rank them in order of the lowest monthly deposit requirement, the lowest minimum balance requirement, and the lowest opening deposit requirement",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1) $1,000 monthly in qualifying direct deposits; 2) Open and maintain an accompanying Varo Bank Account; 3) End the month with positive balances in all Varo accounts; 4) Stated APY paid on balances up to $5,000; APY?",
    "answer": "00% APY\nRequired opening deposit:\nAny amount\nMinimum balance requirement:\nAny amount\nOther requirements/limits:\n1) $1,000 monthly in qualifying direct deposits; 2) Open and maintain an accompanying Varo Bank Account; 3) End the month with positive balances in all Varo accounts; 4) Stated APY paid on balances up to $5,000; APY is 2",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Varo Bank?",
    "answer": "50% for balances greater than $5,000 and if qualifications are not met\nMonthly fee:\nNo\nATM card:\nYes\nMobile check deposit:\nYes\nChecking accounts available:\nYes\nCDs available:\nNo\nOverview:\nVaro Bank is a fintech company, started in 2015 and FDIC-insured since 2020",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is AdelFi?",
    "answer": "35% APY\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card available:\nYes\nMobile check deposit:\nYes\nChecking accounts available:\nYes\nCDs available:\nYes\nOverview:\nAdelFi is a church-based credit union that dates back to 1984 when Conservative Baptist Credit Union merged with the Association of Christian School International Credit Union",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It was rebranded as AdelFi in 2022 and?",
    "answer": "It was rebranded as AdelFi in 2022 and is headquartered in Brea, California",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Anyone nationwide who agrees with AdelFi\u2019s statement of faith?",
    "answer": "Anyone nationwide who agrees with AdelFi\u2019s statement of faith is eligible for membership",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is FDIC-insured since 1963 as National Bank of New York City, Newtek?",
    "answer": "35% APY\nRequired opening deposit:\nAny amount\nMinimum balance requirement:\nAny amount\nOther requirements/limits:\nNone\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card:\nNo\nMobile check deposit:\nNo\nChecking accounts available:\nNo\nCDs available:\nYes\nOverview:\nFDIC-insured since 1963 as National Bank of New York City, Newtek is the bank's 2023 rebranded identity, which operates one branch each in New York and Miami while serving nationwide customers online",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It?",
    "answer": "It is headquartered in San Diego",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Openbank?",
    "answer": "20% APY\nRequired opening deposit:\n$500\nMinimum balance requirement:\nAny amount\nOther requirements/limits:\nMobile device with face or fingerprint recognition\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card available:\nNo\nMobile check deposit:\nNo\nChecking accounts available:\nNo\nCDs available:\nNo\nOverview:\nOpenbank is an online and mobile affiliate of Santander Bank, which has locations around the world and has been in the U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ivy Bank?",
    "answer": "10% APY\nRequired opening deposit:\n$2,500\nMinimum balance requirement:\n$2,500 to earn stated APY\nOther requirements/limits:\nNone\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card available:\nNo\nMobile check deposit:\nYes\nChecking accounts available:\nNo\nCDs available:\nYes\nOverview:\nIvy Bank is an online-only division of Cambridge Savings Bank, which has been serving the greater Boston area since 1834",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Vio Bank?",
    "answer": "09% APY\nRequired opening deposit:\n$100\nMinimum balance requirement:\nAny amount\nOther requirements/limits:\nNone\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card:\nNo\nMobile check deposit:\nYes\nChecking accounts available:\nNo\nCDs available:\nYes\nOverview:\nVio Bank is the online banking division of MidFirst Bank, an Oklahoma institution established in 1911 that is among the Top 100 largest U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about premium?",
    "answer": "12, 2026\nMutualOne Bank, Mo Premium Savings \u2013 4",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dating back to 1889, MutualOne?",
    "answer": "07% APY\nRequired opening deposit:\n$20,000\nMinimum balance requirement:\n$20,000\nOther requirements/limits:\nMinimum deposit to open account must be new money to the bank\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card available:\nNo\nMobile check deposit:\nYes\nChecking accounts available:\nYes\nCDs available:\nYes\nOverview:\nDating back to 1889, MutualOne is a brick-and-mortar Massachusetts bank that offers some of its banking products online",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Jenius?",
    "answer": "05% APY\nRequired opening deposit:\nAny amount\nMinimum balance requirement:\nAny amount\nOther requirements/limits:\nNone\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card available:\nNo\nMobile check deposit:\nNo\nChecking accounts available:\nNo\nCDs available:\nNo\nOverview:\nJenius is the digital banking division of SMBC MANUBANK, part of the SMBC group, which has offices worldwide and U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Bread Savings?",
    "answer": "05% APY\nMinimum opening deposit:\n$100\nMinimum ongoing balance:\nAny amount\nOther requirements/limits:\nNone\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card available:\nNo\nMobile check deposit:\nYes\nChecking accounts available:\nNo\nCDs available:\nYes\nOverview:\nBread Savings is the online consumer deposits bank operated by credit card issuer Comenity Capital Bank",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is My Banking Direct?",
    "answer": "02% APY\nRequired opening deposit:\n$500\nMinimum balance requirement:\nAny amount\nOther requirements/limits:\nNone\nMonthly fee:\nNone\nATM card:\nNo\nMobile check deposit:\nYes\nChecking accounts available:\nYes\nCDs available:\nYes\nOverview:\nMy Banking Direct is an internet-only division of New York Community Bank, which was founded in 1859 and operates more than 200 branches in five states",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Savings rates closely follow the fed funds rate, which?",
    "answer": "Savings rates closely follow the fed funds rate, which means\nsavings rates are expected to decline\nas the Fed lowers rates",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why You Can Trust Us\nInvestopedia collects savings account rates from over 100 banks and credit unions every weekday?",
    "answer": "Why You Can Trust Us\nInvestopedia collects savings account rates from over 100 banks and credit unions every weekday",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When ranking high-yield savings account rates, we look at factors that will help readers choose the best savings account, like minimum opening deposit?",
    "answer": "When ranking high-yield savings account rates, we look at factors that will help readers choose the best savings account, like minimum opening deposit",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is a High-Yield Savings Account?",
    "answer": "What Is a High-Yield Savings Account",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Stashing some of your cash in a savings account?",
    "answer": "Reasons to Open a High-Yield Savings Account\nStashing some of your cash in a savings account is smart whether you're saving for something specific, or just want to sock money away for when you'll need it in the future",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is : Earning interest on your money?",
    "answer": "Grow your savings\n: Earning interest on your money means your savings balance will grow faster than if you were making monthly contributions and not earning anything",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Will a High-Yield Savings Account Pay on $1,000, $5,000, or Higher Balances?",
    "answer": "How Much Will a High-Yield Savings Account Pay on $1,000, $5,000, or Higher Balances",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One smart way to do this?",
    "answer": "One smart way to do this is to set up an automated transfer from your checking account once a month",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Choose the Best High-Yield Savings Account\nOnce you've decided to open up a new high-yield savings account, you'll want to do your homework to make sure you're choosing the best one for your needs?",
    "answer": "How to Choose the Best High-Yield Savings Account\nOnce you've decided to open up a new high-yield savings account, you'll want to do your homework to make sure you're choosing the best one for your needs",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is annual percentage yield (APY)?",
    "answer": "Searching for a top\nannual percentage yield (APY)\nis a good starting point when choosing a high-yield savings account, as you'll want to earn a competitive rate",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Though the interest rate can change, it makes sense to choose an account that?",
    "answer": "Though the interest rate can change, it makes sense to choose an account that is paying one of the highest rates in the country, since the higher your rate, the more interest you'll collect every month and every year",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Also, note if there?",
    "answer": "Also, note if there is a minimum balance required to earn the top APY",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Each bank?",
    "answer": "Why Different Banks Pay Different Rates\nEach bank is a business that has different needs for customer deposits, operating in its own regional market",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Different Banks Pay Different Rates\nEach bank is a business that has different needs for customer deposits, operating in its own regional market?",
    "answer": "Why Different Banks Pay Different Rates\nEach bank is a business that has different needs for customer deposits, operating in its own regional market",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Also important?",
    "answer": "Also important is the lending activity the bank is undertaking",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If, for instance, a bank?",
    "answer": "If, for instance, a bank is in a strategic push to build its commercial lending portfolio, it will need to attract more customer deposits in order to fund those loans it hopes to make",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One way they can do this?",
    "answer": "One way they can do this is offering a promotional APY for a short period to boost their deposits balance, but then lowering it after they've accumulated enough funds",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is minimum balance requirement?",
    "answer": "Minimum balance requirement or ongoing balance\n: Unlike a minimum initial deposit, a\nminimum balance requirement\nrefers to the least amount of money you can keep in the account on an\nongoing\nbasis",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Falling below the minimum requirement could?",
    "answer": "Falling below the minimum requirement could mean being hit with a fee, or could instead mean you won't earn the high-yield interest rate on the account",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is fee, the monthly service fee?",
    "answer": "Unlike ones triggered by a transaction, such as an\ninsufficient funds\nfee or a\nwire transfer\nfee, the monthly service fee is a standard fee you could be charged every statement cycle",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is : The electronic process of moving funds between two financial institutions?",
    "answer": "External or ACH transfer\n: The electronic process of moving funds between two financial institutions is called an external or\nACH transfer",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is After comparing the best high-yield savings account and landing on a choice, the next step?",
    "answer": "How to Open a High-Yield Savings Account\nAfter comparing the best high-yield savings account and landing on a choice, the next step is to open the account online",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Open a High-Yield Savings Account\nAfter comparing the best high-yield savings account and landing on a choice, the next step is to open the account online?",
    "answer": "How to Open a High-Yield Savings Account\nAfter comparing the best high-yield savings account and landing on a choice, the next step is to open the account online",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The most common method?",
    "answer": "The most common method is by ACH transfer from another bank, and you'll be provided with instructions on how to set this up",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Once the application process?",
    "answer": "Once the application process is completed, you may be able to set up online banking right away, or you may need to wait a day or two for your account to be fully opened",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When choosing the best savings account for you, you'll want to check the rules of the account, such as whether it limits the number of withdrawals you can make in a month, and if you'll be assessed a monthly maintenance fee?",
    "answer": "When choosing the best savings account for you, you'll want to check the rules of the account, such as whether it limits the number of withdrawals you can make in a month, and if you'll be assessed a monthly maintenance fee",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Lastly, check that the bank?",
    "answer": "Lastly, check that the bank is an FDIC member (or an NCUA member if it's a credit union) so that your money is insured by the federal government\u2014up to $250,000 per depositor\u2014should the bank or credit union fail",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is place to keep surplus funds?",
    "answer": "Checking Account\nWhile the\neasiest\nplace to keep surplus funds is in your\nchecking account\n, this has two major downsides",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is First, money kept in your everyday checking account?",
    "answer": "First, money kept in your everyday checking account is very easy to spend, making it difficult to leave earmarked as savings",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Second, checking accounts tend not to pay any interest\u2014or if they do, the rate?",
    "answer": "Second, checking accounts tend not to pay any interest\u2014or if they do, the rate is a pittance",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is There?",
    "answer": "Traditional Savings Account\nThere is no formal definition of how high a rate needs to be to qualify as \"high yield\"",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why You Don't See Big Name Banks on Our List\nWe track the savings account rates of over 100 banks and credit unions every weekday?",
    "answer": "Why You Don't See Big Name Banks on Our List\nWe track the savings account rates of over 100 banks and credit unions every weekday",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But in exchange, your interest rate?",
    "answer": "But in exchange, your interest rate is locked and guaranteed, even if the Fed lowers rates",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is HYSA?",
    "answer": "HYSA is simply an abbreviation for \"high-yield savings account",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Are the Best High-Yield Savings Accounts?",
    "answer": "What Are the Best High-Yield Savings Accounts",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Or for a list that?",
    "answer": "Or for a list that is exclusive to banks (no credit unions), you can check our daily ranking of the\nbest banks for savings accounts",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Do High-Yield Savings Accounts Work?",
    "answer": "How Do High-Yield Savings Accounts Work",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is That?",
    "answer": "That means whether your dealing with a traditional brick-and-mortar bank, an online bank, or a credit union, your deposits up to $250,000 are equally safe and protected",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How We Find the Best High-Yield Savings Account Rates\nEvery business day, Investopedia tracks the rate data of about 100 banks and credit unions that offer high-yield savings accounts to customers nationwide?",
    "answer": "How We Find the Best High-Yield Savings Account Rates\nEvery business day, Investopedia tracks the rate data of about 100 banks and credit unions that offer high-yield savings accounts to customers nationwide",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is , you don't live in a certain area or work in a certain kind of job), we exclude credit unions whose donation requirement?",
    "answer": ", you don't live in a certain area or work in a certain kind of job), we exclude credit unions whose donation requirement is $40 or more",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about exclude?",
    "answer": ", you don't live in a certain area or work in a certain kind of job), we exclude credit unions whose donation requirement is $40 or more",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If the savings account?",
    "answer": "If the savings account is accessible only through a mobile app, we require that the app be available on both the iOS and Android platforms",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Open a High-Yield Savings Account\nBest High-Yield Business Savings Accounts\nBest Banks for Savings Accounts\nHow Many Savings Accounts Should I Have?",
    "answer": "How to Open a High-Yield Savings Account\nBest High-Yield Business Savings Accounts\nBest Banks for Savings Accounts\nHow Many Savings Accounts Should I Have",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Choose a Money Market Instead of a Savings Account\nBest Money Market Accounts\nSavings Account vs?",
    "answer": "Why Choose a Money Market Instead of a Savings Account\nBest Money Market Accounts\nSavings Account vs",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is **The Annual Percentage Yield (APY)?",
    "answer": "Revolut Disclosure\n**The Annual Percentage Yield (APY) is a variable rate and may change at any time",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Revolut?",
    "answer": "Revolut is not a bank",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This?",
    "answer": "This is a variable rate account and the APY may change without notice",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Only 1 High Yield Account?",
    "answer": "Only 1 High Yield Account is permitted and is limited to $10,000 USD in user initiated deposits",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The max combined balance of all Savings Accounts?",
    "answer": "The max combined balance of all Savings Accounts is $250,000 per user",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This promotional code?",
    "answer": "This promotional code is intended for single use only and is non-transferable",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This offer?",
    "answer": "This offer is only valid for a new Premium Savings Account (PSA)",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is residents, and residents of any jurisdiction where this offer?",
    "answer": "residents, and residents of any jurisdiction where this offer is not valid",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Each customer?",
    "answer": "Each customer is limited to a lifetime maximum of two new Premium Savings Account offers",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is **As of 12/16/2025, the Annual Percentage Yield (APY) of the Premium Savings Account offered by Morgan Stanley Private Bank, National Association, Member FDIC?",
    "answer": "**As of 12/16/2025, the Annual Percentage Yield (APY) of the Premium Savings Account offered by Morgan Stanley Private Bank, National Association, Member FDIC is 3",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, the account must be funded within 30 days to remain open?",
    "answer": "However, the account must be funded within 30 days to remain open",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about condition?",
    "answer": "Certain conditions must be met",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/high-yield-savings-accounts-4770633",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Life insurance?",
    "answer": "Life insurance is a financial product that offers a death benefit to beneficiaries upon the policyholder's passing, and age is one of the primary factors affecting its premiums",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/articles/personal-finance/022615/how-age-affects-life-insurance-rates.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Learn why age?",
    "answer": "Learn why age is a pivotal consideration, how premiums are structured, and ways to keep costs manageable",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/articles/personal-finance/022615/how-age-affects-life-insurance-rates.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Overall, age?",
    "answer": "Overall, age is the most important contributor to both term and permanent life insurance rates",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/articles/personal-finance/022615/how-age-affects-life-insurance-rates.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The annual premium, or \u201crate,\u201d for a term life insurance policy?",
    "answer": "How Age Impacts Life Insurance Costs\nThe annual premium, or \u201crate,\u201d for a term life insurance policy is determined at the time of purchase and set for the duration of the policy",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/articles/personal-finance/022615/how-age-affects-life-insurance-rates.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Age Impacts Life Insurance Costs\nThe annual premium, or \u201crate,\u201d for a term life insurance policy is determined at the time of purchase and set for the duration of the policy?",
    "answer": "How Age Impacts Life Insurance Costs\nThe annual premium, or \u201crate,\u201d for a term life insurance policy is determined at the time of purchase and set for the duration of the policy",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/articles/personal-finance/022615/how-age-affects-life-insurance-rates.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201d The reason every year inches up the cost of term life insurance?",
    "answer": "\u201d The reason every year inches up the cost of term life insurance is simple math",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/articles/personal-finance/022615/how-age-affects-life-insurance-rates.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 Cs of Credit: What They Are, How They\u2019re Used, and Which?",
    "answer": "5 Cs of Credit: What They Are, How They\u2019re Used, and Which Is Most Important\nBest Credit Repair Companies for January 2026\nHow FICO Scores Are Calculated\nCredit Rating vs",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Another thing that goes into a person\u2019s credit score?",
    "answer": "Another thing that goes into a person\u2019s credit score is the length of credit history, which means the age of the oldest account on file",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What Lenders Look at on Your Credit Report?",
    "answer": "Learn More:\nWhat Lenders Look at on Your Credit Report\nIs a credit card different from a line of credit",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A credit card?",
    "answer": "A credit card is a card-based form of payment that has a revolving credit line",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Once a check?",
    "answer": "Once a check is written against a line of credit principal and interest is paid back in installments",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What behaviors affect credit scores?",
    "answer": "What behaviors affect credit scores",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Credit?",
    "answer": "Key Terms\nCredit\nHard Inquiry\nCredit Rating\nCredit History\nCredit Quality\nBuy Now, Pay Later\nCredit\nCredit refers to the extension of financial borrowing privileges from one individual or organization to another",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ultimately, credit?",
    "answer": "Ultimately, credit is based on trust between the lender and borrower that the amount owed will be repaid",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A hard inquiry?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nHard Inquiry\nA hard inquiry refers to a lender pulling a full credit report on an individual from a credit reporting company in order to determine their creditworthiness for a loan or revolving line of credit",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Credit rating generally?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nCredit Rating\nCredit rating generally refers to an individual\u2019s creditworthiness as measured by a credit score",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Credit history?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nCredit History\nCredit history is the accumulated credit account behavior of an individual that is tracked by credit reporting agencies",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Credit quality?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nCredit Quality\nCredit quality is another term for creditworthiness, meaning the level at which lenders assign credit amounts and terms based on risk level",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Buy Now, Pay Later, also known as BNPL,?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nBuy Now, Pay Later\nBuy Now, Pay Later, also known as BNPL, is a relatively recent take on the old layaway plans of the past",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, unlike layaway plans, Buy Now, Pay Later allows the buyer to take possession of the goods immediately and break up payments into four equal installments over a short period of time?",
    "answer": "However, unlike layaway plans, Buy Now, Pay Later allows the buyer to take possession of the goods immediately and break up payments into four equal installments over a short period of time",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Your Credit?",
    "answer": "Most People Don\u2019t Know the Full Picture\nYour Credit Is at Risk from Unpaid Medical Bills\u2014Here's How to Safeguard It\nCould Your BNPL Debt Impact Your Credit Report",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Credit Affects Renting an Apartment\nWhat Is APY and How Is It Calculated?",
    "answer": "How Credit Affects Renting an Apartment\nWhat Is APY and How Is It Calculated",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Get and Use an Annual Credit Report (Now Weekly)\nBankruptcy Rates by Race\nAverage Credit Scores by Gender\nAverage U?",
    "answer": "How to Get and Use an Annual Credit Report (Now Weekly)\nBankruptcy Rates by Race\nAverage Credit Scores by Gender\nAverage U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Lenders Look at on Your Credit Report\nBest Credit Monitoring Services for January 2026\nYou've Got a Wallet Full of Credit Cards?",
    "answer": "What Lenders Look at on Your Credit Report\nBest Credit Monitoring Services for January 2026\nYou've Got a Wallet Full of Credit Cards",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Do a Consumer Disclosure and Credit Report Differ?",
    "answer": "How Do a Consumer Disclosure and Credit Report Differ",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/credit-and-debt-4689724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Robert Kelly?",
    "answer": "Kelly\nFull Bio\nRobert Kelly is managing director of XTS Energy LLC, and has more than three decades of experience as a business executive",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is He?",
    "answer": "He is a professor of economics and has raised more than $4",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is Abandonment and Salvage?",
    "answer": "What Is Abandonment and Salvage",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Abandonment and salvage?",
    "answer": "Abandonment and salvage is a marine\ninsurance\nconcept, where an owner\nforfeits\nproperty\nto the insurer, which may then recover and claim it as salvage",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Abandonment and Salvage Function\nAbandonment and salvage is a term that can surface fairly frequently in insurance contracts?",
    "answer": "How Abandonment and Salvage Function\nAbandonment and salvage is a term that can surface fairly frequently in insurance contracts",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is When such a clause?",
    "answer": "When such a clause is present, it indicates that the insurer has the ability to rightfully claim an insured\nasset\nor piece of property that has been destroyed and subsequently abandoned by its owners",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When such a clause is present, it indicates that the insurer has the ability to rightfully claim an insured\nasset\nor piece of property that has been destroyed and subsequently abandoned by its owners?",
    "answer": "When such a clause is present, it indicates that the insurer has the ability to rightfully claim an insured\nasset\nor piece of property that has been destroyed and subsequently abandoned by its owners",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Once that process?",
    "answer": "Once that process is complete, the insurance company could choose to take full possession of the damaged property after paying out its insured value to the policyholder",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If acceptance?",
    "answer": "If acceptance is granted, the insurer pays a\ntotal loss\n, usually the maximum settlement possible according to the terms of the insurance policy, then takes over the salvage as owner, regardless of any amount received from its subsequent sale",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, the insurers may waive this condition in appropriate circumstances, if merited?",
    "answer": "However, the insurers may waive this condition in appropriate circumstances, if merited",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For example, if a vessel sinks and?",
    "answer": "For example, if a vessel sinks and is deemed too expensive to reclaim, it may be declared abandoned",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The insured must transfer all rights, ownership, and interest of the damaged cargo to the insurer, after which the insurer becomes the owner of the damaged remaining cargo, which?",
    "answer": "The insured must transfer all rights, ownership, and interest of the damaged cargo to the insurer, after which the insurer becomes the owner of the damaged remaining cargo, which is known as salvage",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The process of transferring rights of the damaged asset or property?",
    "answer": "The process of transferring rights of the damaged asset or property is called\nsubrogation",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In cases of clear-cut total losses, insurance would pay in full, so the insurer?",
    "answer": "In cases of clear-cut total losses, insurance would pay in full, so the insurer is entitled to the benefit of the salvage",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/terms/a/abandonment-and-salvage.asp",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Everyone Needs to Know About Taxes\nFederal Income Tax\nProperty Tax Calculation and State Rankings: What You Should Know\nWhen to Adjust Your W-4 Withholding\nTop Tax Advantages of Buying a Home\nHow to Maximize Your Tax Return\nFrequently Asked Questions\nWhich states don\u2019t charge sales tax?",
    "answer": "What Everyone Needs to Know About Taxes\nFederal Income Tax\nProperty Tax Calculation and State Rankings: What You Should Know\nWhen to Adjust Your W-4 Withholding\nTop Tax Advantages of Buying a Home\nHow to Maximize Your Tax Return\nFrequently Asked Questions\nWhich states don\u2019t charge sales tax",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, that doesn\u2019t keep them from charging\nincome tax\n,\nexcise taxes\nor tourist taxes?",
    "answer": "However, that doesn\u2019t keep them from charging\nincome tax\n,\nexcise taxes\nor tourist taxes",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is And it doesn\u2019t?",
    "answer": "And it doesn\u2019t mean that cities or municipalities within those states can\u2019t change a local sales tax",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Alternative minimum tax (AMT)?",
    "answer": "Alternative minimum tax (AMT)\nis a system invented to make sure that higher income people with significant tax deductions didn\u2019t avoid paying federal income tax",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What you need to do?",
    "answer": "What you need to do is keep your AGI as low as possible through maximizing salary deferrals and pre-tax contributions to flexible spending plans and the like, keeping tax-efficient investments in taxable investment accounts, and taking all the tax credits of which you qualify",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What you need to do is keep your AGI as low as possible through maximizing salary deferrals and pre-tax contributions to flexible spending plans and the like, keeping tax-efficient investments in taxable investment accounts, and taking all the tax credits of which you qualify?",
    "answer": "What you need to do is keep your AGI as low as possible through maximizing salary deferrals and pre-tax contributions to flexible spending plans and the like, keeping tax-efficient investments in taxable investment accounts, and taking all the tax credits of which you qualify",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Unlike the estate tax, which?",
    "answer": "Unlike the estate tax, which is paid by the deceased\u2019s estate, this tax is paid by the beneficiary",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A consumption tax imposed on goods and services, a sales tax?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nSales Tax\nA consumption tax imposed on goods and services, a sales tax is paid at the point of sale by the consumer and is collected by the seller",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How 2026 Tax Bracket Changes Will Impact Retirees\u2014What It?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nHow to Add $250 a Month to Your 2026 Budget\u2014Without Earning a Raise\nHow 2026 Tax Bracket Changes Will Impact Retirees\u2014What It Means for Your Retirement\nRetire Without State Taxes: States That Let You Keep Every Dollar You Earn\nFind Out If You Qualify for the New Senior Tax Break\nOne Of My Goals For 2026 Is To Start a Small Business",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Will I Be Taxed?",
    "answer": "How Much Will I Be Taxed",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 Ways the One Big Beautiful Bill Act?",
    "answer": "Why Americans Give So Much Less to Charity Now\nThe Hidden Costs of Ignoring Your Taxes: What You Should Be Aware Of\n5 Ways the One Big Beautiful Bill Act is Transforming Parenting in 2025\nTrump's Tax Bill Makes a Big Change That Could Impact High Earners, Especially Those In New York and California\n7 Things Taxpayers Need To Know About the Big Beautiful Bill Act\nFiling Quarterly Taxes As a Gig Worker\nCan a Personal Loan Make Paying Taxes Easier",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Americans Give So Much Less to Charity Now\nThe Hidden Costs of Ignoring Your Taxes: What You Should Be Aware Of\n5 Ways the One Big Beautiful Bill Act is Transforming Parenting in 2025\nTrump's Tax Bill Makes a Big Change That Could Impact High Earners, Especially Those In New York and California\n7 Things Taxpayers Need To Know About the Big Beautiful Bill Act\nFiling Quarterly Taxes As a Gig Worker\nCan a Personal Loan Make Paying Taxes Easier?",
    "answer": "Why Americans Give So Much Less to Charity Now\nThe Hidden Costs of Ignoring Your Taxes: What You Should Be Aware Of\n5 Ways the One Big Beautiful Bill Act is Transforming Parenting in 2025\nTrump's Tax Bill Makes a Big Change That Could Impact High Earners, Especially Those In New York and California\n7 Things Taxpayers Need To Know About the Big Beautiful Bill Act\nFiling Quarterly Taxes As a Gig Worker\nCan a Personal Loan Make Paying Taxes Easier",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Here's What It?",
    "answer": "Here's What It Means and What to Do\nThese States Have the Lowest Taxes on Food",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What a High-Yield Year?",
    "answer": "Tax Hacks for 2025: 4 Easy Ways to Keep More of Your Money\nThe Hidden Costs of Moving for Lower Taxes: What to Consider Before You Pack Up and Go\n6 Essential Tips to Navigate the Tax Code Like a Pro\nWhat a High-Yield Year Means for Your Taxes\nHow to Be a Tax-Efficient Investor\nCalculate Sales Tax: Simple Steps and Real-Life Examples\nTeens and Income Taxes: Do They Need To File",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Make Estimated Tax Payments\nWhat You Need to Know About Your 2024 Personal Income Taxes\nForm W-2G: Certain Gambling Winnings, Guide, and Filing How-Tos\nSurcharge: What It Is, How It Works, Types, and Examples\nConsumption Tax: Definition, Types, vs?",
    "answer": "How to Make Estimated Tax Payments\nWhat You Need to Know About Your 2024 Personal Income Taxes\nForm W-2G: Certain Gambling Winnings, Guide, and Filing How-Tos\nSurcharge: What It Is, How It Works, Types, and Examples\nConsumption Tax: Definition, Types, vs",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Reduce or Avoid Them\nNet of Tax: Definition, Benefits of Analysis, and How to Calculate\nIndirect Tax: Definition, Meaning, and Common Examples\nTax Incidence: Definition and How It Works\nUnderstanding Local Taxes: Types and Their Impact on Public Services\nTax Expense: Definition, Calculation, and Effect on Earnings\nNoncovered Security: Definition, Reporting Rules, vs?",
    "answer": "How to Reduce or Avoid Them\nNet of Tax: Definition, Benefits of Analysis, and How to Calculate\nIndirect Tax: Definition, Meaning, and Common Examples\nTax Incidence: Definition and How It Works\nUnderstanding Local Taxes: Types and Their Impact on Public Services\nTax Expense: Definition, Calculation, and Effect on Earnings\nNoncovered Security: Definition, Reporting Rules, vs",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/taxes-4427724",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How Fintech?",
    "answer": "Guide to Financial Technology\nAutomate Your Wealth With These Simple, Effective Steps\nHow the Internet Has Changed Investing\nHow Fintech Is Disrupting Wealth Management\nThe Bloomberg Terminal: Step By Step\nThe Most Popular Mobile Payment Apps\nFrequently Asked Questions\nWhat is Fintech",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Fintech?",
    "answer": "Fintech is a portmanteau of the words \u201cfinancial\u201d and \u201ctechnology,\u201d and refers to technologies used in the financial sector of the economy",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Moore\u2019s law?",
    "answer": "Moore\u2019s law is a name given to a prediction by Intel co-founder Gordon Moore that the number of transistors that could be put on a computer chip would roughly double every 2 years",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Quantum computing?",
    "answer": "Quantum computing is a field of computing that uses the principles of quantum mechanics to change the way computers store and process information",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Open banking,?",
    "answer": "Open banking, is a practice that involves the sharing of financial data between financial service providers through the use of\napplication programming interfaces (APIs)",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Cost per click (CPC)?",
    "answer": "Learn More:\nOpen Banking Definition\nKey Terms\nCost Per Click (CPC)\nMobile Commerce\nInsurtech\nQR Code\nMaterial Requirements Planning (MRP)\nMobile banking\nGraphics Processing Unit (GPU)\nCost Per Click (CPC)\nCost per click (CPC) is a model that some websites use to bill advertisers who advertise on their sites",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is That model?",
    "answer": "That model is called \u201c\ncost per mile",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Mobile commerce, also known as m-commerce,?",
    "answer": "\u201d\nLearn more\nMobile Commerce\nMobile commerce, also known as m-commerce, is the use of smartphones, cell phones, and similar mobile devices to make commercial transactions",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Insurtech?",
    "answer": "Learn more\nInsurtech\nInsurtech is a portmanteau of \u201cinsurance\u201d and \u201ctechnology,\u201d and refers to the technology used by the insurance industry",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A quick response (QR) code?",
    "answer": "Learn more\nQR Code\nA quick response (QR) code is a kind of barcode that can be read easily by a computer",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Material requirements planning (MRP)?",
    "answer": "Learn more\nMaterial Requirements Planning (MRP)\nMaterial requirements planning (MRP) is an inventory management system that uses software to keep track of and manage a business\u2019s inventory and supply chain",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Mobile banking?",
    "answer": "Learn more\nMobile banking\nMobile banking is when banking services are used via mobile devices such as smartphones",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is GPUs are a particular type of computer chip that?",
    "answer": "Learn more\nGraphics Processing Unit (GPU)\nGPUs are a particular type of computer chip that is specialized at creating computer graphics",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is However, the kind of mathematics involved in computer graphics?",
    "answer": "However, the kind of mathematics involved in computer graphics is of a similar type to the kind used to mind Bitcoin and train AIs, so the demand for GPUs has risen substantially in recent years as new uses have emerged",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, the kind of mathematics involved in computer graphics is of a similar type to the kind used to mind Bitcoin and train AIs, so the demand for GPUs has risen substantially in recent years as new uses have emerged?",
    "answer": "However, the kind of mathematics involved in computer graphics is of a similar type to the kind used to mind Bitcoin and train AIs, so the demand for GPUs has risen substantially in recent years as new uses have emerged",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 Best Cloud Storage Solutions for Small Business?",
    "answer": "How It Works, How To Get a Loan, and Fees\n8 Best Cloud Storage Solutions for Small Business\nIs Apple Pay Safe",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How It Works, How To Get a Loan, and Fees\n8 Best Cloud Storage Solutions for Small Business\nIs Apple Pay Safe?",
    "answer": "How It Works, How To Get a Loan, and Fees\n8 Best Cloud Storage Solutions for Small Business\nIs Apple Pay Safe",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is CHIPS UID: What it?",
    "answer": "The Future of Fintech\nCircle: A Blockchain-Based Financial Services Innovator\nDigital Transactions: Definition, Functionality, and Advantages\nHow Splitwise Makes Money\nRate of Adoption: How it Works, Examples\nDigital Transaction Management: What It is, How It Works\nSplit Payment: Meaning, Examples and Use Cases\nCHIPS UID: What it is and How it Works in Fintech\nAggregation: Meaning, Importance, Effects\nElectronic Payments Network (EPN): What it is, How it Works\nWhat Are Micropayments",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/financial-technology-and-automated-investing-4689759",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sana Siddiqui?",
    "answer": "Learn about our\neditorial policies\nUpdated December 30, 2025\nFact checked by\nSana Siddiqui\nFact checked by\nSana Siddiqui\nFull Bio\nSana Siddiqui is a former Research Analyst at Investopedia with over 10 years of experience focusing on financial products and services",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Who?",
    "answer": "Who Is a Personal Loan Loan Good For",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is LightStream, the online lending subsidiary of Truist Bank, ticks all the boxes (competitive APRs, no fees, flexible repayment terms) and?",
    "answer": "LightStream, the online lending subsidiary of Truist Bank, ticks all the boxes (competitive APRs, no fees, flexible repayment terms) and is our choice for the best personal loan",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, another lender may be better for you, depending on your circumstances?",
    "answer": "However, another lender may be better for you, depending on your circumstances",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Fund dispersal?",
    "answer": "Fund dispersal is fast, as soon as the same day if you accept a loan proposal before 2:30 p",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Although LightStream?",
    "answer": "Although LightStream is our top choice, it has some flaws",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The most glaring?",
    "answer": "The most glaring is the lack of loan pre-qualification, which Investopedia considers an important shopping tool",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is You\u2019ll have to complete an application to find out your loan details, which?",
    "answer": "You\u2019ll have to complete an application to find out your loan details, which means a small hit to your credit score",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is LightStream?",
    "answer": "LightStream is a solid choice if you have good to excellent credit, but you\u2019ll have to shop elsewhere if you don't",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Truist?",
    "answer": "Truist is headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is That focus on customer experience?",
    "answer": "That focus on customer experience is working for SoFi",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The APR?",
    "answer": "The APR is the cost of credit as a yearly rate and reflects both your interest rate and an origination fee of 9",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Autopay?",
    "answer": "Autopay is not required to receive a loan from SoFi",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Discover, with competitive APRs and no origination fee,?",
    "answer": "99%\nLoan Amount:\n$2,500 - $40,000\nLoan Terms:\n36 months - 84 months\nCheck Rates\n(opens in a new tab)\nOn Investopedia\nWhy We Chose It\nDiscover, with competitive APRs and no origination fee, is a good choice for personal loans for any reason",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Loan funding?",
    "answer": "Loan funding is fast, as soon as the next business day, if everything in your application is accurate",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One downside with Discover?",
    "answer": "One downside with Discover is that it does not accept co-signers or co-borrowers who can help borrowers with lower credit scores qualify for a loan",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The maximum loan amount ($40,000)?",
    "answer": "The maximum loan amount ($40,000) is not as high as many competing lenders, although the lower minimum ($2,500) makes it a good choice if you\u2019re looking for a smaller loan",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Upgrade?",
    "answer": "99%\nLoan Amount:\n$1,000 - $50,000\nLoan Terms:\n24 months - 84 months\nCheck Rates\n(opens in a new tab)\nOn Investopedia\nWhy We Chose It\nUpgrade is our choice for emergencies and quick funding because of its fast funding time and relaxed lending criteria, which makes a loan from Upgrade available to a broad range of borrowers in a pinch",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 99%, and its maximum APR?",
    "answer": "99%, and its maximum APR is 35",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A $200 bonus?",
    "answer": "A $200 bonus is also available for setting up and funding a checking account with Upgrade during your loan application",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Upgrade was founded in 2017 and?",
    "answer": "Upgrade was founded in 2017 and is headquartered in San Francisco",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In practice, that?",
    "answer": "In practice, that means it accepts borrowers with credit scores as low as 300",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If your credit score?",
    "answer": "Pros & Cons\nPros\nLow minimum credit score\nFast funding\nA wide range of loan amounts\nCons\nPotentially high origination fee\nHigh APRs for some borrowers\nFewer loan term options than competitors\nOverview\nIf your credit score is below 580, you don\u2019t have many options to borrow",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Upstart\u2019s minimum required credit score of 300?",
    "answer": "Upstart\u2019s minimum required credit score of 300 is the lowest of the 59 lenders in our database",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is (That rate cap?",
    "answer": "(That rate cap is linked to the Military Lending Act, which limits APRs on consumer loans for military service members at 36%",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The fintech lender?",
    "answer": "The fintech lender is headquartered in San Mateo, Calif",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The bank\u2019s maximum advertised APR?",
    "answer": "The bank\u2019s maximum advertised APR is low, and existing Citibank customers are eligible for same-day funding",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is or late fees, and its maximum advertised APR?",
    "answer": "Power ranking\nCons\nHigh starting APRs\nLower loan limits than other lenders\nMust be an existing Citibank customer\nOverview\nCitibank doesn\u2019t charge\norigination fees\nor late fees, and its maximum advertised APR is low, keeping borrowing costs down",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 50%?",
    "answer": "50% is higher than many other lenders offer (0",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Another perk for existing customers?",
    "answer": "Another perk for existing customers is same-day funding, which is sent directly to their Citibank account",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Citibank, founded in 1812,?",
    "answer": "Citibank, founded in 1812, is the third-largest U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A local credit union?",
    "answer": "00%\nLoan Amount:\n$250 - $25,000\nLoan Terms:\n1 month - 60 months\nCheck Rates\n(opens in a new tab)\nOn Investopedia\nWhy We Chose It\nA local credit union is your best bet for an affordable personal loan",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is We chose Lake Michigan Credit Union as the Best for Small Loan Amounts because its minimum of $250?",
    "answer": "We chose Lake Michigan Credit Union as the Best for Small Loan Amounts because its minimum of $250 is the lowest in our database of 59 lenders, but plenty of credit unions have minimums of $300 or $500",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, many credit unions offer loans under $1,000 and even under $500, so you have plenty of options?",
    "answer": "However, many credit unions offer loans under $1,000 and even under $500, so you have plenty of options",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Because it?",
    "answer": "Because it is a federal credit union, you won\u2019t pay more than 18% interest",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The minimum credit score of 650?",
    "answer": "The minimum credit score of 650 means LMCU loans are available to\npeople with \u201cfair\u201d credit",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This rating, developed by Investopedia researchers,?",
    "answer": "This rating, developed by Investopedia researchers, is an aggregate of consumer review ratings on two third-party review sites: Trustpilot and the Better Business Bureau",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Another knock against Navy Federal?",
    "answer": "Another knock against Navy Federal is that it does not offer\npre-qualification\n; you\u2019ll need to complete a loan application to learn the rates and terms you qualify for",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Navy Federal, founded in 1933 and headquartered in Vienna, Virginia,?",
    "answer": "Navy Federal, founded in 1933 and headquartered in Vienna, Virginia, is the nation\u2019s largest credit union",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Patelco Credit Union?",
    "answer": "Patelco Credit Union is the highest-scoring credit union in our rating model, and it\u2019s no wonder why",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The first?",
    "answer": "The first is a customer loyalty discount of 0",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5% of the late payment amount or $15, whichever?",
    "answer": "00%\n5% of the late payment amount or $15, whichever is greater\n1 days\n$1,000 - $75,000\n60 months\nCheck Rates\n(opens in a new tab)\nOn Investopedia\nHide, not for me\nCitibank\nBest Big Bank\n9",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4% of the balance that?",
    "answer": "00%\n4% of the balance that is due\n1 day\n$250 - $25,000\n60 months\nCheck Rates\n(opens in a new tab)\nOn Investopedia\nHide, not for me\nNavy Federal Credit Union\nBest for Military Members\n8",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 3% of loan payment or $5, whichever?",
    "answer": "00%\n3% of loan payment or $5, whichever is higher\n0 days\n$300 - $100,000\n84 months\nCheck Rates\n(opens in a new tab)\nOn Investopedia\nHide, not for me\n*APR ranges for some companies include a discount for automatic payments or existing bank customers",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Trust Us\nInvestopedia collected thousands of data points from dozens of lenders to evaluate the factors most important for borrowers?",
    "answer": "Why Trust Us\nInvestopedia collected thousands of data points from dozens of lenders to evaluate the factors most important for borrowers",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Borrower credit score?",
    "answer": "Personal Loan APRs by Credit Score\nBorrower credit score is a key factor in personal loan interest rates",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is personal loan?",
    "answer": "A\npersonal loan\nis a type of\ninstallment loan\nwhere borrowers receive a lump sum and then repay it in increments over a period of time",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is , on personal loans?",
    "answer": "Typically, the interest rate, or\nAnnual Percentage Rate (APR)\n, on personal loans is fixed, which means it doesn\u2019t fluctuate",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, some lenders specialize in loans for people with challenging credit?",
    "answer": "However, some lenders specialize in loans for people with challenging credit",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A personal loan?",
    "answer": "A personal loan is best for people who want flexibility in how they use their funds, prefer a lump-sum payment, and have a strong credit score",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is : This?",
    "answer": "Common Personal Loan Terms\nAnnual percentage rate (APR)\n: This is the yearly interest rate, including fees like origination fees, and is represented as a percentage",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is credit score?",
    "answer": "Credit Score\n: A\ncredit score\nis a three-digit number that indicates a borrower\u2019s creditworthiness",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A higher credit score generally?",
    "answer": "A higher credit score generally means that a borrower will receive better terms on a loan",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However,\npre-qualification\ndoes not guarantee approval?",
    "answer": "However,\npre-qualification\ndoes not guarantee approval",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, if you default on an unsecured loan, your account can be sent to collections, which can still negatively impact your credit score?",
    "answer": "However, if you default on an unsecured loan, your account can be sent to collections, which can still negatively impact your credit score",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is : To get the best terms on a personal loan, you\u2019ll probably want a FICO credit score that\u2019s considered \u201cgood\u201d or better\u2014that?",
    "answer": "Cons Explained\nNeed a good credit score to qualify for lower APRs\n: To get the best terms on a personal loan, you\u2019ll probably want a FICO credit score that\u2019s considered \u201cgood\u201d or better\u2014that means having a score of more than 670",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is : While receiving a lump sum?",
    "answer": "Lack of continued access to credit\n: While receiving a lump sum is useful to some, if\u00a0you prefer having access to an open\nline of credit\nthat allows you to borrow money as needed, you may consider opting for a credit card or something like a\nhome equity line of credit (HELOC)\nover a personal loan",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, if you\u2019re not diligent about paying off your balance on time and in full every month, the interest you pay on your credit card debt will exceed the value of the rewards you earn?",
    "answer": "However, if you\u2019re not diligent about paying off your balance on time and in full every month, the interest you pay on your credit card debt will exceed the value of the rewards you earn",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Interest rates are high, especially if your credit score?",
    "answer": "Interest rates are high, especially if your credit score is fair or poor",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In contrast, personal loans generally have fixed interest rates, so your monthly payment?",
    "answer": "In contrast, personal loans generally have fixed interest rates, so your monthly payment is fixed",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Generally, credit cards are a better choice if you\u2019re looking to finance everyday expenses, while a personal loan?",
    "answer": "Generally, credit cards are a better choice if you\u2019re looking to finance everyday expenses, while a personal loan is a better choice if you want a lump-sum payment for debt consolidation or paying off a major expense",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is home equity loan?",
    "answer": "Home Equity Loans\nA\nhome equity loan\nis a type of mortgage loan that allows you to borrow against the equity you have in your home",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Since your home equity?",
    "answer": "Since your home equity is considered collateral with a home equity loan, you could be at\nrisk of foreclosure\nif you can\u2019t pay it off",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Plus, if the value of your home declines, you may end up paying more than your home?",
    "answer": "Plus, if the value of your home declines, you may end up paying more than your home is worth",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One upside of a home equity loan?",
    "answer": "One upside of a home equity loan is that your interest payments can be tax-deductible if you use the funds to \u201cbuy, build, or substantially improve the residence,\u201d according to the IRS",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If you're looking to borrow from a traditional bank, our choice?",
    "answer": "If you're looking to borrow from a traditional bank, our choice is\nCitibank",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What Credit Score?",
    "answer": "What Credit Score Is Needed for a Personal Loan",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Credit Score Is Needed for a Personal Loan?",
    "answer": "What Credit Score Is Needed for a Personal Loan",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, this can vary quite a bit; some lenders, such as Upstart, have no minimum credit score requirement?",
    "answer": "However, this can vary quite a bit; some lenders, such as Upstart, have no minimum credit score requirement",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Would a $5,000 Personal Loan Cost per Month?",
    "answer": "How Much Would a $5,000 Personal Loan Cost per Month",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The easiest way to calculate a monthly payment?",
    "answer": "The easiest way to calculate a monthly payment is to use a\npersonal loan calculator",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, credit unions may not be as convenient as banks or fintechs, due to credit union membership requirements?",
    "answer": "However, credit unions may not be as convenient as banks or fintechs, due to credit union membership requirements",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How We Chose the Best Personal Loans\nInvestopedia collected more than 2,600 data points from 59 lenders, including traditional banks, credit unions, fintechs, and finance companies to evaluate and rank the best personal loan providers?",
    "answer": "How We Chose the Best Personal Loans\nInvestopedia collected more than 2,600 data points from 59 lenders, including traditional banks, credit unions, fintechs, and finance companies to evaluate and rank the best personal loan providers",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201c?",
    "answer": "\u201c\nIs Interest Paid on a Home Equity Loan or a Home Equity Line of Credit (HELOC) Deductible",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/the-best-personal-loans-8761582",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Do I Exercise Them?",
    "answer": "How Do I Exercise Them",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Frequently Asked Questions?",
    "answer": "Understanding Securitization: Definition, Benefits, Risks, and Real-Life Example\nFrequently Asked Questions\nIs options trading a derivative",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Yes, the simplest derivative investment allows individuals to buy or sell what?",
    "answer": "Yes, the simplest derivative investment allows individuals to buy or sell what is known as an option on a security",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An option?",
    "answer": "An option is a contract to buy or sell a specific financial product",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How big?",
    "answer": "Learn More:\nETF Futures and Options\nHow big is the derivatives market",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The entire derivatives market is, simply put, huge, and top estimates can be more than $1 quadrillion on the high end, based on what?",
    "answer": "The entire derivatives market is, simply put, huge, and top estimates can be more than $1 quadrillion on the high end, based on what is included as a derivative",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How Big?",
    "answer": "Learn More:\nHow Big Is the Derivatives Market",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a forward contract?",
    "answer": "What is a forward contract",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A forward contract?",
    "answer": "A forward contract is a derivatives instrument that is one of the oldest and most common types of derivative securities, in which counterparties agree to buy (receive) or sell (deliver) an asset at a specified price on a future date",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A futures contract?",
    "answer": "A futures contract is an agreement to buy or sell shares of an underlying ETF at an agreed-upon price on or before a specified date",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Cboe Options Exchange?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nCboe Options Exchange\nThe Cboe Options Exchange is the world's largest options exchange that was founded in 1973",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Warrant coverage?",
    "answer": "Warrant coverage is an agreement between a company and shareholders in which the company issues a warrant that is worth some percentage of the dollar amount of their investment",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A warrant premium?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nWarrant Premium\nA warrant premium is the difference between the traded price of a warrant and its minimum value",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A warrant's minimum value?",
    "answer": "A warrant's minimum value is the difference between its exercise price and the current traded price of its underlying stock",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A weather derivative?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nWeather Derivative\nA weather derivative is a financial product that companies or investors can use to hedge risk against weather-related disasters, much like insurance",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Freight derivatives are financial products that derive their value from various freight agreements and freight rates, such as dry bulk carrying rates, and?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nFreight Derivatives\nFreight derivatives are financial products that derive their value from various freight agreements and freight rates, such as dry bulk carrying rates, and is used primarily in the shipping and cargo industry to manage the risk of fluctuating levels of freight charges or oil tanker rates changing unexpectedly",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Transaction risk?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nTransaction Risk\nTransaction risk is the risk that an investor or company may take on when currency exchange rate fluctuations may change the value of a foreign transaction after a transaction has been completed but not yet settled, and can also be referred to as exchange rate, or currency risk",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Transaction risk takes on greater risk when there?",
    "answer": "Transaction risk takes on greater risk when there is a longer time between when the transaction occurs and when it settles",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A cashless conversion?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nCashless Conversion\nA cashless conversion is when the ownership of some kind of security or asset changes without cash payment by the owner",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For example such a conversation may take place if convertible bonds or convertible preferred shares are part of a transaction in which there?",
    "answer": "For example such a conversation may take place if convertible bonds or convertible preferred shares are part of a transaction in which there is a cashless conversion to common stock in the deal",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Do You Trade the Weather?",
    "answer": "How Do You Trade the Weather",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How?",
    "answer": "Outright Forward: What it is, How it Works\nHow is the price of a derivative determined",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Are the Main Risks Associated With Trading Derivatives?",
    "answer": "What Are the Main Risks Associated With Trading Derivatives",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/options-and-derivatives-trading-4689663",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Apply for Student Loans\nStudent Loan Interest Rates\nHow Long Does It Take to Pay Off Student Loan Debt?",
    "answer": "How to Apply for Student Loans\nStudent Loan Interest Rates\nHow Long Does It Take to Pay Off Student Loan Debt",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Unsubsidized Student Loans\u2014Which?",
    "answer": "Unsubsidized Student Loans\u2014Which Is Best",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Following a certain period of delinquency, which varies based on the type of loan, there?",
    "answer": "Following a certain period of delinquency, which varies based on the type of loan, there is also a risk of the loan going into\ndefault",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, according to the Debt Collection Improvement Act of 1996, up to 15% of your Social Security payments can be garnished to repay your federal student loan(s) should you default?",
    "answer": "However, according to the Debt Collection Improvement Act of 1996, up to 15% of your Social Security payments can be garnished to repay your federal student loan(s) should you default",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An education loan, more commonly known as a student loan,?",
    "answer": "Learn More:\nHeading Into Retirement With Student Loans\nKey Terms\nEducation Loan\nFederal Direct Loan Program\nFree Application for Federal Student Aid (FAFSA)\nFAFSA Award Letter\nDeferment Period\nPLUS Loan\nDirect Consolidation Loan\nStudent Loan Interest Deduction\nEducation Loan\nAn education loan, more commonly known as a student loan, is an amount of money borrowed from a federal or private lender to pay for a higher education",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ford Federal Direct Loan Program?",
    "answer": "Ford Federal Direct Loan Program is a federal student loan program offered by the U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Federal Direct Loan Program?",
    "answer": "The Federal Direct Loan Program is available to eligible postsecondary students and their parents",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Free Application for Federal Student Aid (FAFSA)?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nFree Application for Federal Student Aid (FAFSA)\nThe Free Application for Federal Student Aid (FAFSA) is an official form that must be filled out in order to receive financial aid from the federal government",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The FAFSA?",
    "answer": "The FAFSA is available starting Oct",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 of the year prior to enrollment, and the federal due date?",
    "answer": "1 of the year prior to enrollment, and the federal due date is June 30 of the academic year (some colleges and/or states have their own deadlines)",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A FAFSA award letter?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nFAFSA Award Letter\nA FAFSA award letter is provided by the colleges that are listed on your FAFSA form and details the cost of attendance for an academic year and your eligibility for any grants, loans, etc",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A deferment period?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nDeferment Period\nA deferment period is an amount of time where a borrower isn't required to repay their loan's principal or interest",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A PLUS loan?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nPLUS Loan\nA PLUS loan is offered to graduate & professional students and the parents of dependent undergraduates",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While eligibility isn\u2019t based on financial need, a credit check?",
    "answer": "While eligibility isn\u2019t based on financial need, a credit check is required, and borrowers with an adverse credit history won\u2019t be eligible without meeting other criteria",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The deduction?",
    "answer": "The deduction is only available if you meet certain eligibility criteria, and it\u2019s gradually reduced as your modified adjusted gross income (MAGI) reaches its annual limit",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This interest deduction?",
    "answer": "This interest deduction is claimed as an adjustment to income, so it don't need to itemized on your income tax returns",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Just How Bad?",
    "answer": "Discover Which Jobs Qualify for Student Loan Forgiveness in 2025\n5 States That Will Tax Your Federal Student Loan Forgiveness: What Borrowers Need to Know\nAmericans With Student Debt Slash Spending, Yet Still Struggle to Keep Up With Loan Payments\nExplore Student Loans\nAll\nReviews\nSaving for College\nJust How Bad Is Your Student Loan Debt",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How Much Debt?",
    "answer": "Here Are All the Other Ways You Can Pay for College\nHow Much Debt Is Too Much for Aspiring Lawyers\u2014and Are You Going to Earn Enough To Pay It Off",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Much Debt Is Too Much for Aspiring Doctors\u2014and Are You Going to Earn Enough To Pay It Off?",
    "answer": "How Much Debt Is Too Much for Aspiring Doctors\u2014and Are You Going to Earn Enough To Pay It Off",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is These States Have the Most and Least Student Loan Debt\u2014the Difference?",
    "answer": "Here's Where to Find More Funding\nThese States Have the Most and Least Student Loan Debt\u2014the Difference Is Huge\nWhat SAVE Borrowers Must Consider Before Switching IDR Plans\nThese Are the Majors With the Least Student Loan Debt\u2014and Which Ones to Avoid to Save Thousands\nWhat Effects Would Mass Student Loan Defaults Have on the US Economy",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Hidden Cost of Student Loan Forbearance Might Be More Than You Expect?",
    "answer": "Here's the Strategy to Turn That 'No' Into a 'Yes'\nThe Hidden Cost of Student Loan Forbearance Might Be More Than You Expect\nIs Student Debt Stressing Your Relationship",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Disqualifies You From Student Loans: Understanding Eligibility Requirements\nPaying Off Student Loans vs?",
    "answer": "What Disqualifies You From Student Loans: Understanding Eligibility Requirements\nPaying Off Student Loans vs",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When Can I Expect to Receive Information About My Financial Aid?",
    "answer": "When Can I Expect to Receive Information About My Financial Aid",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/student-loans-4689727",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In a command economy, a centralized government controls the?",
    "answer": "In a command economy, a centralized government controls the means of production and it decides the output levels for that production",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This type of economy?",
    "answer": "This type of economy is often associated with communist nations",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The advantages of this approach include better equality and lower unemployment, but there?",
    "answer": "The advantages of this approach include better equality and lower unemployment, but there is often a lack of efficiency or innovation in those economies",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A market economy, or free economy,?",
    "answer": "A market economy, or free economy, is directed through the laws of supply and demand to set the prices and quantities for most goods and services",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does inflation do to an economy?",
    "answer": "What does inflation do to an economy",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Inflation?",
    "answer": "Inflation means the rate at which the same goods and services come to cost more",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But if some level of inflation?",
    "answer": "But if some level of inflation is expected, it can drive consumer spending, which drives economic growth",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is When?",
    "answer": "Learn More:\nWhen Is Inflation Good for the Economy\nHow stocks help the economy\nWhen the price of a large number of stocks is on the rise, it can lead to higher consumer and business confidence, higher spending on big-ticket items such as cars and houses, and an increase in investors entering the stock market",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of economy does the U?",
    "answer": "What type of economy does the U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Learn More:?",
    "answer": "Learn More:\nIs the United States a Market Economy or a Mixed Economy",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The management of those resources?",
    "answer": "The management of those resources is used to satisfy the needs of the people, businesses, organizations, and governments in a specific area",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Currency, or money,?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nMoney\nCurrency, or money, is a generally accepted, recognized, and centralized medium of exchange that market participants use to engage in transactions for goods and services in an economy",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Each government has its own money system that?",
    "answer": "Each government has its own money system that is monitored by a central authority",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The buying, selling, or bartering of goods and services?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nTrade\nThe buying, selling, or bartering of goods and services is known as trade",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An exchange of goods and services between two countries?",
    "answer": "An exchange of goods and services between two countries is international trade",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A knowledge economy?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nKnowledge Economy\nA knowledge economy is a system of consumption and production based on the intangible assets of intellectual capital",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Wealthy?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nWealth\nWealthy is an abundant supply of valuable economic assets or resources owned by a person, company, community, or nation",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The law of supply and demand?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nLaw of Supply and Demand\nThe law of supply and demand is an economic theory based on two separate \"laws\" that explain the interaction between the sellers of a resource and the buyers of that resource",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is of a specific currency over time?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nInflation\nA decline of the\npurchasing power\nof a specific currency over time is known as inflation",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The rise in the general level of prices, often expressed as a percentage,?",
    "answer": "The rise in the general level of prices, often expressed as a percentage, means that a unit of currency effectively buys less than it did in prior periods",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The colloquial phrase \"sluggish economy\"?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nSluggish Economy\nThe colloquial phrase \"sluggish economy\" is not an exact and quantifiable thing",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Gross domestic product (GDP)?",
    "answer": "Learn More\nGross Domestic Product (GDP)\nGross domestic product (GDP) is a broad measure of a country's overall domestic production and a measure of that country's overall economic health",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Self-Driving Cars Could Change the Auto Industry\nUnderstanding the New Economy: Definition, History, and Key Companies\nAmerican Dream: The History, Evolution, and Definition\nWage Gaps by Gender\nUnderstanding Centrally Planned Economies: Features, Pros, and Examples\nThe Cost of Unemployment to the Economy\nUnderstanding Contract Provisions: Key Concepts and FAQs\nWhat Happens When a Utility Goes Bankrupt?",
    "answer": "How Self-Driving Cars Could Change the Auto Industry\nUnderstanding the New Economy: Definition, History, and Key Companies\nAmerican Dream: The History, Evolution, and Definition\nWage Gaps by Gender\nUnderstanding Centrally Planned Economies: Features, Pros, and Examples\nThe Cost of Unemployment to the Economy\nUnderstanding Contract Provisions: Key Concepts and FAQs\nWhat Happens When a Utility Goes Bankrupt",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A Comprehensive Guide?",
    "answer": "A Comprehensive Guide\nIs Deflation Bad for the Economy",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/economy-4689801",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Will Baker?",
    "answer": "Best Crypto Exchanges and Apps for January 2026\nBy\nWill Baker\nFull Bio\nWill Baker is a full-time associate editor at Investopedia",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Our exhaustive research has revealed that Kraken?",
    "answer": "Our exhaustive research has revealed that Kraken is best for users seeking low fees",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Experienced traders who value a high degree of platform security may want to consider Gemini, while Coinbase?",
    "answer": "Experienced traders who value a high degree of platform security may want to consider Gemini, while Coinbase is best for beginners",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is com?",
    "answer": "com is best for mobile users who often trade on the go",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Last but not least, cryptocurrency enthusiasts seeking digital assets not found anywhere else will find that BitMart?",
    "answer": "Last but not least, cryptocurrency enthusiasts seeking digital assets not found anywhere else will find that BitMart is best for altcoins",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs)?",
    "answer": "com\nBest for Altcoins:\nBitMart\nImportant\nInvesting in cryptocurrencies,\nDecentralized Finance (DeFi)\n, and other\nInitial Coin Offerings (ICOs)\nis highly risky and speculative, and the markets can be extremely volatile",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This article?",
    "answer": "This article is not a recommendation by Investopedia or the writer to invest in cryptocurrencies, nor can the accuracy or timeliness of the information be guaranteed",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Kraken crypto exchange?",
    "answer": "40%\u00a0on Kraken Pro\nAvailable cryptocurrencies:\n540+\nOpen Account\n(opens in a new tab)\nWhy We Chose It\nThe Kraken crypto exchange is Investopedia\u2019s choice for low fees",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Kraken?",
    "answer": "Pros & Cons\nPros\nLow fees for beginning and advanced cryptocurrency traders\nA good selection of educational resources and research amenities\nAccess to web, desktop, mobile, and Kraken Pro platform\nCons\nKraken is not available in all 50 U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While the company has gone fully remote, its head office?",
    "answer": "While the company has gone fully remote, its head office is in San Francisco, CA",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This platform?",
    "answer": "This platform is designed for traders who need access to advanced order types, charting, and screening capabilities not offered on the original platform",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Kraken Pro's best feature?",
    "answer": "The Kraken Pro's best feature is that it\u2019s free to use",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, Kraken comes with potential drawbacks?",
    "answer": "However, Kraken comes with potential drawbacks",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While Kraken operates in many countries, the exchange?",
    "answer": "While Kraken operates in many countries, the exchange is not available in all 50 U",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Prospective clients interested in a specific service should check if it?",
    "answer": "Prospective clients interested in a specific service should check if it is legal in their respective state",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Gemini?",
    "answer": "40%\nAvailable cryptocurrencies:\n70+\nOpen Account\n(opens in a new tab)\nWhy We Chose It\nBest For Security\nGemini is our top choice for security",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In addition to being our choice for security, Gemini?",
    "answer": "Best for Experienced Traders\nIn addition to being our choice for security, Gemini is also our top choice for experienced traders due to its ActiveTrader software",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Gemini was founded in 2014 and?",
    "answer": "states\nPass-through FDIC insurance for uninvested cash and crypto insurance\nCons\nOffers a low number of cryptocurrencies\nCustomer support only has a request form\nComplex fee structure\nOverview\nGemini was founded in 2014 and is currently headquartered in New York, N",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Due to its high security standards, Gemini?",
    "answer": "Due to its high security standards, Gemini is our choice for users who value security for their cryptocurrency holdings",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, Gemini also supports external hardware security keys, such as YubiKey, to secure accounts further?",
    "answer": "However, Gemini also supports external hardware security keys, such as YubiKey, to secure accounts further",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Users also have the option to store their cryptocurrency in either Gemini\u2019s hot wallet, which?",
    "answer": "Users also have the option to store their cryptocurrency in either Gemini\u2019s hot wallet, which is insured, or its cold wallet",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, Gemini\u2019s ActiveTrader deserves recognition as a highly advanced platform capable of reaching trade execution speeds of 65 microseconds?",
    "answer": "However, Gemini\u2019s ActiveTrader deserves recognition as a highly advanced platform capable of reaching trade execution speeds of 65 microseconds",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Coinbase?",
    "answer": "60%\nAvailable cryptocurrencies:\n300+\nOpen Account\n(opens in a new tab)\nOn with Coinbase\nWhy We Chose It\nCoinbase is best for beginners due to its sleek user interface, solid security infrastructure, and a reasonable fee structure that is easy to understand",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Cryptocurrency?",
    "answer": "Cryptocurrency is a complicated\nalternative investment\nthat requires careful study by traders",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, Coinbase\u2019s educational resources, which cover basic and advanced trading topics, can help clarify its complexity?",
    "answer": "However, Coinbase\u2019s educational resources, which cover basic and advanced trading topics, can help clarify its complexity",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The basic version?",
    "answer": "The basic version is a simple chart with essential data such as market cap, volume, and other metrics that beginning traders will find valuable",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is However, it does not provide any charting tools, which?",
    "answer": "However, it does not provide any charting tools, which is why Coinbase also has an advanced version",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, it does not provide any charting tools, which is why Coinbase also has an advanced version?",
    "answer": "However, it does not provide any charting tools, which is why Coinbase also has an advanced version",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, depending on their 30-day trade volume, users can expect maker fees to be between 0?",
    "answer": "However, depending on their 30-day trade volume, users can expect maker fees to be between 0",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Bitcoin traders will also have access to Bitcoin options and futures, which?",
    "answer": "Bitcoin traders will also have access to Bitcoin options and futures, which is an important feature for traders and investors alike",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Bitmart, which offers over 1,700 cryptocurrencies,?",
    "answer": "BitMart\nMinimum deposit:\nNot publicly disclosed\nMaker fees:\nNot publicly disclosed\nTaker fees:\nNot publicly disclosed\nAvailable cryptocurrencies:\n1,700+\nOpen Account\n(opens in a new tab)\nWhy We Chose It\nBitmart, which offers over 1,700 cryptocurrencies, is our top choice as the best crypto exchange for\naltcoins",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Its fee structure?",
    "answer": "Pros & Cons\nPros\nAccess to over 1,700 cryptocurrencies\nAllows social trading through its copy-trading feature\nBitMart Academy provides excellent educational resources\nCons\nDoes not display its security infrastructure\nIts fee structure is not publicly disclosed without an account\nOnly supports crypto deposits to fund account\nOverview\nBitMart, founded in 2017 and headquartered in New York, N",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is ,?",
    "answer": ", is our top choice for altcoins due to its accessibility to over 1,700 tradable cryptocurrencies",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, traders should remember that past success does not automatically lead to future gains and should proceed cautiously?",
    "answer": "However, traders should remember that past success does not automatically lead to future gains and should proceed cautiously",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In addition, the only way to fund a new account?",
    "answer": "In addition, the only way to fund a new account is to transfer crypto from a wallet or another exchange",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why You Should Trust Us\nInvestopedia launched in 1999, and since 2020, we have independently researched 14 cryptocurrency exchanges currently operating in the industry?",
    "answer": "Why You Should Trust Us\nInvestopedia launched in 1999, and since 2020, we have independently researched 14 cryptocurrency exchanges currently operating in the industry",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How We Picked the Best Cryptocurrency Exchanges and Apps\nInvestopedia's in-house team of researchers collected nearly 450 data points through online research of 14 leading cryptocurrency exchange provider websites?",
    "answer": "How We Picked the Best Cryptocurrency Exchanges and Apps\nInvestopedia's in-house team of researchers collected nearly 450 data points through online research of 14 leading cryptocurrency exchange provider websites",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The score for each company\u2019s overall star rating?",
    "answer": "The score for each company\u2019s overall star rating is a weighted average of the criteria in the following categories:\nTrading Features: 30%\nFees: 28%\nSecurity: 21%\nTransparency: 21%\nThrough our research, Investopedia has provided you with a list of the best crypto exchanges, guided by data-driven analysis and an unbiased and fair approach to helping readers find the best crypto exchange",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Kraken shuts down global headquarters because \u2018San Francisco?",
    "answer": "\"\nKraken shuts down global headquarters because \u2018San Francisco is not safe",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Where?",
    "answer": "\"\nWhere is Kraken Licensed or Regulated",
    "source_url": "https://www.investopedia.com/best-crypto-exchanges-5071855",
    "domain": "investopedia.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "investopedia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Superyacht Insurance Brokers Ltd?",
    "answer": "Superyacht Insurance Brokers Ltd is Regulated and Authorised by the Financial Conduct Authority \u2013 FRN 844548\nThis site uses cookies",
    "source_url": "https://superyachtinsurancebrokers.com/news/superyacht-insurance-clients/",
    "domain": "superyachtinsurancebrokers.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "superyachtinsurancebrokers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Monaco?",
    "answer": "Monaco is one of the largest centres for superyachts in the world",
    "source_url": "https://superyachtinsurancebrokers.com/news/superyacht-insurance-monaco/",
    "domain": "superyachtinsurancebrokers.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "superyachtinsurancebrokers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Heesen Superyacht?",
    "answer": "The way the owners & crew have cared for this fabulous example of a\nHeesen Superyacht\nis outstanding",
    "source_url": "https://superyachtinsurancebrokers.com/news/monaco-yacht-show/",
    "domain": "superyachtinsurancebrokers.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "superyachtinsurancebrokers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Florida weather?",
    "answer": "The\nFort Lauderdale\nFlorida weather is set to be perfect",
    "source_url": "https://superyachtinsurancebrokers.com/news/fort-lauderdale-boat-show-2/",
    "domain": "superyachtinsurancebrokers.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "superyachtinsurancebrokers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is the Jones Act?",
    "answer": "What Is the Jones Act",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is , formally known as the Merchant Marine Act of 1920,?",
    "answer": "A Guide for Yacht Owners\nThe Jones Act\n, formally known as the Merchant Marine Act of 1920, is one of the most critical pieces of legislation in U",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While you may have heard this term within shipping, boating, or insurance discussions, understanding its wide-reaching implications?",
    "answer": "While you may have heard this term within shipping, boating, or insurance discussions, understanding its wide-reaching implications is essential, especially if you\u2019re a yacht owner or maritime professional with captain/crew exposures",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Jones Act?",
    "answer": "The Jones Act is a federal law designed to protect U",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For yacht owners, one of the most critical aspects of the Jones Act?",
    "answer": "For yacht owners, one of the most critical aspects of the Jones Act is its focus on safety and working conditions for maritime workers",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What about liability?",
    "answer": "Liability and Negligence\nUnder the Jones Act, yacht owners can be held responsible for injuries caused by negligence or unsafe conditions on board",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One of the essential provisions of the Jones Act?",
    "answer": "Maintenance and Cure\nOne of the essential provisions of the Jones Act is the requirement to provide \u201cmaintenance and cure\u201d for injured crew members",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Jones Act includes an implied warranty of seaworthiness, meaning that as a yacht owner, you are obligated to ensure that your vessel?",
    "answer": "Seaworthiness Requirement\nThe Jones Act includes an implied warranty of seaworthiness, meaning that as a yacht owner, you are obligated to ensure that your vessel is reasonably fit for its intended use",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If a captain/crew member?",
    "answer": "If a captain/crew member is injured due to the vessel\u2019s unseaworthiness, they may have grounds to file a negligence claim for which the yacht owner would be liable",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is W3 Insurance\u2019s team of marine insurance experts?",
    "answer": "W3 Insurance\u2019s team of marine insurance experts is here to help",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This overview?",
    "answer": "This overview is intended for informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Why?",
    "answer": "Why Is the Jones Act Controversial",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Is the Jones Act Controversial?",
    "answer": "Why Is the Jones Act Controversial",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, supporters view it as vital for protecting national security and the U?",
    "answer": "However, supporters view it as vital for protecting national security and the U",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This field?",
    "answer": "Why a Resume of Experience Matters for Yacht Insurance\nThe Best Storage Options to Protect Your Boat\nTravel Guide: From Florida to The Bahamas By Boat\nProtect Your Power Boat From Lightning Strikes\nAuthor\nbigsea\nSubscribe to Marine Blog\nEmail\n*\nEmail\nThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why a Resume of Experience Matters for Yacht Insurance\nThe Best Storage Options to Protect Your Boat\nTravel Guide: From Florida to The Bahamas By Boat\nProtect Your Power Boat From Lightning Strikes\nAuthor\nbigsea\nSubscribe to Marine Blog\nEmail\n*\nEmail\nThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged?",
    "answer": "Why a Resume of Experience Matters for Yacht Insurance\nThe Best Storage Options to Protect Your Boat\nTravel Guide: From Florida to The Bahamas By Boat\nProtect Your Power Boat From Lightning Strikes\nAuthor\nbigsea\nSubscribe to Marine Blog\nEmail\n*\nEmail\nThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is WW&W?",
    "answer": "Request a Quote\n\u00a92024 Wallace Welch & Willingham\nWW&W is not affiliated with W3 Wealth Management, LLC, owner of the USPTO trademark registration no",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/04/what-is-the-jones-act/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Here?",
    "answer": "Here is everything you need to know about owning a boat in Florida",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The number one most important element to consider when purchasing a boat in Florida?",
    "answer": "Basic Boat Safety Tips\nThe number one most important element to consider when purchasing a boat in Florida is the boating prowess of the owner",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A vessel that?",
    "answer": "A vessel that is too large, or that demands more than your training level, may leave you sitting on the shore, uncertain",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Having a high level of confidence regarding the craft you captain?",
    "answer": "Having a high level of confidence regarding the craft you captain is the most basic of basic boat safety tips",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The next \u2018must have\u2019 element for every boat owner?",
    "answer": "The next \u2018must have\u2019 element for every boat owner is the\nboat safety kit\n, which should always remain aboard",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Just as a Florida homeowner?",
    "answer": "Just as a Florida homeowner is advised to keep a hurricane preparedness kit just in case, so too must the Florida boat owner have a selection of items that help in the event of an accident or loss of power",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The emergency radio?",
    "answer": "The emergency radio is there even if your cell phone isn\u2019t \u2013 a link between you and those on shore",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A whistle?",
    "answer": "A whistle is a simple object that can help to alert others of your presence and need for help",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u2013 The need for the fire extinguisher?",
    "answer": "Fire extinguisher and garbage bags\n\u2013 The need for the fire extinguisher is apparent, but garbage bags",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Look for a course that?",
    "answer": "Look for a course that is Florida-approved; different options exist, including online selections",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is After you\u2019ve aced your Florida boating safety course, make sure you know what to do if your boat breaks down or?",
    "answer": "After you\u2019ve aced your Florida boating safety course, make sure you know what to do if your boat breaks down or is involved in an accident",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Should a boating accident or breakdown occur, do an immediate check of everyone aboard for injury and to see what medical attention, if any,?",
    "answer": "Boating Accident and Breakdown Guide\nShould a boating accident or breakdown occur, do an immediate check of everyone aboard for injury and to see what medical attention, if any, is needed",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What to do when involved in a boating accident\nDocument\nthe moment as much as possible?",
    "answer": "What to do when involved in a boating accident\nDocument\nthe moment as much as possible",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What to do in the event of a breakdown\nTry to move your craft out of the way\n, if possible, if you are on a heavily-traveled waterway?",
    "answer": "What to do in the event of a breakdown\nTry to move your craft out of the way\n, if possible, if you are on a heavily-traveled waterway",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where to store your boat\nIt\u2019s important to know what to do\non\nthe water, but how are you protecting your boat when you\u2019re\nnot\nexploring the Florida waterways?",
    "answer": "Where to store your boat\nIt\u2019s important to know what to do\non\nthe water, but how are you protecting your boat when you\u2019re\nnot\nexploring the Florida waterways",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Storing your boat in Florida?",
    "answer": "Storing your boat in Florida is quite easy",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Exposing your craft to the elements?",
    "answer": "Exposing your craft to the elements\nis a surefire way for it to deteriorate more quickly",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A pervasive example of this?",
    "answer": "A pervasive example of this is upholstery",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Storage at a marina?",
    "answer": "Marina storage\nStorage at a marina is another viable way to keep your boat safe and at the ready for future voyages",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This storage option?",
    "answer": "This storage option is attractive to those who boat rarely or don\u2019t reside in Florida permanently",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Boatyard storage?",
    "answer": "Boatyard storage\nBoatyard storage is a hybrid Florida boat storage option that combines dry stack storage with near-marina storage",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Salt water?",
    "answer": "Salt water is highly corrosive to boats and, for those not in salt water, weather damage can be catastrophic",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Florida marine insurance?",
    "answer": "Importance of marine insurance\nFlorida marine insurance is so absolutely vital",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When it comes to everything you need to know to own a boat in this beautiful state, understanding marine insurance ranks near the top of requirements for safe boating?",
    "answer": "When it comes to everything you need to know to own a boat in this beautiful state, understanding marine insurance ranks near the top of requirements for safe boating",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Marine insurance?",
    "answer": "Marine insurance is the ultimate protection for your vessel",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is , as it?",
    "answer": "Call an experienced advisor\nto compile a\npersonalized policy\n, as it is easy to miss a vital part of insurance protection",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is That\u2019s what Florida marine insurance?",
    "answer": "That\u2019s what Florida marine insurance is there for\u2013 to protect you and your craft in a worst-case scenario, while allowing you to go on every voyage with the calm that comes from that protection",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/everything-you-need-to-know-to-own-a-boat-in-florida/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is JavaScript?",
    "answer": "JavaScript is not available",
    "source_url": "https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?original_referer=https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/&url=https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is We\u2019ve detected that JavaScript?",
    "answer": "We\u2019ve detected that JavaScript is disabled in this browser",
    "source_url": "https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?original_referer=https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/&url=https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is First, let\u2019s answer the obvious question: Why?",
    "answer": "First, let\u2019s answer the obvious question: Why is it important to properly store your boat",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Therefore, it?",
    "answer": "Therefore, it is important to have a plan for securing your boat accordingly",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How you do that?",
    "answer": "How you do that is up to you, but this guide can help you decide",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How you do that is up to you, but this guide can help you decide?",
    "answer": "How you do that is up to you, but this guide can help you decide",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What really wins the blue ribbon for \u2018the best boat storage option\u2019 depends on the type of boat and the storage options that are actually nearby?",
    "answer": "What really wins the blue ribbon for \u2018the best boat storage option\u2019 depends on the type of boat and the storage options that are actually nearby",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The answer that?",
    "answer": "The answer that is right for one Florida boat owner is different from the answer for another",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If you do not care how long your vessel stays pristine, this?",
    "answer": "If you do not care how long your vessel stays pristine, this is a great option",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Hopefully, you have a plan to take it out and secure a different?",
    "answer": "Hopefully, you have a plan to take it out and secure a different means of storage as soon as possible",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For those boat owners who use boat lifts, this?",
    "answer": "Lift storage\nFor those boat owners who use boat lifts, this is a viable means of boat storage",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One of the benefits of lift storage?",
    "answer": "One of the benefits of lift storage is that the boat will be\neasy to launch\n; this may mean that you and your family will use it more often than you might if the vessel were at an offsite location",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A boat that?",
    "answer": "A boat that is overrun by storm surge may break free of its tether",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Internet?",
    "answer": "The Internet is full of shocking pictures of boats tipped half-in, half-out of the water or nudged into neighboring backyards by strong currents, wind, & tidal surge",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is are two options, and as for cost, a good rule?",
    "answer": "Platform lifts and profile lifts\nare two options, and as for cost, a good rule is to expect to pay approximately $1 for every pound that the lift will have to hoist",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For the sake of preparedness, this?",
    "answer": "For the sake of preparedness, this is definitely a time to overestimate your costs",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An outdoor boatyard?",
    "answer": "Outdoor boatyard\nAn outdoor boatyard is another option",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One option?",
    "answer": "One option is the\nwet slip\n, in which a vessel will securely float in the water",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Often, this storage area?",
    "answer": "Often, this storage area is covered and offers fair protection from the elements",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Still, this?",
    "answer": "Still, this is a version of that in-water storage that can lead to corrosion of the paint and other wear-and-tear",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Another option?",
    "answer": "Another option is a\nlift slip\n, which is just what it sounds like",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The boat?",
    "answer": "The boat is lifted out of the water, which helps prevent the erosion it can suffer in the water",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, not every marina covers its lifts, meaning that the elements can affect the vessel?",
    "answer": "However, not every marina covers its lifts, meaning that the elements can affect the vessel",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This can cause major problems if a storm hits and the boat?",
    "answer": "This can cause major problems if a storm hits and the boat is not properly secured",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This adds another step to the preparation you must do before taking the boat out on the water, so consider whether high-and-dry storage?",
    "answer": "This adds another step to the preparation you must do before taking the boat out on the water, so consider whether high-and-dry storage is too much of a hassle",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The cheapest mode of storage?",
    "answer": "The cheapest mode of storage is obviously at-home storage",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is No matter which way you choose to store a boat, it?",
    "answer": "No matter which way you choose to store a boat, it is\nimportant to properly insure it",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Though Florida does not require marine insurance for boat owners, electing not to purchase a policy?",
    "answer": "Though Florida does not require marine insurance for boat owners, electing not to purchase a policy is a huge risk",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The best course of action?",
    "answer": "The best course of action is to\nselect a marine insurance advisor\nyou trust to build a personalized policy plan for you",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Boating?",
    "answer": "Boating is such a joy; protect yourself for the unexpected by trusting W3 Insurance with your boat insurance requirements",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why a Resume of Experience Matters for Yacht Insurance\nBass Fishing Boat Insurance 101: What Every Angler Needs to Know\nWhat Is the Jones Act?",
    "answer": "Why a Resume of Experience Matters for Yacht Insurance\nBass Fishing Boat Insurance 101: What Every Angler Needs to Know\nWhat Is the Jones Act",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/yacht-storage-options/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why a Resume of Experience Matters for Yacht Insurance\nDecember 23, 2025\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t    In\nYacht Insurance\nWhen you are looking to insure pleasure use yachts, the process can sometimes feel complicated?",
    "answer": "Why a Resume of Experience Matters for Yacht Insurance\nDecember 23, 2025\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t    In\nYacht Insurance\nWhen you are looking to insure pleasure use yachts, the process can sometimes feel complicated",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, one of the most critical factors insurance companies look at isn\u2019t just the boat itself\u2014it\u2019s you?",
    "answer": "However, one of the most critical factors insurance companies look at isn\u2019t just the boat itself\u2014it\u2019s you",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In the world of yachting, experience?",
    "answer": "In the world of yachting, experience is everything",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For example, if your yacht owner\u2019s history consists of vessels under 60 feet and you are now buying a 75-foot vessel, this \u201cjump in length\u201d?",
    "answer": "For example, if your yacht owner\u2019s history consists of vessels under 60 feet and you are now buying a 75-foot vessel, this \u201cjump in length\u201d is significant",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But why?",
    "answer": "But why is this such a significant factor",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A larger yacht usually requires advanced handling techniques because it?",
    "answer": "Safety and Stability\nA larger yacht usually requires advanced handling techniques because it is less maneuverable than a smaller boat",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, this comes with increased risk?",
    "answer": "However, this comes with increased risk",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is with increased length or multiple engines?",
    "answer": "Operational Complexity\nManaging a yacht\nwith increased length or multiple engines is far more complex than handling a smaller, single-engine yacht",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Insurance Carriers Need a Resume of Experience Upfront\nProviding a boating resume isn\u2019t just paperwork; it\u2019s about securing the right insurance protection for your specific needs?",
    "answer": "Why Insurance Carriers Need a Resume of Experience Upfront\nProviding a boating resume isn\u2019t just paperwork; it\u2019s about securing the right insurance protection for your specific needs",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A resume of experience that demonstrates a history of safe operation helps reassure insurers that the yacht?",
    "answer": "A resume of experience that demonstrates a history of safe operation helps reassure insurers that the yacht is in capable hands",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is regular maintenance of larger yachts?",
    "answer": "Moreover,\nregular maintenance of larger yachts\nis crucial",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Insurance carriers want to know that the yacht owner?",
    "answer": "Insurance carriers want to know that the yacht owner is proactive about maintaining the yacht properly, as this significantly affects the risk of mechanical failure or accidents",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When we look at your experience, we can better structure the policy to address:\nHull Coverage:\nProtection for physical damage to your vessel\nAgreed Value vs?",
    "answer": "When we look at your experience, we can better structure the policy to address:\nHull Coverage:\nProtection for physical damage to your vessel\nAgreed Value vs",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This builds trust with the underwriters and shows that the yacht owner?",
    "answer": "This builds trust with the underwriters and shows that the yacht owner is serious about the application process",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It reassures insurance carriers that the owner?",
    "answer": "It reassures insurance carriers that the owner is committed to safe and knowledgeable yachting practices, which can positively influence the terms and conditions of the insurance policy",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This can further reassure insurance carriers that the owner?",
    "answer": "This can further reassure insurance carriers that the owner is well-prepared to handle the sophisticated systems onboard",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The world of yachting?",
    "answer": "The Importance of Continuous Learning\nThe world of yachting is constantly evolving",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Continuous learning?",
    "answer": "Continuous learning is essential for staying up to date and ensuring safe, responsible yacht operation",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Insurance carriers rely on a detailed resume of experience to assess whether the yacht?",
    "answer": "Insurance carriers rely on a detailed resume of experience to assess whether the yacht is being operated by an insured or by a captain accustomed to navigating similar vessels",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Whether you are purchasing a new yacht with significant differences in size and engine capacity from your prior yachting experience, providing a comprehensive resume of your experience upfront?",
    "answer": "Whether you are purchasing a new yacht with significant differences in size and engine capacity from your prior yachting experience, providing a comprehensive resume of your experience upfront is essential",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The resume of experience?",
    "answer": "The resume of experience is not just a formality but a crucial document that reflects your capability and commitment as a yacht owner",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Normal Deductible?",
    "answer": "What is a Normal Deductible",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A deductible?",
    "answer": "A deductible is the amount you pay out of pocket before insurance covers the rest",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For yachts, this?",
    "answer": "For yachts, this is typically a percentage of the insured value (often 1% to 2%)",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An increased Named Storm Deductible?",
    "answer": "An increased Named Storm Deductible is also applicable to most yacht policies",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Are the Exclusions from Yacht Insurance Policies?",
    "answer": "What Are the Exclusions from Yacht Insurance Policies",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Indemnity?",
    "answer": "Indemnity is generally intended for sudden, accidental losses, not for maintenance issues",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/12/why-a-resume-matters-for-yacht-insurance/#respond",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is Charter Boat Insurance?",
    "answer": "What Is Charter Boat Insurance",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Charter boat insurance?",
    "answer": "Charter boat insurance\nis a specialized type of marine insurance designed to protect charter boat owners and operators from risks specific to their operations",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Whether you\u2019re running fishing charters, harbor sightseeing tours, or private parties on the water, having the right insurance?",
    "answer": "Whether you\u2019re running fishing charters, harbor sightseeing tours, or private parties on the water, having the right insurance is not just recommended but vital for compliance and peace of mind",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A valid COI issued by the USCG?",
    "answer": "Vessels Carrying 12 or More Passengers\nThese vessels are classified as Small Passenger Vessels and must adhere to stricter regulations:\nCertificate of Inspection (COI):\nA valid COI issued by the USCG is required",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Understanding the distinctions between charter insurance and pleasure-use boat insurance?",
    "answer": "Pleasure-Use Boat Insurance\nUnderstanding the distinctions between charter insurance and pleasure-use boat insurance is crucial for ensuring proper coverage tailored to your vessel\u2019s intended purpose",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is a Bareboat Charter?",
    "answer": "What Is a Bareboat Charter",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A bareboat charter?",
    "answer": "A bareboat charter is when you lease the vessel without crew, fuel, or provisions, and the charterer takes full responsibility for its operation",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The charterer?",
    "answer": "Bareboat Charter:\nThe charterer is responsible for hiring their own captain and crew, assuming legal and operational control",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This needs to cover hull, liability, and passenger injury; stricter underwriting?",
    "answer": "Insurance Differences\nBareboat Charter Insurance:\nThis needs to cover hull, liability, and passenger injury; stricter underwriting is required due to the liability shift",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Affects the Cost of Charter Boat Insurance?",
    "answer": "What Affects the Cost of Charter Boat Insurance",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Choose the Right Policy for Your Charter Business\nWith countless insurance companies and marine underwriters offering specialized packages, finding the right coverage involves a step-by-step process?",
    "answer": "How to Choose the Right Policy for Your Charter Business\nWith countless insurance companies and marine underwriters offering specialized packages, finding the right coverage involves a step-by-step process",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Why Charter Boat Insurance?",
    "answer": "Request a Quote\nWhy Charter Boat Insurance is Essential\nRunning a charter\nboat business\ncomes with both rewards and risks",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I report a claim on my boat insurance policy?",
    "answer": "How do I report a claim on my boat insurance policy",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How much does insurance cost for a charter fishing boat?",
    "answer": "How much does insurance cost for a charter fishing boat",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/07/charter-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If you\u2019re in the market to buy a boat, marine insurance?",
    "answer": "If you\u2019re in the market to buy a boat, marine insurance is\none of the most important things to consider\nduring that process",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What\u2019s more, the coverage offers peace of mind?",
    "answer": "What\u2019s more, the coverage offers peace of mind",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why do I need boat insurance?",
    "answer": "Why do I need boat insurance",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The list?",
    "answer": "The list is long, and a Florida marine insurance advisor will have plenty of stories to share that prove coverage is truly imperative",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Boat collision insurance?",
    "answer": "Boat collision insurance is a popular coverage option, because the reality of a craft crashing into yours (or the other way around) is a possible one",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you\u2019re out on the water, you\u2019re going to need the\nspecialized coverage\nthat only a solid marine insurance policy provides?",
    "answer": "When you\u2019re out on the water, you\u2019re going to need the\nspecialized coverage\nthat only a solid marine insurance policy provides",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does boat insurance cover?",
    "answer": "What does boat insurance cover",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is combo of what?",
    "answer": "As with most insurance coverage options, you can make your boat policy an\na la carte\ncombo of what is important to you as a boat owner",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you leave that expensive navigation equipment or personal items on board you\u2019re leaving yourself open to possible theft?",
    "answer": "When you leave that expensive navigation equipment or personal items on board you\u2019re leaving yourself open to possible theft",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What\u2019s more, that underwater object can result in the sinking of your boat?",
    "answer": "What\u2019s more, that underwater object can result in the sinking of your boat",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An accident in which both boat owners carry insurance?",
    "answer": "An accident in which both boat owners carry insurance is going to be much less devastating on the pocketbook than one in which neither (or just one) has it",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Running a boat aground?",
    "answer": "Grounding\nRunning a boat aground is unfortunately common; thanks to the ever-changing levels of tides, it\u2019s easy to misjudge or forget that certain parts of the waterways are not deep enough",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is W3?",
    "answer": "W3 is here to help so that you select the coverage that\u2019s right for you and your boat",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2022/08/10-most-common-boat-insurance-claims/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The sun?",
    "answer": "The sun is just beginning",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/category/boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For Florida boat owners, being out on the water?",
    "answer": "10 Most Common Boat Insurance Claims\nAugust 26, 2022\t\t\t\t\t    \t\t\t\t\t    \tIn\nBoat Insurance\nBoat Ownership\nFlorida Boating\nFor Florida boat owners, being out on the water is one of life\u2019s true pleasures",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/category/boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The state of Florida?",
    "answer": "Everything You Need to Know to Own a Boat in Florida\nAugust 12, 2022\t\t\t\t\t    \t\t\t\t\t    \tIn\nBoat Insurance\nBoat Ownership\nFlorida Boating\nThe state of Florida is made up of close to 19% water",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/category/boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Does Boat Insurance Cover?",
    "answer": "What Does Boat Insurance Cover",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/category/boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What boat safety equipment?",
    "answer": "Boat Safety Equipment in Florida: A Step by Step Guide\nNovember 2, 2020\t\t\t\t\t    \t\t\t\t\t    \tIn\nBoat Insurance\nBoat Ownership\nFlorida Boating\nWhat boat safety equipment is required on a boat in Florida",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/category/boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Asking this question before the vessel?",
    "answer": "Asking this question before the vessel is en route",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/category/boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Owning a bass fishing boat?",
    "answer": "Owning a bass fishing boat is a dream come true for many anglers",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Whether you\u2019re a seasoned tournament competitor, you own a bass fishing charter boat, or you enjoy leisurely fishing trips, protecting your investment?",
    "answer": "Whether you\u2019re a seasoned tournament competitor, you own a bass fishing charter boat, or you enjoy leisurely fishing trips, protecting your investment is crucial",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Why Insurance?",
    "answer": "Request a Quote\nWhy Insurance Is Essential for Bass Fishing Boats\nBass fishing boats face unique risks, making insurance coverage particularly important",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Equipment theft?",
    "answer": "Equipment theft is a common occurrence, particularly when boats are stored at marinas or boat ramps",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Hull insurance?",
    "answer": "Hull Insurance\nHull insurance is the foundation of any boat insurance policy",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Bass fishing often takes place in crowded tournament conditions or in popular fishing areas where boat traffic?",
    "answer": "Liability Insurance\nBass fishing often takes place in crowded tournament conditions or in popular fishing areas where boat traffic is heavy",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This coverage?",
    "answer": "This coverage is critical because boat insurance isn\u2019t required in most states, including Florida",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ensure your coverage?",
    "answer": "Ensure your coverage is sufficient to protect against the potential risks you may face on the water",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When evaluating insurance options, consider your purchase price for your bass boat plus added electronics?",
    "answer": "When evaluating insurance options, consider your purchase price for your bass boat plus added electronics",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Understanding policy limits and exclusions?",
    "answer": "Reviewing Policy Limits and Ensuring Sufficient Coverage\nUnderstanding policy limits and exclusions is crucial for ensuring adequate protection",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How Much?",
    "answer": "Request a Quote\nFAQs\nHow Much Is Insurance for a Fishing Boat",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Do You Estimate Boat Insurance?",
    "answer": "How Do You Estimate Boat Insurance",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Speaking with one of our\u00a0 marine insurance specialists?",
    "answer": "Speaking with one of our\u00a0 marine insurance specialists is a great strategy for obtaining quotes",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Does Boat Insurance Not Cover?",
    "answer": "What Does Boat Insurance Not Cover",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Is Boat Insurance So Hard to Get?",
    "answer": "Why Is Boat Insurance So Hard to Get",
    "source_url": "https://marineins.com/blog/2025/08/bass-fishing-boat-insurance/",
    "domain": "marineins.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marineins"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u2026the breadth and depth of knowledge contained within the Attainable Adventure Cruising site?",
    "answer": "\u201d\n\u2026the breadth and depth of knowledge contained within the Attainable Adventure Cruising site is unmatched by any other resource I know",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Nothing on this website or in direct communications received from us, or in our articles in the media, should be construed to?",
    "answer": "Nothing on this website or in direct communications received from us, or in our articles in the media, should be construed to mean or imply that offshore voyaging is anything other than potentially hazardous",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/cruising-topics/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The information on this web site?",
    "answer": "The information on this web site is based on what has worked for the authors in the past, but that does not mean it will work for you, or that it is the best, or even a good way for you to do things",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/cruising-topics/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Our thinking?",
    "answer": "Read more\n: More Engine Maintenance Tips\nSurvival and Exposure Suits\nJohn Harries\nJanuary 7, 2026\n25 Comments\nReading Time:\n9\nminutes\nMembers\nOur thinking is that survival and exposure suits have very different although overlapping functions, and that both should be carried for cold water offshore sailing and at least one type by most all cruising boats",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Now there?",
    "answer": "Now there is a new product that goes a long way to fix that",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But the sad reality?",
    "answer": "But the sad reality is that a lot of cruisers are really not having as much fun as they could",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The good news?",
    "answer": "The good news is that these tips will help",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Keeping shell and weed off a propeller?",
    "answer": "Read more\n: Five Tips To Get Ready For Happy Cruising\nPropSpeed Antifouling Report\nJohn Harries\nDecember 6, 2025\n13 Comments\nReading Time:\n2\nminutes\nMembers\nKeeping shell and weed off a propeller is vital for efficient motoring and good sailing performance, but far from easy to achieve",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Electric winches are fundamentally dangerous, but there?",
    "answer": "Read more\n: Give an AAC Membership For Christmas\nElectric Winch Fatality\nJohn Harries\nDecember 3, 2025\n23 Comments\nReading Time:\n2\nminutes\nMembers\nElectric winches are fundamentally dangerous, but there is a way to make them less so",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Matt\u2019s C&C 35 could be made ready for offshore sailing, but what will that really cost and?",
    "answer": "Matt Marsh\nNovember 27, 2025\n55 Comments\nReading Time:\n12\nminutes\nMembers\nMatt\u2019s C&C 35 could be made ready for offshore sailing, but what will that really cost and is it a smart project to take on",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Orca Core?",
    "answer": "Orca Core is an installation breath of fresh air",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The AAC comment system?",
    "answer": "Read more\n: Good Podcast On Electronic Navigation\nComment Editing And Image Upload Fixed\nJohn Harries\nNovember 7, 2025\n2 Comments\nReading Time:\n< 1\nminute\nFree\nThe AAC comment system is working properly again",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Every summer several pairs of ospreys nest and rear their young in the trees surrounding our cove, which?",
    "answer": "Every summer several pairs of ospreys nest and rear their young in the trees surrounding our cove, which is wonderful",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In Part 1 we looked at efficiency, but there?",
    "answer": "Paid membership required: Learn About Membership Get to know us for FREE\nRead more\n: Mast & Rigging Storage Hacks\nChoosing The Right Alternator, Part 2\u2014Other Criteria\nJohn Harries\nOctober 8, 2025\n29 Comments\nReading Time:\n7\nminutes\nMembers\nIn Part 1 we looked at efficiency, but there is a lot more to think about before buying a high-output alternator",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/members/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What if, after the first year, I wanted to cancel, but forgot?",
    "answer": "What if, after the first year, I wanted to cancel, but forgot",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/2024-buy-matrix/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What currency do you bill in?",
    "answer": "What currency do you bill in",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/2024-buy-matrix/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But If you know what a toque?",
    "answer": "But If you know what a toque is and who first said \u201celbows up\u201d\u2026and live in Canada\u2026we pay the HST for you, all 14% of it (we are a Nova Scotia company)",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/2024-buy-matrix/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is How safe?",
    "answer": "\u200b\nHow safe is my credit card with you",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/2024-buy-matrix/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Hull Materials, Which?",
    "answer": "Hull Materials, Which Is Best",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/get-to-know-us-for-free/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One of the common debates in any sailor\u2019s bar?",
    "answer": "One of the common debates in any sailor\u2019s bar is which hull material is best",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/get-to-know-us-for-free/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Everyone loves to tout the benefits of their favourite anchor, John included, but this article?",
    "answer": "4 Vital Anchor Selection Criteria and a Review of SPADE\nEveryone loves to tout the benefits of their favourite anchor, John included, but this article is about much more: how to cut through all the claims to the criteria that really matter when selecting an anchor",
    "source_url": "https://www.morganscloud.com/get-to-know-us-for-free/",
    "domain": "morganscloud.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "morganscloud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Choose Marine Bind?",
    "answer": "Why Choose Marine Bind",
    "source_url": "https://marinebind.com/about-us/",
    "domain": "marinebind.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marinebind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Marine Bind?",
    "answer": "Marine Bind is a trading name of Hiller Marine Pty Ltd",
    "source_url": "https://marinebind.com/about-us/",
    "domain": "marinebind.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marinebind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If your quote request?",
    "answer": "\u00d7\nNo survey required conditions\nOnly applies to New Business quotes\nOnly applies to automatic online quotes\nIf your quote request is referred to an underwriter they may or may not ask for a survey report\n\u00d7\nDisclaimer\nThe information on this site is for general information purposes only and does not take into account your particular needs and objectives",
    "source_url": "https://marinebind.com/about-us/",
    "domain": "marinebind.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marinebind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Why Regular Boat Maintenance?",
    "answer": "Read more\nWhy Regular Boat Maintenance is Crucial for Insurance Claims: A Guide for Australian Boat Owners and Brokers\nRegular boat maintenance is crucial for ensuring the safety and longevity of your vessel, as well as protecting your insurance coverage",
    "source_url": "https://marinebind.com/marine-insights/",
    "domain": "marinebind.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "marinebind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is With the exception of mortgage, home equity and other home-lending products or services, partner compensation?",
    "answer": "With the exception of mortgage, home equity and other home-lending products or services, partner compensation is one of several factors that may affect which products we highlight and where they appear on our site",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, these factors\ndo not influence our editors\u2019 opinions or ratings\n, which are based on independent research and analysis?",
    "answer": "However, these factors\ndo not influence our editors\u2019 opinions or ratings\n, which are based on independent research and analysis",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is NerdWallet's content?",
    "answer": "NerdWallet's content is fact-checked for accuracy, timeliness and relevance",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It undergoes a thorough review process involving writers and editors to ensure the information?",
    "answer": "It undergoes a thorough review process involving writers and editors to ensure the information is as clear and complete as possible",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Melissa Lambarena?",
    "answer": "More on our editorial rigor\nWritten by\nMelissa Lambarena\nMelissa Lambarena\nSenior Writer & Content Strategist\n10 years of experience\nExpertise\nCredit cards\ndebt\nMelissa Lambarena is a senior writer on the credit cards team at NerdWallet",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u00bb This article?",
    "answer": "Managing Editor\n+\nmore\n\u00bb This article is out of date\nThe promotion described in this story has expired",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The offer?",
    "answer": "The offer is available only if you submit an application between Dec",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Only one link?",
    "answer": "Only one link is allowed per individual",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Make sure your email address?",
    "answer": "Make sure your email address is up to date because every second counts",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The next phase?",
    "answer": "The next phase is the random selection draw, which required applications for specific matches",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Melissa?",
    "answer": "About the author\nMelissa Lambarena\nMelissa is a credit cards writer at NerdWallet",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When evaluating offers, please review\nthe financial institution's Terms and Conditions?",
    "answer": "When evaluating offers, please review\nthe financial institution's Terms and Conditions",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Neither Atomic Invest nor Atomic Brokerage, nor any of their affiliates?",
    "answer": "Neither Atomic Invest nor Atomic Brokerage, nor any of their affiliates\nis a bank",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/bank-of-america-fifa-world-cup-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If your goal?",
    "answer": "Managing Editor\n+\nmore\nIf your goal is to save some cash \u2014 perhaps by dining in more than you dine out \u2014 in the new year, Discover\u2019s latest 5% cash-back categories can incentivize those financial resolutions",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/discover-5-percent-bonus-categories-q1-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If your Discover card?",
    "answer": "\u00bb MORE:\nSee our best credit cards for groceries\nWholesale clubs\nIf your Discover card is accepted at a wholesale club, you can earn bonus cash back on purchases there",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/discover-5-percent-bonus-categories-q1-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This category?",
    "answer": "\u00bb MORE:\nSee our best credit cards for Costco purchases\nSelect streaming services\nThis category is a repeat from Discover\u2019s first-quarter picks of 2025",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/discover-5-percent-bonus-categories-q1-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Funto Omojola?",
    "answer": "More on our editorial rigor\nWritten by\nFunto Omojola\nFunto Omojola\nLead Writer & Content Strategist\n7 years of experience\nExpertise\nCredit cards\nFunto Omojola is a lead writer and content strategist on the credit cards team",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/chase-freedom-unlimited-hikes-welcome-bonus",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Chase Freedom Unlimited\u00ae?",
    "answer": "Managing Editor\n+\nmore\nRight in time for the festive season,\nChase Freedom Unlimited\u00ae\nis topping off its already lucrative benefits with a higher bonus",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/chase-freedom-unlimited-hikes-welcome-bonus",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Which Chase Freedom credit card?",
    "answer": "\u00bb MORE:\nWhich Chase Freedom credit card is right for you",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/chase-freedom-unlimited-hikes-welcome-bonus",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The new $0-annual-fee SoFi Smart Card earns an uncapped 5% cash back at grocery stores, which?",
    "answer": "The new $0-annual-fee SoFi Smart Card earns an uncapped 5% cash back at grocery stores, which is among the best rates on the market in one of the biggest spending categories for many shoppers",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/sofi-smart-card-5x-at-grocery-stores",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, there are some caveats to be aware of:\nBecause it's a\ncharge card\nand not a credit card, you won\u2019t be able to carry a balance on the SoFi Smart Card and must instead pay it off in full each month?",
    "answer": "However, there are some caveats to be aware of:\nBecause it's a\ncharge card\nand not a credit card, you won\u2019t be able to carry a balance on the SoFi Smart Card and must instead pay it off in full each month",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/sofi-smart-card-5x-at-grocery-stores",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Another unique feature of the SoFi Smart Card?",
    "answer": "Another unique feature of the SoFi Smart Card is how it\u2019s integrated with the cardholder\u2019s checking and savings account to prevent overspending",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/sofi-smart-card-5x-at-grocery-stores",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is When a purchase?",
    "answer": "When a purchase is made with the SoFi Smart Card, the amount of that purchase is \u201creserved,\" meaning those funds are no longer accessible to make other purchases until the card balance is paid",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/sofi-smart-card-5x-at-grocery-stores",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When a purchase is made with the SoFi Smart Card, the amount of that purchase is \u201creserved,\" meaning those funds are no longer accessible to make other purchases until the card balance is paid?",
    "answer": "When a purchase is made with the SoFi Smart Card, the amount of that purchase is \u201creserved,\" meaning those funds are no longer accessible to make other purchases until the card balance is paid",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/sofi-smart-card-5x-at-grocery-stores",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Jae?",
    "answer": "\u00bb NEXT:\nNerdWallet's best credit cards for groceries\nAbout the author\nJae Bratton\nJae is a writer for the credit cards team at NerdWallet",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/sofi-smart-card-5x-at-grocery-stores",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, this does not influence our evaluations?",
    "answer": "However, this does not influence our evaluations",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Amy?",
    "answer": "com\nAmy is a former editor and insurance authority at NerdWallet",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What boat insurance will pay for\nBoat insurance costs and discounts\nWhere to buy boat insurance\nTable of Contents\nDo you need boat insurance?",
    "answer": "What boat insurance will pay for\nBoat insurance costs and discounts\nWhere to buy boat insurance\nTable of Contents\nDo you need boat insurance",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What boat insurance will pay for\nBoat insurance costs and discounts\nWhere to buy boat insurance\nYour prized boat probably didn\u2019t come cheap?",
    "answer": "What boat insurance will pay for\nBoat insurance costs and discounts\nWhere to buy boat insurance\nYour prized boat probably didn\u2019t come cheap",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is So a home insurance policy might help you only if your boat?",
    "answer": "So a home insurance policy might help you only if your boat is small, slow and inexpensive",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What boat insurance will pay for\nYou can typically buy liability insurance \u2014 which pays for damage your boat does to others \u2014 in amounts from $15,000 to $300,000, according to the Insurance Information Institute?",
    "answer": "What boat insurance will pay for\nYou can typically buy liability insurance \u2014 which pays for damage your boat does to others \u2014 in amounts from $15,000 to $300,000, according to the Insurance Information Institute",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Bodily injury liability, which pays expenses when someone?",
    "answer": "Bodily injury liability, which pays expenses when someone is injured on your boat",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If your boat?",
    "answer": "If your boat is destroyed, your insurance company determines its market value",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Taking your boat out of the water?",
    "answer": "Layup periods:\nTaking your boat out of the water is typical during cold weather, and most insurance companies will give you a credit because it\u2019s not being used",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In Texas, children under 13 are barred from driving one unless a licensed operator who's at least 18?",
    "answer": "In Texas, children under 13 are barred from driving one unless a licensed operator who's at least 18 is on board",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is You can choose your deductible, which?",
    "answer": "You can choose your deductible, which is the amount deducted from your insurance check if you make a claim",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Boat insurance?",
    "answer": "Where to buy boat insurance\nBoat insurance is widely available",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where to buy boat insurance\nBoat insurance is widely available?",
    "answer": "Where to buy boat insurance\nBoat insurance is widely available",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Average cost of boat insurance from Allstate?",
    "answer": "Allstate\nAverage cost of boat insurance from Allstate is about $20 a month, according to Allstate",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Optional boat insurance coverage?",
    "answer": "Auto-Owners\nOptional boat insurance coverage is available through homeowners policies",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Additional coverage, which costs extra,?",
    "answer": "The Hartford\nAdditional coverage, which costs extra, is available for your accessories, trailer and boat hull",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Total loss replacement coverage pays for a new boat if your new boat?",
    "answer": "Progressive\nTotal loss replacement coverage pays for a new boat if your new boat is a total loss within five years of adding the coverage",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is USAA members get a 5% discount on boat insurance, but the discount?",
    "answer": "USAA\nUSAA members get a 5% discount on boat insurance, but the discount is not available in all states",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is USAA?",
    "answer": "USAA is open only to active and retired military and their families",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Juan Castillo?",
    "answer": "Juan Castillo is a former staff writer at NerdWallet",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/article/insurance/boat-insurance/#boat-insurance-costs-and-discounts",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Currently, the card?",
    "answer": "Currently, the card is issued and serviced by Goldman Sachs",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/apple-card-chase-new-issuer",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The transition?",
    "answer": "The transition is still subject to closing conditions and regulatory approvals",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/apple-card-chase-new-issuer",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does that entail?",
    "answer": "What does that entail",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/apple-card-chase-new-issuer",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Once the transition?",
    "answer": "Stay tuned\nOnce the transition is complete, your balance will be with Chase",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/apple-card-chase-new-issuer",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Marriott Bonvoy Boundless\u00ae Credit Card?",
    "answer": "\u00bb MORE:\nNerdWallet's Marriott Bonvoy guide\nIn addition to its updated welcome offer, the\nMarriott Bonvoy Boundless\u00ae Credit Card\nis also offering both new and existing cardholders up to $100 in statement credits after they spend $500 on eligible airline purchases with their card in 2026",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/marriott-bonvoy-bold-boundless-unveil-new-bonus-offers",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How the cards compare\nMarriott Bonvoy Boundless\u00ae Credit Card\nApply now\non Chase's website\nRates & Fees\nMarriott Bonvoy Bold\u00ae Credit Card\nApply now\non Chase's website\nRates & Fees\nAnnual fee\n$95?",
    "answer": "How the cards compare\nMarriott Bonvoy Boundless\u00ae Credit Card\nApply now\non Chase's website\nRates & Fees\nMarriott Bonvoy Bold\u00ae Credit Card\nApply now\non Chase's website\nRates & Fees\nAnnual fee\n$95",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/marriott-bonvoy-bold-boundless-unveil-new-bonus-offers",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Chase?",
    "answer": "\u00bb MORE:\nNerdWallet's best credit cards for cruises\nAmerican Heart Association\nChase is extending the season of giving into the new year with a never-before-offered bonus category",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/chase-5-percent-bonus-categories-q1-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is However, this?",
    "answer": "However, this is the first time this specific charity has appeared on the bonus calendar",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/chase-5-percent-bonus-categories-q1-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, this is the first time this specific charity has appeared on the bonus calendar?",
    "answer": "However, this is the first time this specific charity has appeared on the bonus calendar",
    "source_url": "https://www.nerdwallet.com/credit-cards/news/chase-5-percent-bonus-categories-q1-2026",
    "domain": "nerdwallet.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "nerdwallet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This new Flite RACE?",
    "answer": "Courtesy Fliteboard\nThis new Flite RACE is being billed as \u201cthe world\u2019s fastest Fliteboard",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201d\u00a0Designed and built in partnership with Mercury Racing, it?",
    "answer": "\u201d\u00a0Designed and built in partnership with Mercury Racing, it is said to be capable of\u00a0hitting\u00a034 mph",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For now, check out the press release, which?",
    "answer": "For now, check out the press release, which is published below",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Fliteboard RACE?",
    "answer": "The Fliteboard RACE is a competition e-foil",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Showcased on the opening day of the 2026 Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in Las Vegas on Tuesday, this new eFoil?",
    "answer": "Showcased on the opening day of the 2026 Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in Las Vegas on Tuesday, this new eFoil is engineered for elite riders seeking ultimate speed, precision, and flawless control",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is To support speed on demand, RACE?",
    "answer": "To support speed on demand, RACE is the first Fliteboard to use FLITELab* surf foiling wings in the setup",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What began as a small passion project has grown into a multimillion-dollar eFoil industry with Fliteboard at the helm?",
    "answer": "What began as a small passion project has grown into a multimillion-dollar eFoil industry with Fliteboard at the helm",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is , Mercury Racing, a division of Mercury Marine,?",
    "answer": ", Mercury Racing, a division of Mercury Marine, is a leading provider of high-performance marine propulsion systems for discriminating boaters worldwide, offering an exciting and fulfilling power boating experience on the water",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Mercury Marine?",
    "answer": "Mercury Marine is a division of Brunswick Corp",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Reproduction in whole or in part without permission?",
    "answer": "Reproduction in whole or in part without permission is prohibited",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/water-sports/fliteboard-race-brings-high-performance-to-foiling/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Consumer Electronics Show?",
    "answer": "Brunswick Corporation Unveils Its Largest-Ever Showcase of Marine Technology and AI-Driven Boating Experiences at CES 2026\nConsumer Electronics Show is the venue to debut new Sea Ray, Navan, Lund, Flite and more, all part of Brunswick\u2019s ACES strategy",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Boats afford us the?",
    "answer": "Boats afford us the means to create happy occasions with friends and family on the water",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But what type of boat?",
    "answer": "But what type of boat is right for you",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The 288 LXF?",
    "answer": "2026 Scout 288 LXF\nThe 288 LXF is a dual threat, ready to go toe to toe with fish or tux to tux in the party crowd",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The 281 Coastal Explorer?",
    "answer": "2026 Grady-White 281 Coastal Explorer\nThe 281 Coastal Explorer is a well-equipped fishing platform that offers a smooth, comfortable ride",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The R277 Dual Console?",
    "answer": "2026 Robalo R277 Dual Console\nThe R277 Dual Console is a versatile craft sure to meet the needs of anglers and boating families",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For every type of boater, there?",
    "answer": "Read More\n\u00bb\nAdvertisement\nTypes of Boats\nFor every type of boater, there is a type of boat",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Properly Flush Your Boat\u2019s Motor\nHow to run inboard, outboard and sterndrive engines on land?",
    "answer": "How to Properly Flush Your Boat\u2019s Motor\nHow to run inboard, outboard and sterndrive engines on land",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Comparing the electronics available today to those from a decade ago?",
    "answer": "Advertisement\nMarine Electronics\nComparing the electronics available today to those from a decade ago is pretty eye opening",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The technological changes in just 10 years?",
    "answer": "The technological changes in just 10 years means today we have better sonar, multi-function display units, night vision technology, and boat camera security systems than ever before",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is FLIR\u2019s Ocean Scout Pro?",
    "answer": "FLIR Ocean Scout Pro\nFLIR\u2019s Ocean Scout Pro is a next-gen handheld thermal camera for boaters from a company known for their marine devices",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is No longer?",
    "answer": "No longer is the 250-horsepower engine the pride of the offshore center console fleet",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is McLaren\u2019s M300, based on Honda\u2019s BF250,?",
    "answer": "McLaren M300 Outboard\nMcLaren\u2019s M300, based on Honda\u2019s BF250, is a performance-inspired outboard engine that serves up top-end power",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Whether buying a boat or taking stock of your current boat, an engine-room inspection?",
    "answer": "By\nKevin Falvey\nJanuary 5, 2026\nWhether buying a boat or taking stock of your current boat, an engine-room inspection is required",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, I was prompted to write this Quick Study after attending Steve D\u2019Antonio\u2019s seminar (\nstevedmarineconsulting?",
    "answer": "However, I was prompted to write this Quick Study after attending Steve D\u2019Antonio\u2019s seminar (\nstevedmarineconsulting",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Among many titles, D\u2019Antonio?",
    "answer": "Among many titles, D\u2019Antonio is an American Boat & Yacht Council (ABYC) Master Technician, holding certifications in corrosion, diesel, electrical and systems",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Checking for chafe-protection?",
    "answer": "Checking for chafe-protection is important",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cWire loom buys some time but it?",
    "answer": "\u201cWire loom buys some time but it is not a permanent solution,\u201d D\u2019Antonio says",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is ) Make sure the handle?",
    "answer": ") Make sure the handle is not obstructed by a hose, other equipment or a stringer\u2014we see this on occasion\u2014so that the valve can be closed",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Non-conductive, these will also \u201cbreak away\u201d unlike metal rings, which can deglove a finger if caught in machinery, during a fall, or if a heavy object?",
    "answer": "Non-conductive, these will also \u201cbreak away\u201d unlike metal rings, which can deglove a finger if caught in machinery, during a fall, or if a heavy object is dropped",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Make sure the engine?",
    "answer": "Make sure the engine is cool and the battery is off or disconnected before inspecting belts",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Pros often perform a backdown test, in which the mounts are observed while the engine?",
    "answer": "Pros often perform a backdown test, in which the mounts are observed while the engine is placed in reverse and accelerated",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Make sure the fire-suppression system?",
    "answer": "Fire Suppression\nMake sure the fire-suppression system is active",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is D\u2019Antonio says he encounters many in which the system?",
    "answer": "D\u2019Antonio says he encounters many in which the system is disabled because the \u201cshipping pin\u201d has not been removed from the manual cable",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/importance-of-engine-room-inspections/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is So, the Boat of the Year?",
    "answer": "So, the Boat of the Year is the boat that stands out in its category more than any other boat we tested stands out in any other category",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boat-of-the-year/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Coupled with our editors nearly 200 years of combined experience testing boats, this provides the Boating Tech Team with a river of experience that?",
    "answer": "Coupled with our editors nearly 200 years of combined experience testing boats, this provides the Boating Tech Team with a river of experience that is broad and deep",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boat-of-the-year/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Pete McDonald?",
    "answer": "Pete McDonald\nExecutive Editor\nPete McDonald is the executive editor of Boating Magazine",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boat-of-the-year/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In addition, he?",
    "answer": "In addition, he is the author of the book \u201cThe Blitz: Fly Fishing the Atlantic Migration",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boat-of-the-year/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Author of \u201cPower Boating for Dummies,\u201d Vance?",
    "answer": "Author of \u201cPower Boating for Dummies,\u201d Vance is a popular video boat-review host with millions of combined views, and is a 45-year veteran of outdoor and boating journalism",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/boat-of-the-year/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The CrossWave?",
    "answer": "2026 Yamaha CrossWave\nThe CrossWave is a stable fishing platform that provides a fun ride for up to four people",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/personal-watercraft/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Sea-Doo Spark Trixx?",
    "answer": "2026 Sea-Doo Spark Trixx\nThe Sea-Doo Spark Trixx is for those seeking to have a blast on the water",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/personal-watercraft/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Yamaha CrossWave?",
    "answer": "Boat Test: 2026 Yamaha CrossWave\nThe Yamaha CrossWave is a fishing dream machine that\u2019s exciting, maneuverable and easy to launch, tow and stow",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/personal-watercraft/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Whether it\u2019s a review of one of the hottest new models, an update on the PWC racing scene, or a story about personal watercraft being used in a unique or interesting manner or setting, here?",
    "answer": "Whether it\u2019s a review of one of the hottest new models, an update on the PWC racing scene, or a story about personal watercraft being used in a unique or interesting manner or setting, here is the place you will find the PWC content that inspires and informs",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/personal-watercraft/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Catching a Swordfish on a PWC?",
    "answer": "Catching a Swordfish on a PWC\nIs a personal watercraft capable enough to be used for landing a swordfish",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/personal-watercraft/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Spark Trixx?",
    "answer": "2024 Sea-Doo Spark Trixx\nThe Spark Trixx is packed full of playful personality",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/personal-watercraft/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Pursuit S 388 Sport?",
    "answer": "By\nBoating Tech Team\nDecember 30, 2025\nVisit Pursuit\nBuild Your Pursuit\nFind a Pursuit Dealer\nThe Pursuit S 388 Sport is\u00a0 an evolved center-console, focusing on both functionality and comfort",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-pursuit-s388-sport-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The S 388 Sport?",
    "answer": "The S 388 Sport is packed with the latest tech",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-pursuit-s388-sport-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Pursuit\u2019s meticulous attention to detail?",
    "answer": "The Pursuit\u2019s meticulous attention to detail is apparent in the orderly rigging and smart placement of service access under the cockpit sole, such as the slide-out shelf for the batteries",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-pursuit-s388-sport-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Plush seating?",
    "answer": "Plush seating is found fore and aft",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-pursuit-s388-sport-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The center-console cabin?",
    "answer": "The center-console cabin is nicely appointed",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-pursuit-s388-sport-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What\u2019s the best pontoon boat for you?",
    "answer": "What\u2019s the best pontoon boat for you",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/#trigger-cky-consent",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Typically a runabout?",
    "answer": "Runabout Boats\nTypically a runabout is an open boat, but it may have a flush-deck cuddy cabin--and is sometimes known as a sport boat in that configuration",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/#trigger-cky-consent",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Replace an Outboard Water Pump\nReplacing your outboard\u2019s water pump will keep it in prime running condition?",
    "answer": "How to Replace an Outboard Water Pump\nReplacing your outboard\u2019s water pump will keep it in prime running condition",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/#trigger-cky-consent",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Vanemar\u2019s New Security System?",
    "answer": "Vanemar\u2019s New Security System is a Snap to Install\nDownload the app, sign up, turn on the devices and they can be easily added to the system",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/#trigger-cky-consent",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Gill OS2?",
    "answer": "Gill OS2 Offshore Jacket and Bibs for Women\nThe Gill OS2 is for anglers who don\u2019t back down to foul weather",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/#trigger-cky-consent",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But then I did my research, and in the Roman religion, Neptune?",
    "answer": "But then I did my research, and in the Roman religion, Neptune is the god of the sea and of fresh water",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/the-perils-of-an-unnamed-boat/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cI know the lake?",
    "answer": "\u201cI know the lake is frozen but you\u2019ve got to come up with a name for the Dunphy before next season,\u201d Chuck said, \u201cespecially if you\u2019re taking these beautiful little children out on the water",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/the-perils-of-an-unnamed-boat/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How could you ever forgive yourself if Neptune decides to cast calamity down from the heavens?",
    "answer": "How could you ever forgive yourself if Neptune decides to cast calamity down from the heavens",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/the-perils-of-an-unnamed-boat/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The second?",
    "answer": "The second is\nAnalog\n, because there is nothing digital about this boat",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/the-perils-of-an-unnamed-boat/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is who can view a given boat through three lenses: what it?",
    "answer": "Second, you get\ninsightful commentary that can only come from professionals\nwho can view a given boat through three lenses: what it is in itself, how it compares to other similar boats, and where it fits in the universe of all boats",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/pontoon-boat-buyers-guide/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is gives you a?",
    "answer": "Third, with the compilation of this annual Pontoon Boat Buyers Guide, our team of staffers and contributors\ngives you a means to compare a number of boats of the same type",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/pontoon-boat-buyers-guide/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What to look for in a boat\nBoating\nhas several guides geared towards helping you know what to look for when shopping for a boat?",
    "answer": "What to look for in a boat\nBoating\nhas several guides geared towards helping you know what to look for when shopping for a boat",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/pontoon-boat-buyers-guide/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The seller?",
    "answer": "What to Do if Your Boat\u2019s Engine Dies\nPreparing for Weather When Boating\nWhat to Include in a Float Plan\nSafety gear and requirements\nThe seller is not required to supply safety gear",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/pontoon-boat-buyers-guide/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What to Do if Your Boat\u2019s Engine Dies\nPreparing for Weather When Boating\nWhat to Include in a Float Plan\nSafety gear and requirements\nThe seller is not required to supply safety gear?",
    "answer": "What to Do if Your Boat\u2019s Engine Dies\nPreparing for Weather When Boating\nWhat to Include in a Float Plan\nSafety gear and requirements\nThe seller is not required to supply safety gear",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/pontoon-boat-buyers-guide/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Brunswick display at CES?",
    "answer": "By\nKevin Falvey\nJanuary 5, 2026\nThe Brunswick display at CES is itself a technological showcase, providing for immersive experience for a variety of recreational marine products",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/brunswick-technology-ces-2026/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2026 CES showcase features the groundbreaking Simrad\u00a0AutoCaptain autonomous boating system on two boats including the global debut of a brand-new Sea Ray SLX and a NAVAN C30, which?",
    "answer": "This year\u2019s\nBrunswick\n2026 CES showcase features the groundbreaking Simrad\u00a0AutoCaptain autonomous boating system on two boats including the global debut of a brand-new Sea Ray SLX and a NAVAN C30, which is making its first appearance at CES",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/brunswick-technology-ces-2026/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The exhibit?",
    "answer": "The exhibit is further elevated by an exclusive, high-horsepower outboard concept from Mercury Marine, exemplifying the innovative future of marine propulsion",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/brunswick-technology-ces-2026/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cCES stands as the global epicenter for unveiling transformative innovation, and Brunswick?",
    "answer": "\u201cCES stands as the global epicenter for unveiling transformative innovation, and Brunswick is poised to exemplify the revolutionary impact of artificial intelligence and next-generation marine technologies,\u201d said Dave Foulkes, Brunswick Corporation CEO",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/brunswick-technology-ces-2026/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is At the center?",
    "answer": "At the center is Sea Ray\u2019s automotive-inspired helm featuring steering wheel-integrated controls, dual\nSimrad\nNSX ULTRAWIDE displays, and deep connectivity with Mercury Marine propulsion",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/brunswick-technology-ces-2026/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In addition, Brunswick Corporation will also participate in CES Foundry, hosting a panel discussion on how AI?",
    "answer": "In addition, Brunswick Corporation will also participate in CES Foundry, hosting a panel discussion on how AI is elevating the boating experience",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/brunswick-technology-ces-2026/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Visit Brunswick at the Last Vegas Convention Center West Hall, exhibit #5041, and experience how the Company?",
    "answer": "Find Brunswick at CES 2026\nVisit Brunswick at the Last Vegas Convention Center West Hall, exhibit #5041, and experience how the Company is making boating more intuitive, connected and consumer-ready than ever before",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/brunswick-technology-ces-2026/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A spacious optional head?",
    "answer": "Courtesy Regulator Marine\nA spacious optional head is inside the console and easily accessed",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-regulator-28-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In summary, the Regulator 28 should top the list for boat buyers seeking to combine serious fishing capability with luxury and comfort and the kind of confidence at sea only found when quality?",
    "answer": "In summary, the Regulator 28 should top the list for boat buyers seeking to combine serious fishing capability with luxury and comfort and the kind of confidence at sea only found when quality is underfoot",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-regulator-28-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The ABYC Foundation?",
    "answer": "The ABYC Foundation is encouraging the marine industry to help spread the word about this event to local schools",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/abyc-foundation-educator-forum-encourage-people-seek-marine-service/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cThe Educator Forum?",
    "answer": "Read Next:\nABYC Color Codes for Boat Wiring\n\u201cThe Educator Forum is about building connections that strengthen marine education programs and, ultimately, our industry\u2019s workforce,\u201d said Sarah Devlin, ABYC Foundation Accreditation Director",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/abyc-foundation-educator-forum-encourage-people-seek-marine-service/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cWhether a school already offers a marine service program or?",
    "answer": "\u201cWhether a school already offers a marine service program or is just getting started, this event offers practical insights and tools to help them succeed",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/abyc-foundation-educator-forum-encourage-people-seek-marine-service/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What\u2019s New in ABYC Education: Tim Murphy and Mike Bonicker share updates on ABYC\u2019s growing curriculum, including\nAdvanced Marine Systems Technology\nand\nIntroduction to Boatyard Basics?",
    "answer": "What\u2019s New in ABYC Education: Tim Murphy and Mike Bonicker share updates on ABYC\u2019s growing curriculum, including\nAdvanced Marine Systems Technology\nand\nIntroduction to Boatyard Basics",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/how-to/abyc-foundation-educator-forum-encourage-people-seek-marine-service/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An inflatable water mat?",
    "answer": "Inflatable Water Mats for Boaters\nAn inflatable water mat is a great way to expand entertaining capabilities while at the sandbar or on the lake",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/tag/boating-lab/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How in the world are these going to be comfortable, or even functional?",
    "answer": "How in the world are these going to be comfortable, or even functional",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/gear/ombraz-sunglasses-tested/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The custom-woven nylon material?",
    "answer": "The custom-woven nylon material is abrasion resistant, soft, and 100-percent recycled",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/gear/ombraz-sunglasses-tested/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When I received a pair of Ombraz several months ago to test, I was convinced they would feel wobbly or too different to be usable?",
    "answer": "When I received a pair of Ombraz several months ago to test, I was convinced they would feel wobbly or too different to be usable",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/gear/ombraz-sunglasses-tested/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Another advantage to the cord-for-arms system?",
    "answer": "Another advantage to the cord-for-arms system is loss prevention",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/gear/ombraz-sunglasses-tested/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The cord?",
    "answer": "The cord is a built-in keeper, so you can easily pull the Ombraz off your face and let them hang from your neck",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/gear/ombraz-sunglasses-tested/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While you might have your doubts looking at them, all I can say?",
    "answer": "While you might have your doubts looking at them, all I can say is you\u2019ve got to try them",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/gear/ombraz-sunglasses-tested/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For folks with plus-sized heads like myself, this?",
    "answer": "For folks with plus-sized heads like myself, this is a wonderful option",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/gear/ombraz-sunglasses-tested/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to clean mildew seats?",
    "answer": "How to clean mildew seats",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/how-to/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to repair your gel coat?",
    "answer": "How to repair your gel coat",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/how-to/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to troubleshoot your engine when it\u2019s not starting?",
    "answer": "How to troubleshoot your engine when it\u2019s not starting",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/how-to/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is seamanship?",
    "answer": "For most,\nseamanship\nis learned via experience on the water",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/how-to/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This new Parker?",
    "answer": "This new Parker is powered by twin Yamaha engines with a maximum horsepower of 700",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-parker-294-fathom-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It offers a self-bailing cockpit, which?",
    "answer": "It offers a self-bailing cockpit, which is a must for any boat on big water in our opinion",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-parker-294-fathom-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Comfortable seating?",
    "answer": "Comfortable seating is found throughout the 294",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-parker-294-fathom-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A fiberglass T-top with powder-coated framework?",
    "answer": "A fiberglass T-top with powder-coated framework is outfitted with a plethora of accessories",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-parker-294-fathom-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is T-Top?",
    "answer": "Courtesy Parker Boats\nHigh Points\nT-Top is as fully featured and as well-engineered as you are likely to find aboard a boat of any price",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-parker-294-fathom-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The bow seating?",
    "answer": "The bow seating is comprised of lounges with backrests that make sandbar days oh-so comfortable",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-parker-294-fathom-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Full, bolt-on transom bracket?",
    "answer": "Full, bolt-on transom bracket means you get all the boat length you pay for",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-parker-294-fathom-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Shearwater 270 SS Open Carolina, built by American Marine Sports,?",
    "answer": "Courtesy American Marine Sports\nVisit American Marine Sports\nFind an American Marine Sports Dealer\nThe Shearwater 270 SS Open Carolina, built by American Marine Sports, is positioned as a premium crossover bay boat designed for both dedicated anglers and family cruising",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-shearwater-270-ss-open-carolina-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Construction?",
    "answer": "Construction is a key highlight, featuring a vacuum-infused composite hull with Kevlar reinforcement for lightweight strength",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-shearwater-270-ss-open-carolina-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The builder utilizes a High-Pressure Injection closed-cell foam core, which?",
    "answer": "The builder utilizes a High-Pressure Injection closed-cell foam core, which is injected while the hull and liner are still in the molds",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-shearwater-270-ss-open-carolina-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Closed-cell foam flotation ensures the boat?",
    "answer": "High Points\nClosed-cell foam flotation ensures the boat is unsinkable, doesn\u2019t shutter or rattle, and always floats upright",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-shearwater-270-ss-open-carolina-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Integrated hardtop?",
    "answer": "Integrated hardtop is mounted internally in the center console to free up pass-through space between the cockpit and bow area",
    "source_url": "https://boatingmag.com/boats/2026-shearwater-270-ss-open-carolina-bbg/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The 22 HFC?",
    "answer": "2026 Sea Chaser 22 HFC\nThe 22 HFC is a fantastic sport-utility boat that\u2019s at home in salt water or fresh",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/fishing-boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Bass Cat Lynx STS?",
    "answer": "2026 Bass Cat Lynx STS\nThe Bass Cat Lynx STS is a high-performance fishing machine",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/fishing-boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Sportsman 1910 SE?",
    "answer": "2026 G3 Sportsman 1910 SE\nThe Sportsman 1910 SE is packed with fishing features and offers cat-quick acceleration",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingmag.com/fishing-boats/",
    "domain": "boatingmag.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingmag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why won\u2019t my holding tank pump out?",
    "answer": "Why won\u2019t my holding tank pump out",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Which way?",
    "answer": "Which way is better: Erie Canal or  the St",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I prepare for a new boat delivery?",
    "answer": "How do I prepare for a new boat delivery",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I keep my A-sail under control?",
    "answer": "How do I keep my A-sail under control",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The marine diesel engine?",
    "answer": "I've used a Martec folding prop on my boat sin\nTechnique\n2025 July 1 - 12:00 am\nDiesel engine care\nDiesels are tough  machines that can provide power for the life of a boat if treated properly\nBy\nBob Pingel\nThe marine diesel engine is an amazing piece of machinery",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is From adaptors to avoiding stray voltage, managing onboard power?",
    "answer": "Each panel has two black plugs on it and my charg\nTechnique\n2025 February 1 - 12:00 am\nOptimizing shore power\nFrom adaptors to avoiding stray voltage, managing onboard power is key for safety and efficiency\nBy\nBob Pingel\nBattery-sourced direct current power is the lifeblood of our boats, running lights, electronics, pumps and even starting our engines",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The capacity and efficiency of charging?",
    "answer": "The capacity and efficiency of charging is really compelling, but I don\u2019t want to have to r\nBoat Doctor\n2024 October 1 - 12:00 am\nWhy won\u2019t my holding tank pump out",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the pros and cons?",
    "answer": "What are the pros and cons",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When it still leaked I replaced the\nBoat Test\n2024 April 1 - 12:00 am\nBeneteau First 36\nBeneteau\u2019s latest midsize racer-cruiser gets the mix right\nBy\nBob Pingel\nThe Beneteau First series has a long history and proud pedigree?",
    "answer": "When it still leaked I replaced the\nBoat Test\n2024 April 1 - 12:00 am\nBeneteau First 36\nBeneteau\u2019s latest midsize racer-cruiser gets the mix right\nBy\nBob Pingel\nThe Beneteau First series has a long history and proud pedigree",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dyneema?",
    "answer": "The boat tur\nTechnique\n2023 December 1 - 12:00 am\nSplicing Dyneema\nEmbrace the splice because knots aren\u2019t best on the extremely strong fiber Dyneema\nBy\nBob Pingel\nDyneema is seriously strong, but a very slippery fiber",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The slipperiness?",
    "answer": "The slipperiness means that you can\u2019t efficiently use knots to terminate it",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-991-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Some stories begin with a dream, which?",
    "answer": "Building a dream\nBuilding a dream\n2025 July 1\nBy\nDavid Liscio\nThe quest for a perfect daysailer led Chris Hood to create a 32-footer that has won the hearts of sailors around the world\nSome stories begin with a dream, which is exactly how Chris Hood ended up designing and building the C",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Designing a boat?",
    "answer": "Designing a boat is one challenge, building it another, but as often happens, marketing and sales proved the most difficult hurdle",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When I decided to try this, Morris and Tartan were already building daysailers, and Hinckley had made one as well,\u201d Hood said?",
    "answer": "When I decided to try this, Morris and Tartan were already building daysailers, and Hinckley had made one as well,\u201d Hood said",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It\u2019s on a hoist so I can sail whenever I like,\u201d said Jobson, whose home port?",
    "answer": "It\u2019s on a hoist so I can sail whenever I like,\u201d said Jobson, whose home port is Annapolis, Maryland",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Buyers were given the option of an electric outboard motor called the Torqueedo, which?",
    "answer": "Buyers were given the option of an electric outboard motor called the Torqueedo, which is clamped to the hull, or the Mastervolt PODMaster sail-drive propulsion system that took up space inside the boat",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Everything about them?",
    "answer": "Everything about them is quality",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cChris?",
    "answer": "\u201cChris is a pleasure to work with,\u201d said Pfeifer, who sails his Hood 32\nYoung America\nout of Sister Bay, Wisconsin",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cThis?",
    "answer": "\u201cThis is only our second sailboat as we have mostly owned powerboats",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When we bought\u00a0Switchback, we owned a 50-foot Grand Banks Eastbay that we used for cruising, so we wanted a daysailer that we could sail from our club with ease?",
    "answer": "When we bought\u00a0Switchback, we owned a 50-foot Grand Banks Eastbay that we used for cruising, so we wanted a daysailer that we could sail from our club with ease",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While the boat can be singlehanded the cockpit?",
    "answer": "\u201d\nWhile the boat can be singlehanded the cockpit is just as comfortable with six, he said",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Although the boat?",
    "answer": "Although the boat is built without a head, causing some consternation among those who might be out on the water for longer than the prescribed four-hour sail, owners have tested some options",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cI remember saying to myself, when this?",
    "answer": "\u201cI remember saying to myself, when this is done we won\u2019t have anything to do",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cIf a boat?",
    "answer": "\u201cIf a boat is beautiful, you won\u2019t forget it,\u201d Hood said",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2640-building-a-dream.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This recreational coastal cruiser?",
    "answer": "Boat shopping often starts with a dream boat t\nUsed Boat Notebook\n2024 July 1 - 12:00 am\nHunter Vision 32\nThis recreational coastal cruiser is designed for effortless sailing\nBy\nDavid Liscio\nThe Hunter Vision 32 has been described as a lazy sailor\u2019s boat because it\u2019s so effortless to sail",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-987-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is These days, Salzmann?",
    "answer": "These days, Salzmann is owner and captain of When and If, a\nFeatures\n2023 October 1 - 12:00 am\nThe wide, wide world of multihulls\nWhat to know before you take the plunge and purchase a boat with more than one hull\nBy\nDavid Liscio\nOne of our earliest family sailing charters was along the Florida Panhandle 20 years ago aboard a 34-foot Tony Smith-designed Gemini 105M catamaran",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-987-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Robustly built, this traditional cruiser?",
    "answer": "It was a disappointing result for the once dominant team, which was\nUsed Boat Notebook\n2021 March 1 - 12:00 am\nGozzard 44\nRobustly built, this traditional cruiser is made for bluewater sailing\nBy\nDavid Liscio\nIf Gozzard Yachts had a mantra, it might be comfort and safety",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-987-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is When \u2018Fast?",
    "answer": "The late Canadian boat designer and builder Hedley \u201cTed\u201d Gozzard harbored strong opinions on how a sailboat should be laid out\nUsed Boat Notebook\n2020 October 1 - 12:00 am\nSanta Cruz 52\nWhen \u2018Fast is Fun\u2019 is designed to cruise, you get a swift passagemaker\nBy\nDavid Liscio\nThere\u2019s really no way to talk about the Santa Cruz 52 without stating the obvious: It\u2019s fun to go fast",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-987-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Catch wet, delaminated core early and the fix?",
    "answer": "And because they require little in the way of everyday maintena\nTechnique\n2024 January 1 - 12:00 am\nRepairing delaminated core\nCatch wet, delaminated core early and the fix is not difficult\nBy\nRichard Reichelsdorfer\nIt\u2019s not unusual for boats, particularly those of a certain age, to have some areas of wet core and delamination",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-1034-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Wet core?",
    "answer": "Sailboats\nTechnique\n2020 May 1 - 12:00 am\nDelamination repair\nWet core is a recipe for problems, but repairing the problem is often not as hard as you may think\nBy\nRichard Reichelsdorfer\nWet core is one of the most common problems you\u2019ll find in boats constructed with a cored-laminate hull or deck, particularly those of a certain age",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-1034-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Upgrading your boat\u2019s  power grid?",
    "answer": "Although tackling such damage can be a messy job\nTechnique\n2018 January 1 - 12:00 am\nInstalling a new battery system\nUpgrading your boat\u2019s  power grid is a good investment in time, money\nBy\nRichard Reichelsdorfer\nSome upgrades and repairs on a sailboat are no-brainers",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-1034-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But figuring out if a battery upgrade?",
    "answer": "But figuring out if a battery upgrade is necessary and how to do it is at times less obvious",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-1034-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is With sleek, modern looks this cruiser?",
    "answer": "Boat Test\n2017 January 1 - 12:00 am\nPowerful passagemaker\nWith sleek, modern looks this cruiser is kitted out for long voyages at a quick pace\nBy\nRichard Reichelsdorfer\nAt first glance, the 54 is an impressive boat",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-1034-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Its contemporary look?",
    "answer": "Its contemporary look is apparent in the plumb bow and a nearly flat sheer, and the raised bulwark reduces the visual height of the cabinhouse but accentuates the high freeboard",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingmagazine.net/by-author-1034-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Catana Group?",
    "answer": "Perry\nThe Catana Group is launching its 14th Bali catamaran model, the 5",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-134-1-boats.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dufour?",
    "answer": "Perry\nDufour is a French builder that has been around as long or longer than I have been designing",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-134-1-boats.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This new Dufour?",
    "answer": "This new Dufour is aimed at the cr\n2024 July 1\nHunter Vision 32\nThis recreational coastal cruiser is designed for effortless sailing\nBy\nDavid Liscio\nThe Hunter Vision 32 has been described as a lazy sailor\u2019s boat because it\u2019s so effortless to sail",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-134-1-boats.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The newest design in the Elan series of cruising boats?",
    "answer": "Perry\nThe newest design in the Elan series of cruising boats is this Rob Humphreys-designed Elan Impression 43, which marks 20 years of Humphreys designs for Elan",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-134-1-boats.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The deck?",
    "answer": "The deck is designed by the Pininfarina st\n2024 July 1\nCayman 28\nThis gentleman\u2019s skiff takes you sailing fast and comfortable\nBy\nRobert H",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-134-1-boats.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Most life rafts pack small so they don\u2019t take up a lot of room, but make sure they are stowed somewhere that?",
    "answer": "Most life rafts pack small so they don\u2019t take up a lot of room, but make sure they are stowed somewhere that is easily accessible in an emergency",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2127-life-raft.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This setup?",
    "answer": "This setup is working pretty well, but we have torn the bow light off the pulpit twice",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The best answer?",
    "answer": "The best answer is a gennaker sprit, which allows you to tack the sail a bit forward of the pulpit, clear of most everything",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201d It takes some work to fit a sprit, but?",
    "answer": "\u201d It takes some work to fit a sprit, but is very doable",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An easier but less functional option?",
    "answer": "An easier but less functional option is to fix the spinnaker\u2019s tack to (or near) the furled jib",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The string of beads?",
    "answer": "The string of beads is looped around the furled headsail, and the free ends are attached to the spinnaker\u2019s tack",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is There are modern options to parrel beads, the most popular?",
    "answer": "There are modern options to parrel beads, the most popular is the ATN Tacker (www",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The beads can\u2019t be installed until the sail?",
    "answer": "The beads can\u2019t be installed until the sail is furled, and the sail can\u2019t be unfurled until the beads are removed",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I replace leaking hatches?",
    "answer": "How do I replace leaking hatches",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I stop my mast from leaking?",
    "answer": "How do I stop my mast from leaking",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How should I rig a preventer?",
    "answer": "How should I rig a preventer",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2562-how-do-i-keep-my-a-sail-under-control.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When it still leaked I replaced the\n2024 March 1\nHow do I stop my mast from leaking?",
    "answer": "When it still leaked I replaced the\n2024 March 1\nHow do I stop my mast from leaking",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-126-1-boat-doctor.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is My VHF radio?",
    "answer": "By\nBob Pingel\nDear Boat Doctor,\nMy VHF radio is not working very well",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-126-1-boat-doctor.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is I can make hot water when the engine?",
    "answer": "I can make hot water when the engine is running, but it doesn\u2019t work at the dock",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-126-1-boat-doctor.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is My AIS?",
    "answer": "My AIS is stuck in the supply chain\nBy\nBob Pingel\nHelp",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-126-1-boat-doctor.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Not for the first time I realized that the world?",
    "answer": "Not for the first time I realized that the world is indeed round and that I have been sailing in circles for almost four decades",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What a difference from my first visit to Montserrat 32 years before?",
    "answer": "What a difference from my first visit to Montserrat 32 years before",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cLisbon?",
    "answer": "\u201cLisbon is supposed to be a big city and I don\u2019t see any lights on the horizon",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Then and now, Kretsch?",
    "answer": "Then and now, Kretsch is never far from a sextant",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is That\u2019s Antigua man, dis?",
    "answer": "That\u2019s Antigua man, dis is Montserrat, Antigua is 30 miles over there",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is , a Kaufman 47 that in some design aspects?",
    "answer": "These days I conduct offshore training passages aboard\nQuetzal\n, a Kaufman 47 that in some design aspects is an oversized Contessa 32",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One of our rites of autumn?",
    "answer": "One of our rites of autumn is the heavy weather passage from Nova Scotia to the Caribbean, a challenging passage that has provided the crew of\nQuetzal\nsome interesting adventures, including a near catastrophic broach, a savage knockdown and the joy of weathering several serious gales",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Many miles and many storms later I am here to report that keeping moving?",
    "answer": "Many miles and many storms later I am here to report that keeping moving is always a good thing",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Henry, a living encyclopedia of small boat voyaging,?",
    "answer": "Henry, a living encyclopedia of small boat voyaging, is a friend to all sailors and we realized we had a mutual friend",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When a yacht with the unfortunate name of Innocent Bystander was shelled everything changed?",
    "answer": "When a yacht with the unfortunate name of Innocent Bystander was shelled everything changed",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Trevor and Annie were awarded the Cruising Club of America\u2019s Blue Water Medal in 2009 and he?",
    "answer": "Trevor and Annie were awarded the Cruising Club of America\u2019s Blue Water Medal in 2009 and he is thought to be the only sailor to have spent winters frozen in the Arctic and Antarctic",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ostensibly I teach voyaging skills, and maybe I do, but it seems Aristotle?",
    "answer": "Ostensibly I teach voyaging skills, and maybe I do, but it seems Aristotle is more influential than the Annapolis Book of Seamanship",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is There\u2019s humanity about our voyages, a sense of shared adventure, freedom and responsibility that?",
    "answer": "There\u2019s humanity about our voyages, a sense of shared adventure, freedom and responsibility that is elusive and just plain hard to find ashore",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-1781-the-great-circle-route-connecting-the-dots-of-a-sailing-life.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The layout?",
    "answer": "The layout is inviting and the boat seems to beckon passersby to step aboard",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-117-1-launchings.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Maine?",
    "answer": "2016 January 1\nNew boat: Reach 14\nBy\nSAILING Magazine\nMaine is home to many artists whose inspiration is the sea and whose mediums of choice are teak, mahogany and fiberglass",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-117-1-launchings.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The hardware?",
    "answer": "The hardware is custom built",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-117-1-launchings.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The woodwork trim?",
    "answer": "The woodwork trim is beautiful African mahogany and reflects the history of this fishing vessel",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-117-1-launchings.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Monohull one-design racing?",
    "answer": "2015 July 1\nCorsair Pulse 600\nBy\nSAILING Magazine\nMonohull one-design racing is as popular as ever, but it can be harder to find affordable one-design multihulls, especially trimarans",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-117-1-launchings.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A\u00a0Seascape 27 won the doublehanded division of last year\u2019s Chicago-Mackinac race, so there?",
    "answer": "Corsair Marine aims to change that with its Pulse 600, a trailera\n2015 June 1\nNew boat: Seascape 27\nBy\nSAILING Magazine\nA\u00a0Seascape 27 won the doublehanded division of last year\u2019s Chicago-Mackinac race, so there is no doubt about its racing credentials",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-117-1-launchings.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Arcona 380?",
    "answer": "The Arcona 380 is a 37-foot, nine-tenths fractional rig, bluewater boat designed as a successor to the venerable Arcona 400",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-117-1-launchings.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The SP?",
    "answer": "The SP is a motorsailer designed as a cross between a trawler and sailboat; a boat equally at ho\n2014 September 1\nNew boat: Arbor 26\nBy\nSAILING Magazine\nAppearances can be deceiving",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-117-1-launchings.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Annapolis Sailboat Show?",
    "answer": "Over time, the design ethos wavered a bit, b\n2024 March 1\nJeanneau Yachts 55\nJeanneau keeps pushing the boat design envelope with its breakthrough open-air deck saloon cruiser\nBy\nGreta Schanen\nThe Annapolis Sailboat Show is the place to catch all the newest models making their debuts, but there\u2019s always one boat that creates a bigger buzz than the rest",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-119-1-boat-test.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Jeanneau Sun Odyssey 319?",
    "answer": "Cushy comforts\n2019 March 1\nPacking a big punch\nThe Jeanneau Sun Odyssey 319 is a new entry-level cruiser that packs all the best of a big cruiser in an affordable package\nBy\nGreta Schanen\nThe test boat came with the standard stainless steel bow roller, but the 319 is available with an optional sprit to fly an asymmetrical spinnaker or code zero",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-119-1-boat-test.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, we are seeing more boats today with minimal overhangs and broad sterns, so the catboat does not look as foreign as it did to me in the early '60s?",
    "answer": "However, we are seeing more boats today with minimal overhangs and broad sterns, so the catboat does not look as foreign as it did to me in the early '60s",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-65-alerion-express-cat.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Garry's board?",
    "answer": "Garry's board is a higher-aspect-ratio board that is shown with two different shapes depending upon the drawing",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-65-alerion-express-cat.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Express Cat's rudder?",
    "answer": "The Express Cat's rudder is quite unusual",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-65-alerion-express-cat.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An important part of sailing for me?",
    "answer": "An important part of sailing for me is independence",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-65-alerion-express-cat.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The only \"trouble\" you can have with a folding prop?",
    "answer": "The only \"trouble\" you can have with a folding prop is if fails to open, and there are a limited number of reasons why this can happen",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2650-take-care-of-your-prop-and-it-will-take-care-of-you.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One?",
    "answer": "One is stiffness or corrosion in the pivot, for which disassembly and cleaning is the answer",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2650-take-care-of-your-prop-and-it-will-take-care-of-you.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The other?",
    "answer": "The other is wear-folding props have moving parts so wear is an issue",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2650-take-care-of-your-prop-and-it-will-take-care-of-you.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is You can tell this wear?",
    "answer": "You can tell this wear is happening as you describe, the blades should stay a quarter-inch apart when closed",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2650-take-care-of-your-prop-and-it-will-take-care-of-you.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The High-Performance SPF 50 Sunscreen?",
    "answer": "The High-Performance SPF 50 Sunscreen is water resistant for 80 minutes, sweat resistant and offers full spectrum protection from UVA/UVB, infrared and HEVL rays",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2040-sunscreen-for-sailors.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A Daily Skin Repair Lotion?",
    "answer": "A Daily Skin Repair Lotion is also available",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/article-2040-sunscreen-for-sailors.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is information?",
    "answer": "Providing us with other\ninformation is optional",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/flex-49-privacy-policy.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is automatically receive general information that?",
    "answer": "Like many web sites, we may also\nautomatically receive general information that is contained in our\nserver log files such as your IP address and cookie information",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/flex-49-privacy-policy.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all)?",
    "answer": "Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all)\nis set forth below",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/flex-49-privacy-policy.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is cookies on your computer and?",
    "answer": "Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access\ncookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those\nparties providing the advertisement",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/flex-49-privacy-policy.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, the companies serving the\nadvertising do not have access to our cookies?",
    "answer": "However, the companies serving the\nadvertising do not have access to our cookies",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/flex-49-privacy-policy.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that?",
    "answer": "Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not\ncontained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within\nour forums, may continue to remain on our site at our discretion even\nthough your user account is deleted",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/flex-49-privacy-policy.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is e-mail address you have provided to us that?",
    "answer": "We\nwill notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a\nprominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the\ne-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your\nuser settings",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/flex-49-privacy-policy.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why won\u201a\u00c4\u00f4t my holding tank pump out?",
    "answer": "Why won\u201a\u00c4\u00f4t my holding tank pump out",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-994-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is No one?",
    "answer": "From something akin to a dictatorship to something much closer to a democracy, there are four ways that crews tend\nOn the Wind\n2024 October 1 - 12:00 am\nThe passion for multihulls isn\u201a\u00c4\u00f4t waning, it\u201a\u00c4\u00f4s just changing\nBy\nNick Hayes\nNo one is more passionate about their version of sailing than a multihull sailor",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-994-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2024 July 1 - 12:00 am?",
    "answer": "One avid friend has introduced hundreds of guests to\nOn the Wind\n2024 July 1 - 12:00 am\nIs sailing risky",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-994-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is But?",
    "answer": "But is there any reason to be concerned",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-994-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The sea change that\u201a\u00c4\u00f4s happening might not be the big shift escapists think it?",
    "answer": "One state\u201a\u00c4\nOn the Wind\n2024 April 1 - 12:00 am\nThe sea change that\u201a\u00c4\u00f4s happening might not be the big shift escapists think it is\nBy\nNick Hayes\nEscapism is built into the human psyche, has genetic and evolutionary roots, and persists in story across the millennia",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-994-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201a\u00c4\u00faThis?",
    "answer": "\u201a\u00c4\u00faThis is it,\u201a\u00c4\u00f9 he said",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-994-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is And sail trim, like playing an instrument,?",
    "answer": "And sail trim, like playing an instrument, is our touchpoint with the medium",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-994-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In fact, apart from steering a sailboat, which?",
    "answer": "In fact, apart from steering a sailboat, which is one o\nOn the Wind\n2021 March 31 - 12:00 am\nHey racers: The cruisers are coming, tone it down\nBy\nNick Hayes\nSailing can seem bicameral\u201a\u00c4\u00eelike a 50/50 Senate\u201a\u00c4\u00eesplit between racers whose passion is intense competition, strategy and speed, and cruisers seeking fun-in-the-sun and vacations to exotic locales",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/by-author-994-1.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dragonfly 36This 36-footer?",
    "answer": "By\nSAILING Magazine\nDragonfly 36This 36-footer is the latest in Dragonfly\u2019s line of folding cruising trimarans",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-1-1-news.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The only thing between us and Antarctica?",
    "answer": "The only thing between us and Antarctica is 1,300 nautic\n2025 April 1\nSpring Boat Show Time\nBy\nSAILING Magazine\nThe Annapolis Spring Sailboat Show kicks off April 25 for a weekend of boats, gear, sailing seminars",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-1-1-news.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Maarten Heineken Regatta?",
    "answer": "Maarten Heineken Regatta is an iconic, bucket-list event in the Caribbean, and I\u2019ve been fortunate to attend multiple times over in its 45-year history",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-1-1-news.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Tuning your rig?",
    "answer": "I\u2019ve been on race boats, chase boat\n2025 March 17\nRig tuning\nTuning your rig means better performance and safer sailing\nBy\nDavid Liscio\n2025 March 13\nAvocet\nA young couple falls in love with the soul of their bluewater cruiser and prepares for adventure\nBy\nErin L",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-1-1-news.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Chris and Marissa Neely may be young boat owners, but the love the 20-somethings have for their old boat?",
    "answer": "Schanen\nChris and Marissa Neely may be young boat owners, but the love the 20-somethings have for their old boat is rooted in its old soul",
    "source_url": "https://sailingmagazine.net/articles.sec-1-1-news.html",
    "domain": "sailingmagazine.net",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingmagazine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Yacht ownership?",
    "answer": "Yacht insurance\nYacht ownership is a reflection of your passion for the water and nautical lifestyle",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/industries/marine-yacht/individuals?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The program?",
    "answer": "The program is underwritten by Geo Blue\nWho manages this crew medical health insurance program",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Rick Bagnall?",
    "answer": "Rick Bagnall is the program manager; you can reach him at\nrbagnall@risk-strategies",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is (Please note: Current US Sailing membership?",
    "answer": "(Please note: Current US Sailing membership is required",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is After Open Enrollment, enrollment?",
    "answer": "After Open Enrollment, enrollment is closed unless the US Sailing member has a qualifying event",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Online enrollment?",
    "answer": "Online enrollment is available only during the Open Enrollment period which runs from July 1st to August 31st",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are the premiums so low in the US Sailing Group crew medical program?",
    "answer": "Why are the premiums so low in the US Sailing Group crew medical program",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Many people covered in the program spend time outside of the United States for much of the year, and health insurance coverage?",
    "answer": "Many people covered in the program spend time outside of the United States for much of the year, and health insurance coverage is a lot less expensive overseas",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Many in the program have multiple sources of coverage (eg, paid crew typically have P&I from the vessel), thus the full exposure to risk?",
    "answer": "Many in the program have multiple sources of coverage (eg, paid crew typically have P&I from the vessel), thus the full exposure to risk is lower",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a qualifying event?",
    "answer": "What is a qualifying event",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, if you experience a qualified change in status you can make mid-year changes?",
    "answer": "However, if you experience a qualified change in status you can make mid-year changes",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A qualifying event, also called a life event change,?",
    "answer": "A qualifying event, also called a life event change, is a personal change in status which may allow you to change your benefit elections",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I enroll if I have a qualifying event?",
    "answer": "How do I enroll if I have a qualifying event",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What if my US physician or hospital?",
    "answer": "What if my US physician or hospital is not listed in Geo Blue\u2019s online provider network",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What if my US physician or hospital is not listed in Geo Blue\u2019s online provider network?",
    "answer": "What if my US physician or hospital is not listed in Geo Blue\u2019s online provider network",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Geo Blue?",
    "answer": "Geo Blue is the carrier for the US Sailing group crew medical program",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Founded in 1997, Geo Blue?",
    "answer": "Founded in 1997, Geo Blue is a leading provider of international health insurance programs and an innovator in online healthcare information, medical assistance and insurance services around the globe",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Risk Strategies/Gowrie Group's role in the US Sailing health insurance plan?",
    "answer": "What is Risk Strategies/Gowrie Group's role in the US Sailing health insurance plan",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Risk Strategies/Gowrie Group?",
    "answer": "Risk Strategies/Gowrie Group is US Sailing\u2019s insurance partner and manages this health insurance program",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Rick Bagnall runs the program for Risk Strategies/Gowrie Group and?",
    "answer": "Rick Bagnall runs the program for Risk Strategies/Gowrie Group and is the direct contact for all clients",
    "source_url": "https://www.gowrie.com/crewmedical?hsLang=en",
    "domain": "gowrie.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "gowrie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What Your Boat\u2019s Beam?",
    "answer": "Boating\nHow to Dock a Pontoon Boat: Tips and Tricks for Easy Docking\nBoat Reviews\nOverview of the 2024 Sea-Doo RXP-X 325\nBoat Reviews\nOverview of the 2024 Parker Offshore 2900 CC\nBoating\nWhat Your Boat\u2019s Beam Is and Why It Matters\nQ&A\nArticles\nWhat type of wood is used for pier pilings",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingworld.com/articles/page/2/",
    "domain": "boatingworld.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingworld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What does \u2018no wake\u2019?",
    "answer": "Articles\nWhat does \u2018no wake\u2019 mean on a lake",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingworld.com/articles/page/2/",
    "domain": "boatingworld.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingworld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Disclaimer: The information provided on this website?",
    "answer": "Disclaimer: The information provided on this website is intended for educational purposes only and should not be used as a substitute for professional advice, judgment, or personal experience",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingworld.com/articles/page/2/",
    "domain": "boatingworld.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingworld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Any reliance you place on such information?",
    "answer": "Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatingworld.com/articles/page/2/",
    "domain": "boatingworld.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatingworld"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The gig?",
    "answer": "Dash of Salt: Boat Test Blues\nNovember 18, 2025\nThe gig is more workaday than champagne and caviar, and sometimes the harbor patrol saves our bacon",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/lifestyle/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Handle a Serious Swell\nNovember 4, 2025\nSprains, strains and fractures are common onboard injuries, each with specific treatments?",
    "answer": "How to Handle a Serious Swell\nNovember 4, 2025\nSprains, strains and fractures are common onboard injuries, each with specific treatments",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/lifestyle/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Smarter steering?",
    "answer": "The Case for the Compass\nSmarter steering means frequent, but only short, glances at the chartplotter",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/lifestyle/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The company?",
    "answer": "On Sustainability: Supersede CEO Sean Petterson\nNovember 5, 2025\nThe company is scaling up production on its innovative replacement to marine plywood derived from 100 percent recycled plastic waste",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/trawlertalk/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Trawlerfest?",
    "answer": "July 3, 2025\nSeptember 23-27, 2025\nTrawlerfest Baltimore 2025\nMay 23, 2025\nTrawlerfest is Passagemaker\u2019s stand-alone series of boat shows designed for cruising enthusiasts",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/event-news/trawlerfest-event-news/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Lauderdale 2025?",
    "answer": "Lauderdale 2025 is LIVE\nDecember 18, 2024\nCome join us at Trawlerfest in sunny Ft",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/event-news/trawlerfest-event-news/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Trawlerfest ticketing?",
    "answer": "Trawlerfest Stuart 2024\nMarch 4, 2024\nTrawlerfest ticketing is now LIVE",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/event-news/trawlerfest-event-news/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The three-stateroom model?",
    "answer": "Sargo 31 Outboard\nNovember 10, 2025\nNordic Strength Meets Yamaha Power\nAbsolute Navetta 62\nOctober 28, 2025\nThe three-stateroom model is a sophisticated and stylish little ship",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/cruiser-reviews/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This imposing 55-footer?",
    "answer": "North by Northwest\nSeptember 5, 2025\nThis imposing 55-footer is a comfortable, well-appointed coastal cruiser primed to take on more ambitious journeys",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/cruiser-reviews/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The semi-displacement, full-keel Helmsman 43E Pilothouse does just what a trawler?",
    "answer": "Sea Trial Report: Helmsman 43E Pilothouse\nJune 24, 2025\nThe semi-displacement, full-keel Helmsman 43E Pilothouse does just what a trawler is supposed to: She goes the distance",
    "source_url": "https://passagemaker.com/category/cruiser-reviews/",
    "domain": "passagemaker.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "passagemaker"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Troubleshoot Your Boat\u2019s Air-Conditioning System\nMay 30, 2025\nEverything you need to know about fixing your air conditioner?",
    "answer": "How to Troubleshoot Your Boat\u2019s Air-Conditioning System\nMay 30, 2025\nEverything you need to know about fixing your air conditioner",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Affordable, powerful and safe, a new solid state battery tech?",
    "answer": "Solid-State Batteries for Boats\nApril 7, 2025\nAffordable, powerful and safe, a new solid state battery tech  is set to further propel an electrified future",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain Your Boat\u2019s Stabilizers\nOctober 15, 2020\nInside tricks from the pros on maintaining your boat\u2019s stabilizer system?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain Your Boat\u2019s Stabilizers\nOctober 15, 2020\nInside tricks from the pros on maintaining your boat\u2019s stabilizer system",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Perform Preventive Maintenance on Your Boat\nAugust 4, 2017\nHead trouble off at the pass by giving your boat a thorough physical?",
    "answer": "How to Perform Preventive Maintenance on Your Boat\nAugust 4, 2017\nHead trouble off at the pass by giving your boat a thorough physical",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Fall?",
    "answer": "How to Check the Cooling System on Your Boat\nOctober 31, 2016\nFall is an ideal time to inspect your engine\u2019s cooling system",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Check the Cooling System on Your Boat\nOctober 31, 2016\nFall is an ideal time to inspect your engine\u2019s cooling system?",
    "answer": "How to Check the Cooling System on Your Boat\nOctober 31, 2016\nFall is an ideal time to inspect your engine\u2019s cooling system",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain the Exhaust System on Your Boat\nMay 19, 2016\nInspecting your boat\u2019s exhaust system now might save your engine later?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain the Exhaust System on Your Boat\nMay 19, 2016\nInspecting your boat\u2019s exhaust system now might save your engine later",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What a Walker FuelSep can do for Your Boat\nJanuary 26, 2016\nAdd a FuelSep to your engine\u2019s fuel line and get ready for a cleaner burn?",
    "answer": "What a Walker FuelSep can do for Your Boat\nJanuary 26, 2016\nAdd a FuelSep to your engine\u2019s fuel line and get ready for a cleaner burn",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Care for Davits and Cranes\nJune 2, 2015\nFind tips to help you maintain your davits or crane here?",
    "answer": "How to Care for Davits and Cranes\nJune 2, 2015\nFind tips to help you maintain your davits or crane here",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Prepare for a Day on Your Boat\nApril 16, 2015\nBeing smart at the dock can save you major headaches out at sea?",
    "answer": "How to Prepare for a Day on Your Boat\nApril 16, 2015\nBeing smart at the dock can save you major headaches out at sea",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Pick the Right Battery for Your Boat\nJanuary 14, 2015\nYou need to know the differences between battery types before you can pick the right setup for your boat?",
    "answer": "How to Pick the Right Battery for Your Boat\nJanuary 14, 2015\nYou need to know the differences between battery types before you can pick the right setup for your boat",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is There\u2019s nothing glamorous about it, but maintaining a clean and well running bilge system?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain the Bilge on Your Boat\nSeptember 3, 2014\nThere\u2019s nothing glamorous about it, but maintaining a clean and well running bilge system is a good indicator that you\u2019re a consummate boater",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain the Bilge on Your Boat\nSeptember 3, 2014\nThere\u2019s nothing glamorous about it, but maintaining a clean and well running bilge system is a good indicator that you\u2019re a consummate boater?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain the Bilge on Your Boat\nSeptember 3, 2014\nThere\u2019s nothing glamorous about it, but maintaining a clean and well running bilge system is a good indicator that you\u2019re a consummate boater",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Troubleshoot Your Boat\u2019s Air-Conditioning System\nEverything you need to know about fixing your air conditioner?",
    "answer": "How to Troubleshoot Your Boat\u2019s Air-Conditioning System\nEverything you need to know about fixing your air conditioner",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain Your Boat\u2019s Stabilizers\nInside tricks from the pros on maintaining your boat\u2019s stabilizer system?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain Your Boat\u2019s Stabilizers\nInside tricks from the pros on maintaining your boat\u2019s stabilizer system",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Perform Preventive Maintenance on Your Boat\nHead trouble off at the pass by giving your boat a thorough physical?",
    "answer": "How to Perform Preventive Maintenance on Your Boat\nHead trouble off at the pass by giving your boat a thorough physical",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Check the Cooling System on Your Boat\nFall is an ideal time to inspect your engine\u2019s cooling system?",
    "answer": "How to Check the Cooling System on Your Boat\nFall is an ideal time to inspect your engine\u2019s cooling system",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain the Exhaust System on Your Boat\nInspecting your boat\u2019s exhaust system now might save your engine later?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain the Exhaust System on Your Boat\nInspecting your boat\u2019s exhaust system now might save your engine later",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What a Walker FuelSep can do for Your Boat\nAdd a FuelSep to your engine\u2019s fuel line and get ready for a cleaner burn?",
    "answer": "What a Walker FuelSep can do for Your Boat\nAdd a FuelSep to your engine\u2019s fuel line and get ready for a cleaner burn",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Care for Davits and Cranes\nFind tips to help you maintain your davits or crane here?",
    "answer": "How to Care for Davits and Cranes\nFind tips to help you maintain your davits or crane here",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Prepare for a Day on Your Boat\nBeing smart at the dock can save you major headaches out at sea?",
    "answer": "How to Prepare for a Day on Your Boat\nBeing smart at the dock can save you major headaches out at sea",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Pick the Right Battery for Your Boat\nYou need to know the differences between battery types before you can pick the right setup for your boat?",
    "answer": "How to Pick the Right Battery for Your Boat\nYou need to know the differences between battery types before you can pick the right setup for your boat",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain the Bilge on Your Boat\nThere\u2019s nothing glamorous about it, but maintaining a clean and well running bilge system is a good indicator that you\u2019re a consummate boater?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain the Bilge on Your Boat\nThere\u2019s nothing glamorous about it, but maintaining a clean and well running bilge system is a good indicator that you\u2019re a consummate boater",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/systems/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is March 2, 2025?",
    "answer": "March 2, 2025\nIs there really such a thing as too many outboards",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/engines/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In the race to clean power, electricity?",
    "answer": "July 18, 2023\nIn the race to clean power, electricity is in the lead",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/engines/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Flux Motors?",
    "answer": "Previous\nNext\nFlux Marine FM115 Electric Outboard: Silent Power Tested\nFlux Motors is bringing Bristol, Rhode Island into the maritime future",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/engines/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is December 15, 2025?",
    "answer": "Waterfront: Adventures Abound\nDecember 15, 2025\nIs Jeanneau\u2019s 695 the ultimate boat for an adventurous young family",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/voyaging/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This story about the Nordhavn 120 crossing the Pacific Ocean?",
    "answer": "Crossing the Pacific Ocean in a Nordhavn 120\nNovember 25, 2025\nThis story about the Nordhavn 120 crossing the Pacific Ocean is guaranteed to make you want to pull up your own anchor and set off for ports unknown",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/voyaging/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Waterfront: Adventures Abound?",
    "answer": "Waterfront: Adventures Abound\nIs Jeanneau\u2019s 695 the ultimate boat for an adventurous young family",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/voyaging/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Traveling with your tender?",
    "answer": "How to Travel with Your Tender\nJuly 10, 2025\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/voyaging/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Travel with Your Tender\nJuly 10, 2025\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions?",
    "answer": "How to Travel with Your Tender\nJuly 10, 2025\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/voyaging/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Travel with Your Tender\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions?",
    "answer": "How to Travel with Your Tender\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/voyaging/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Too Much?",
    "answer": "Too Much is Never Enough\nAugust 13, 2025\nA Malaysian speed run with Mark Richards reveals how Grand Banks and Palm Beach have become such a rising force",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/page/3/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Azimut\u2019s newcomer?",
    "answer": "Azimut 72 Fly\nJuly 8, 2025\nAzimut\u2019s newcomer is a yacht with speed, safety, beauty and yes, practicality",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/page/3/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How the Outboard Helped Win World War II\nJuly 2, 2025\nFueled by patriotism, there was a time when outboard manufacturers worked toward a common mission: leading the Allies to victory against the Nazis, one river at a time?",
    "answer": "How the Outboard Helped Win World War II\nJuly 2, 2025\nFueled by patriotism, there was a time when outboard manufacturers worked toward a common mission: leading the Allies to victory against the Nazis, one river at a time",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/page/3/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Rugged on the outside, luxurious on the inside, The Arksen 85?",
    "answer": "Arksen 85\nJuly 2, 2025\nRugged on the outside, luxurious on the inside, The Arksen 85 is far from ordinary",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/page/3/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The C10 Offshore?",
    "answer": "Viggo C10 Offshore\nJune 27, 2025\nThe C10 Offshore is a point-a-to-point-b foul-weather adventure vessel built to get you there\u2014wherever there might be\u2014high and dry",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/page/3/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How the Outboard Helped Win World War II\nFueled by patriotism, there was a time when outboard manufacturers worked toward a common mission: leading the Allies to victory against the Nazis, one river at a time?",
    "answer": "How the Outboard Helped Win World War II\nFueled by patriotism, there was a time when outboard manufacturers worked toward a common mission: leading the Allies to victory against the Nazis, one river at a time",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/page/3/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Charlie Levine hosts a DADS (Dads Appreciating Down Syndrome) fishing trip in Florida, where the haul?",
    "answer": "Waterfront: Little Fish, Big Memories\nDecember 16, 2024\nCharlie Levine hosts a DADS (Dads Appreciating Down Syndrome) fishing trip in Florida, where the haul is small and the memories are anything but",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/sportfishing/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Built on a deep-V platform and powered with twin 250-hp Yamahas, the Regulator 25?",
    "answer": "Regulator 25 Walkthrough\nNovember 7, 2024\nBuilt on a deep-V platform and powered with twin 250-hp Yamahas, the Regulator 25 is ready to head offshore",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/sportfishing/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One of the stars of the 2024 Fort Lauderdale Show?",
    "answer": "Viking 74 Walkthrough\nNovember 2, 2024\nOne of the stars of the 2024 Fort Lauderdale Show is undoubtedly Viking\u2019s new 74, which replaces their popular 72",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/sportfishing/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 60 years of dedication to building a better boat?",
    "answer": "60 years of dedication to building a better boat is certainly on display here",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/sportfishing/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The feature-filled Formula 457 Fish center console?",
    "answer": "Formula 457 CCF\nOctober 9, 2024\nThe feature-filled Formula 457 Fish center console is much more than a fishing boat",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/sportfishing/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How did tiny Wanchese, North Carolina become the global mecca for custom sportfish building?",
    "answer": "How did tiny Wanchese, North Carolina become the global mecca for custom sportfish building",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/sportfishing/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is After putting AI to the test, Bill reckons that his profession as a yacht designer?",
    "answer": "July 16, 2025\nAfter putting AI to the test, Bill reckons that his profession as a yacht designer is secure\u2014at least for now",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/column/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A stroll on the dock with a voice from the past reminds the author that beauty?",
    "answer": "Walking with Ghosts\nJuly 16, 2025\nA stroll on the dock with a voice from the past reminds the author that beauty is timeless",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/column/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It may sound clich\u00e9, but in boatbuilding\u2014and life\u2014laughter?",
    "answer": "Stem to Stern: The Best Medicine\nJune 24, 2025\nIt may sound clich\u00e9, but in boatbuilding\u2014and life\u2014laughter is still the best medicine",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/column/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Spoiler Alert: The revolution?",
    "answer": "December 9, 2025\nSpoiler Alert: The revolution is already well underway",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Properly Place and Maintain Your Transducer\nJune 27, 2025\nTransducer Installation Tips for Clear Sonar Performance\nInlet Navigation Safety Tips\nJune 6, 2025\nInlets can be tricky?",
    "answer": "How to Properly Place and Maintain Your Transducer\nJune 27, 2025\nTransducer Installation Tips for Clear Sonar Performance\nInlet Navigation Safety Tips\nJune 6, 2025\nInlets can be tricky",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is January 17, 2024?",
    "answer": "Special Report: Wind Farms and Their Effect on Boating\nJanuary 17, 2024\nIs the wind farm apocalypse nigh",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Add Wireless Charging to Your Boat\nMay 9, 2023\nThrow that old cord away?",
    "answer": "How to Add Wireless Charging to Your Boat\nMay 9, 2023\nThrow that old cord away",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Going digital?",
    "answer": "How To: Add Digital Switching to Your Boat\nApril 5, 2023\nGoing digital is easy",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How To: Add Digital Switching to Your Boat\nApril 5, 2023\nGoing digital is easy?",
    "answer": "How To: Add Digital Switching to Your Boat\nApril 5, 2023\nGoing digital is easy",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Digital switching?",
    "answer": "Garmin Showcases Boat Switch\nOctober 27, 2022\nDigital switching is ubiquitous with the new boat market; Garmin\u2019s Boat Switch brings it to the used boat masses",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Next?",
    "answer": "Previous\nNext\nIs AI Coming for Boating",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Properly Place and Maintain Your Transducer\nTransducer Installation Tips for Clear Sonar Performance\nInlet Navigation Safety Tips\nInlets can be tricky?",
    "answer": "How to Properly Place and Maintain Your Transducer\nTransducer Installation Tips for Clear Sonar Performance\nInlet Navigation Safety Tips\nInlets can be tricky",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Special Report: Wind Farms and Their Effect on Boating?",
    "answer": "Special Report: Wind Farms and Their Effect on Boating\nIs the wind farm apocalypse nigh",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Add Wireless Charging to Your Boat\nThrow that old cord away?",
    "answer": "How to Add Wireless Charging to Your Boat\nThrow that old cord away",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How To: Add Digital Switching to Your Boat\nGoing digital is easy?",
    "answer": "How To: Add Digital Switching to Your Boat\nGoing digital is easy",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/electronics/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The venerable builder adds to its go-anywhere, do-anything Voyager line with a five-stateroom stunner that\u2019s as comfortable crossing oceans at displacement speeds as she?",
    "answer": "The venerable builder adds to its go-anywhere, do-anything Voyager line with a five-stateroom stunner that\u2019s as comfortable crossing oceans at displacement speeds as she is outrunning the competition at over 25 knots",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/megayachts/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Set Up and Maintain a Ditch Bag for Your Boat\nAugust 22, 2025\nEssential Guide to Ditch Bag Boating Safety\nDrowning Doesn\u2019t Look Like Drowning\nJuly 2, 2025\nSigns of Drowning: What to Know Before It\u2019s Too Late\nInlet Navigation Safety Tips\nJune 6, 2025\nInlets can be tricky?",
    "answer": "How to Set Up and Maintain a Ditch Bag for Your Boat\nAugust 22, 2025\nEssential Guide to Ditch Bag Boating Safety\nDrowning Doesn\u2019t Look Like Drowning\nJuly 2, 2025\nSigns of Drowning: What to Know Before It\u2019s Too Late\nInlet Navigation Safety Tips\nJune 6, 2025\nInlets can be tricky",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/seamanship/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What to do if You Run Your Boat Aground\nMay 22, 2025\nCruise for long enough and you\u2019ll touch bottom?",
    "answer": "What to do if You Run Your Boat Aground\nMay 22, 2025\nCruise for long enough and you\u2019ll touch bottom",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/seamanship/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What\u2019s the plan for when you do?",
    "answer": "What\u2019s the plan for when you do",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/seamanship/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Set Up and Maintain a Ditch Bag for Your Boat\nEssential Guide to Ditch Bag Boating Safety\nDrowning Doesn\u2019t Look Like Drowning\nSigns of Drowning: What to Know Before It\u2019s Too Late\nInlet Navigation Safety Tips\nInlets can be tricky?",
    "answer": "How to Set Up and Maintain a Ditch Bag for Your Boat\nEssential Guide to Ditch Bag Boating Safety\nDrowning Doesn\u2019t Look Like Drowning\nSigns of Drowning: What to Know Before It\u2019s Too Late\nInlet Navigation Safety Tips\nInlets can be tricky",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/seamanship/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What to do if You Run Your Boat Aground\nCruise for long enough and you\u2019ll touch bottom?",
    "answer": "What to do if You Run Your Boat Aground\nCruise for long enough and you\u2019ll touch bottom",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/seamanship/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Set Up and Maintain a Ditch Bag for Your Boat\nAugust 22, 2025\nEssential Guide to Ditch Bag Boating Safety\nA Gift for the Boater Who Has Everything\nJune 9, 2025\nCustom art from Sea Bold Portraits helps bring boating memories to life?",
    "answer": "How to Set Up and Maintain a Ditch Bag for Your Boat\nAugust 22, 2025\nEssential Guide to Ditch Bag Boating Safety\nA Gift for the Boater Who Has Everything\nJune 9, 2025\nCustom art from Sea Bold Portraits helps bring boating memories to life",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/gear/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How To: (And Why To) Clean the Bottom of Your Boat\nJuly 8, 2024\nMike Smith on why you need to get some dive gear and get under your boat?",
    "answer": "How To: (And Why To) Clean the Bottom of Your Boat\nJuly 8, 2024\nMike Smith on why you need to get some dive gear and get under your boat",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/gear/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A hobbyist woodworker?",
    "answer": "Filling the Gaps\nFebruary 5, 2024\nA hobbyist woodworker is filling some holes in the boating market with high-quality fender boards",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/gear/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A new slender and lightweight outboard?",
    "answer": "Previous\nNext\nTemo 1000 Electric Outboard\nA new slender and lightweight outboard is en route to a dinghy dock near you",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/gear/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Set Up and Maintain a Ditch Bag for Your Boat\nEssential Guide to Ditch Bag Boating Safety\nA Gift for the Boater Who Has Everything\nCustom art from Sea Bold Portraits helps bring boating memories to life?",
    "answer": "How to Set Up and Maintain a Ditch Bag for Your Boat\nEssential Guide to Ditch Bag Boating Safety\nA Gift for the Boater Who Has Everything\nCustom art from Sea Bold Portraits helps bring boating memories to life",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/gear/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How To: (And Why To) Clean the Bottom of Your Boat\nMike Smith on why you need to get some dive gear and get under your boat?",
    "answer": "How To: (And Why To) Clean the Bottom of Your Boat\nMike Smith on why you need to get some dive gear and get under your boat",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/gear/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Handle a Fuel Spill on Your Boat\nNovember 21, 2025\nSomehow you\u2019ve drenched your boat in fuel \u2026 here\u2019s what you should do next?",
    "answer": "How to Handle a Fuel Spill on Your Boat\nNovember 21, 2025\nSomehow you\u2019ve drenched your boat in fuel \u2026 here\u2019s what you should do next",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Why the Right Helm Chair?",
    "answer": "Helm Seating For Your Boat\nNovember 13, 2025\nWhy the Right Helm Chair Is Worth Every Dollar\nLife on Orla\nNovember 7, 2025\nA social media influencer makes a name for himself\u2014and a home\u2014by refurbishing vintage oil rig lifeboat",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Get Rid of Stubborn Boat Odors\nOctober 23, 2025\nYour boat stinks?",
    "answer": "How to Get Rid of Stubborn Boat Odors\nOctober 23, 2025\nYour boat stinks",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Mike Smith dives deep into how to best rid your boat of unwanted pests\u2014and we don\u2019t?",
    "answer": "How to Control Pests on Your Boat\nSeptember 4, 2025\nMike Smith dives deep into how to best rid your boat of unwanted pests\u2014and we don\u2019t mean your in-laws",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Control Pests on Your Boat\nSeptember 4, 2025\nMike Smith dives deep into how to best rid your boat of unwanted pests\u2014and we don\u2019t mean your in-laws?",
    "answer": "How to Control Pests on Your Boat\nSeptember 4, 2025\nMike Smith dives deep into how to best rid your boat of unwanted pests\u2014and we don\u2019t mean your in-laws",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Handle a Fuel Spill on Your Boat\nSomehow you\u2019ve drenched your boat in fuel \u2026 here\u2019s what you should do next?",
    "answer": "How to Handle a Fuel Spill on Your Boat\nSomehow you\u2019ve drenched your boat in fuel \u2026 here\u2019s what you should do next",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Get Rid of Stubborn Boat Odors\nYour boat stinks?",
    "answer": "How to Get Rid of Stubborn Boat Odors\nYour boat stinks",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Control Pests on Your Boat\nMike Smith dives deep into how to best rid your boat of unwanted pests\u2014and we don\u2019t mean your in-laws?",
    "answer": "How to Control Pests on Your Boat\nMike Smith dives deep into how to best rid your boat of unwanted pests\u2014and we don\u2019t mean your in-laws",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Change a Boat\u2019s Name\nAugust 28, 2025\nChanging a boat\u2019s name often leaves ghosts of the old letters behind?",
    "answer": "How to Change a Boat\u2019s Name\nAugust 28, 2025\nChanging a boat\u2019s name often leaves ghosts of the old letters behind",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/refit-and-upgrade/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain A Dripless Shaft Seal\nJune 3, 2025\nDon\u2019t fear dripless shaft seals?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain A Dripless Shaft Seal\nJune 3, 2025\nDon\u2019t fear dripless shaft seals",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/refit-and-upgrade/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Change a Boat\u2019s Name\nChanging a boat\u2019s name often leaves ghosts of the old letters behind?",
    "answer": "How to Change a Boat\u2019s Name\nChanging a boat\u2019s name often leaves ghosts of the old letters behind",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/refit-and-upgrade/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain A Dripless Shaft Seal\nDon\u2019t fear dripless shaft seals?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain A Dripless Shaft Seal\nDon\u2019t fear dripless shaft seals",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/refit-and-upgrade/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Protect Your Boat From a Lightning Strike\nJuly 31, 2025\nHas your boat ever been on the receiving end of a thunderbolt?",
    "answer": "How to Protect Your Boat From a Lightning Strike\nJuly 31, 2025\nHas your boat ever been on the receiving end of a thunderbolt",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Properly Ventilate Your Boat\u2019s Engine Room\nJuly 10, 2025\nMarine Engine Ventilation: Ensure Proper Airflow\nHow to Travel with Your Tender\nJuly 10, 2025\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions?",
    "answer": "How to Properly Ventilate Your Boat\u2019s Engine Room\nJuly 10, 2025\nMarine Engine Ventilation: Ensure Proper Airflow\nHow to Travel with Your Tender\nJuly 10, 2025\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Marine Growth Can Damage Your Boat\nJune 19, 2025\nMike Smith on keeping algae, grass and barnacles at bay?",
    "answer": "How Marine Growth Can Damage Your Boat\nJune 19, 2025\nMike Smith on keeping algae, grass and barnacles at bay",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain the Hydraulic Systems on Your Boat\nJune 6, 2025\nHydraulic systems are extra-reliable but they need regular maintenance to stay that way?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain the Hydraulic Systems on Your Boat\nJune 6, 2025\nHydraulic systems are extra-reliable but they need regular maintenance to stay that way",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Protect Your Boat From a Lightning Strike\nHas your boat ever been on the receiving end of a thunderbolt?",
    "answer": "How to Protect Your Boat From a Lightning Strike\nHas your boat ever been on the receiving end of a thunderbolt",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Properly Ventilate Your Boat\u2019s Engine Room\nMarine Engine Ventilation: Ensure Proper Airflow\nHow to Travel with Your Tender\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions?",
    "answer": "How to Properly Ventilate Your Boat\u2019s Engine Room\nMarine Engine Ventilation: Ensure Proper Airflow\nHow to Travel with Your Tender\nTraveling with your tender is easier with these solutions",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How Marine Growth Can Damage Your Boat\nMike Smith on keeping algae, grass and barnacles at bay?",
    "answer": "How Marine Growth Can Damage Your Boat\nMike Smith on keeping algae, grass and barnacles at bay",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Maintain the Hydraulic Systems on Your Boat\nHydraulic systems are extra-reliable but they need regular maintenance to stay that way?",
    "answer": "How to Maintain the Hydraulic Systems on Your Boat\nHydraulic systems are extra-reliable but they need regular maintenance to stay that way",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/page/2/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How the Outboard Mechanic\u2019s Job has Evolved\nSeptember 14, 2021\nAs outboards evolve with each passing year, so too has the know-how of mechanics that service these increasingly powerful behemoths?",
    "answer": "How the Outboard Mechanic\u2019s Job has Evolved\nSeptember 14, 2021\nAs outboards evolve with each passing year, so too has the know-how of mechanics that service these increasingly powerful behemoths",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Help Your Genset Live Forever\nDecember 7, 2020\nMaximize Your Genset\u2019s Lifespan with Expert Maintenance Advice\nDiesel Engine Myths\nMarch 4, 2020\nWhen it comes to your boat\u2019s engines don\u2019t believe everything you hear?",
    "answer": "How to Help Your Genset Live Forever\nDecember 7, 2020\nMaximize Your Genset\u2019s Lifespan with Expert Maintenance Advice\nDiesel Engine Myths\nMarch 4, 2020\nWhen it comes to your boat\u2019s engines don\u2019t believe everything you hear",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How To: Make Sure Your Turbo Runs Forever\nApril 22, 2019\nTurbocharger Basics for Boaters: Maintenance, Cleaning & Troubleshooting\nHow to Repower Your Outboard-Powered Boat\nJanuary 31, 2019\nSwapping out old outboards isn\u2019t as simple as you may think, but it\u2019s worth the effort and expense to upgrade to high-tech motors?",
    "answer": "How To: Make Sure Your Turbo Runs Forever\nApril 22, 2019\nTurbocharger Basics for Boaters: Maintenance, Cleaning & Troubleshooting\nHow to Repower Your Outboard-Powered Boat\nJanuary 31, 2019\nSwapping out old outboards isn\u2019t as simple as you may think, but it\u2019s worth the effort and expense to upgrade to high-tech motors",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The demand for speed has been around since water\u2019s been wet, but don\u2019t forget that great performance?",
    "answer": "Considerations When Repowering Your Boat\nJuly 18, 2018\nThe demand for speed has been around since water\u2019s been wet, but don\u2019t forget that great performance is about more than sheer horsepower",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is What Running Aground Can?",
    "answer": "What Running Aground Can Mean For Your Engines\nApril 26, 2018\nSounds or vibrations a little off",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Running Aground Can Mean For Your Engines\nApril 26, 2018\nSounds or vibrations a little off?",
    "answer": "What Running Aground Can Mean For Your Engines\nApril 26, 2018\nSounds or vibrations a little off",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Recommission Your Boat in the Spring\nMarch 16, 2018\nOur expert walks you through ten easy, but important, tips that will help you keep your boat running smoothly?",
    "answer": "How to Recommission Your Boat in the Spring\nMarch 16, 2018\nOur expert walks you through ten easy, but important, tips that will help you keep your boat running smoothly",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How the Outboard Mechanic\u2019s Job has Evolved\nAs outboards evolve with each passing year, so too has the know-how of mechanics that service these increasingly powerful behemoths?",
    "answer": "How the Outboard Mechanic\u2019s Job has Evolved\nAs outboards evolve with each passing year, so too has the know-how of mechanics that service these increasingly powerful behemoths",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Help Your Genset Live Forever\nMaximize Your Genset\u2019s Lifespan with Expert Maintenance Advice\nDiesel Engine Myths\nWhen it comes to your boat\u2019s engines don\u2019t believe everything you hear?",
    "answer": "How to Help Your Genset Live Forever\nMaximize Your Genset\u2019s Lifespan with Expert Maintenance Advice\nDiesel Engine Myths\nWhen it comes to your boat\u2019s engines don\u2019t believe everything you hear",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How To: Make Sure Your Turbo Runs Forever\nTurbocharger Basics for Boaters: Maintenance, Cleaning & Troubleshooting\nHow to Repower Your Outboard-Powered Boat\nSwapping out old outboards isn\u2019t as simple as you may think, but it\u2019s worth the effort and expense to upgrade to high-tech motors?",
    "answer": "How To: Make Sure Your Turbo Runs Forever\nTurbocharger Basics for Boaters: Maintenance, Cleaning & Troubleshooting\nHow to Repower Your Outboard-Powered Boat\nSwapping out old outboards isn\u2019t as simple as you may think, but it\u2019s worth the effort and expense to upgrade to high-tech motors",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Running Aground Can Mean For Your Engines\nSounds or vibrations a little off?",
    "answer": "What Running Aground Can Mean For Your Engines\nSounds or vibrations a little off",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Recommission Your Boat in the Spring\nOur expert walks you through ten easy, but important, tips that will help you keep your boat running smoothly?",
    "answer": "How to Recommission Your Boat in the Spring\nOur expert walks you through ten easy, but important, tips that will help you keep your boat running smoothly",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/engine/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I check for engines damaged by forgetting to open seacocks?",
    "answer": "How do I check for engines damaged by forgetting to open seacocks",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/ask-professor-diesel/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I care for my unused engine?",
    "answer": "How do I care for my unused engine",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/ask-professor-diesel/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When\nCan switching motor oil viscosity harm my engine?",
    "answer": "When\nCan switching motor oil viscosity harm my engine",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/ask-professor-diesel/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Question: When I took your one-day Introductory Diesel Maintenance Course several years ago, I forgot to ask one question: What?",
    "answer": "Seasonal Storage For Fuel Tanks\nMarch 1, 2011\nQuestion: When I took your one-day Introductory Diesel Maintenance Course several years ago, I forgot to ask one question: What is the best way to lay up a fuel tank for seasonal storage",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/ask-professor-diesel/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As I grow older, this noise?",
    "answer": "As I grow older, this noise is starting to bother me, particularly at times when I have to shout to be heard on the flying bridge at cruise speed",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/maintenance/ask-professor-diesel/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Coeur d\u2019Alene, Idaho, it just so happens,?",
    "answer": "Grandpa\u2019s Patina\nDecember 8, 2025\nCoeur d\u2019Alene, Idaho, it just so happens, is home to some of the most beautiful and storied wooden boats in America",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/boats/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A boat ride reveals how Joe Namath?",
    "answer": "Exclusive: A Florida Cruise with Broadway Joe Namath\nJuly 2, 2025\nA boat ride reveals how Joe Namath is spending the fourth quarter of his life",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/blogs/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is When all the kid wants for Christmas?",
    "answer": "Previous\nNext\nA Christmas Story\nWhen all the kid wants for Christmas is an old boat to fix up (and learn from) how can Santa say no",
    "source_url": "https://powerandmotoryacht.com/category/blogs/",
    "domain": "powerandmotoryacht.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "powerandmotoryacht"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Protect Your Anchor\nHow to Anchor Like a Pro: GlobeSailor X Ardent Training Webinar\nHow To Read Weather in Greece: Ionian Forecast Tips\nLearning to Wingfoil: Andy Rice\u2019s Tips\n<<\n<\n1\n2\n3\n4?",
    "answer": "How to Protect Your Anchor\nHow to Anchor Like a Pro: GlobeSailor X Ardent Training Webinar\nHow To Read Weather in Greece: Ionian Forecast Tips\nLearning to Wingfoil: Andy Rice\u2019s Tips\n<<\n<\n1\n2\n3\n4",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/cruising/cruising-skills/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When we speak, Ellie has just returned from competing in the Rolex Middle Sea Race \u2013 a 600nm sprint from Malta around Sicily \u2013 on board Gordon Ketelbey\u2019s fully-crewed TP52\nZen?",
    "answer": "When we speak, Ellie has just returned from competing in the Rolex Middle Sea Race \u2013 a 600nm sprint from Malta around Sicily \u2013 on board Gordon Ketelbey\u2019s fully-crewed TP52\nZen",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While Ellie recounts the race\u2019s most memorable moments \u2013 from the dramatic start line within Valletta\u2019s Grand Harbour, to sailing past Stromboli as it spewed clouds of ash \u2013 the sailing itself she says made a complete contrast to the short-handed racing she?",
    "answer": "While Ellie recounts the race\u2019s most memorable moments \u2013 from the dramatic start line within Valletta\u2019s Grand Harbour, to sailing past Stromboli as it spewed clouds of ash \u2013 the sailing itself she says made a complete contrast to the short-handed racing she is accustomed to, with \u201cplenty of corners and opportunities to learn, as well as a lot less personal space and a lot more sleep\u201d",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Undoubtedly, short-handed sailing?",
    "answer": "Ellie on her first  single-handed race,  the brutal La Solitaire  |  Photo credit: T Campion\nUndoubtedly, short-handed sailing is where her passion lies",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is With hundreds of young people already benefitting over the first few years of the scheme, Ellie?",
    "answer": "With hundreds of young people already benefitting over the first few years of the scheme, Ellie is full of praise for her dad\u2019s involvement and the impact that it is having",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While Ollie\u2019s ambitions stop short of his own Vend\u00e9e Globe campaign, his focus?",
    "answer": "While Ollie\u2019s ambitions stop short of his own Vend\u00e9e Globe campaign, his focus is firmly on winning La Solitaire du Figaro, a goal that stands as an achievement in its own right",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The class, he says, \u201coffers very pure racing and creates incredibly talented sailors in a remarkably short time\u201d, noting that not only does the fleet feed many top-level sailors into Class40 and IMOCA campaigns, but it retains a very high calibre of sailors, and as such, the class?",
    "answer": "The class, he says, \u201coffers very pure racing and creates incredibly talented sailors in a remarkably short time\u201d, noting that not only does the fleet feed many top-level sailors into Class40 and IMOCA campaigns, but it retains a very high calibre of sailors, and as such, the class is notoriously difficult to dominate",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u2013 as Ollie describes: \u201cEveryone?",
    "answer": "\u2013 as Ollie describes: \u201cEveryone is there to help each other",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cWith a fleet of 35 identical boats racing in such close quarters, Figaro racing?",
    "answer": "\u201cWith a fleet of 35 identical boats racing in such close quarters, Figaro racing is almost like dinghy racing \u2013 it\u2019s impossible to relax,\u201d explains Ollie, who says by leg three they were both feeling the effects of cumulative sleep deprivation",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, by the end everyone completely crashed?",
    "answer": "However, by the end everyone completely crashed",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It was an outstanding result, particularly given the short preparation period, but Ollie?",
    "answer": "It was an outstanding result, particularly given the short preparation period, but Ollie is quick to emphasise that it illustrates how the Figaro class, while open to newcomers, demands high standards of professionalism",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While Ollie sums it up as a \u201chidden gem of a race \u2013 relentless, gruesome, but one that brings out brilliant sailors\u201d, Ellie explains that their search for partners to enable them to continue their campaigns?",
    "answer": "While Ollie sums it up as a \u201chidden gem of a race \u2013 relentless, gruesome, but one that brings out brilliant sailors\u201d, Ellie explains that their search for partners to enable them to continue their campaigns is already well underway",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-news/latest-news/offshore-rising-stars-ellie-driver-and-ollie-hill-young-short-hand-ambition/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why Families Escape to Yachting Abroad?",
    "answer": "Why Families Escape to Yachting Abroad",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/cruising/cruising-advice/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Boat Trim Guide:?",
    "answer": "Boat Trim Guide: Is Sailing Flat Always Fast",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Win the Endeavour Trophy\nSailing Start Line Tips: How To Avoid a Bad Race Start\nHow to Reduce Drag: A Keelboat Masterclass from Niall Myant\nProtesting in a sailing race - how the process works\nBack to top ^\n\u00a9 The Chelsea Magazine Company 2025\n\u00a9 Telegraph Media Group Holdings Limited 2025\nFOLLOW US\nPrivacy Policy\nCookie Policy\nTerms & Conditions\nTelegraph?",
    "answer": "How to Win the Endeavour Trophy\nSailing Start Line Tips: How To Avoid a Bad Race Start\nHow to Reduce Drag: A Keelboat Masterclass from Niall Myant\nProtesting in a sailing race - how the process works\nBack to top ^\n\u00a9 The Chelsea Magazine Company 2025\n\u00a9 Telegraph Media Group Holdings Limited 2025\nFOLLOW US\nPrivacy Policy\nCookie Policy\nTerms & Conditions\nTelegraph",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Corsica?",
    "answer": "Corsica is known for its dramatic mountainous terrain and rugged coastline, offering a blend of natural beauty and cultural heritage",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The island\u2019s interior?",
    "answer": "The island\u2019s interior is a haven for hikers and nature lovers, with deep gorges, lush forests, and towering peaks like Monte Cinto",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sardinia, the second-largest island in the Mediterranean,?",
    "answer": "Sardinia, the second-largest island in the Mediterranean, is famous for its beautiful beaches, ancient ruins, and wild, rugged landscapes",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sardinia?",
    "answer": "Sardinia is also renowned for its excellent sailing conditions, offering sheltered bays, dramatic cliffs, and idyllic islands like La Maddalena Archipelago",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Its location however,?",
    "answer": "Its location however, means the northwest winds can be strong sometimes reaching 25+kts, so it\u2019s a great place if you want to expand your sailing skill",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An exciting aspect of cruising in this region?",
    "answer": "An exciting aspect of cruising in this region is the visibility of active volcanoes like Mount Etna and Stromboli",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Stromboli, in particular,?",
    "answer": "Stromboli, in particular, is one of the most active volcanoes in the world, providing a dynamic and ever-changing landscape if you want to explore the Aeolian Islands",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If you are interested in a flotilla holiday in this area, Tubber?",
    "answer": "If you are interested in a flotilla holiday in this area, Tubber is well worth investigating because this company has a selection of package routes in all areas",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Girolata?",
    "answer": "Girolata is located in the Scandola Nature Reserve",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If you are looking for a by-the-cabin charter, which?",
    "answer": "If you are looking for a by-the-cabin charter, which is an ideal way to holiday if you are travelling solo, or are totally new to sailing/want to gain experience under the supervision of experienced crew members, then Sailsquare could be a good choice",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This company has a huge range of options on a selection of different monohulls and multihulls, and what\u2019s included in the price?",
    "answer": "This company has a huge range of options on a selection of different monohulls and multihulls, and what\u2019s included in the price is clearly explained on its website",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The globesailor?",
    "answer": "The globesailor is a good example of yacht charter agent that also offers a by-the-cabin charter package",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/sailing-in-corsica-sardinia-sicily-mediterranean-chartering/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Designed by Stephen Jones to produce a swift, comfortable passage, and built by Rustler Yachts for stunning, durable living, this?",
    "answer": "Author\n:\nSailing Today\nPublished Date:\n24 November 2025\nSHARE THIS ARTICLE\nyachts for sale  |  Photo credit: Alex Grabu\nRUSTLER 44 |  SEA HAYES\nDesigned by Stephen Jones to produce a swift, comfortable passage, and built by Rustler Yachts for stunning, durable living, this is an ultimate bluewater cruising yacht",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/used-boats/yachts-for-sale-three-of-the-best-sailing-boats-on-the-market/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is She has recently returned to the UK following a season in the Caribbean, and?",
    "answer": "She has recently returned to the UK following a season in the Caribbean, and is a fine example offered in ready to sail condition with many features including a generator, inverter, heating, bow thruster, electric halyard winch, and electric primary winches",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/used-boats/yachts-for-sale-three-of-the-best-sailing-boats-on-the-market/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dancing Bear?",
    "answer": "com\nYachts for Sale: Catamaran\nGUNBOAT 48 | DANCING BEAR\nDancing Bear\nis an extremely rare to the market Morrelli & Melvin-designed carbonfibre Gunboat 48 with upgraded rig and interior",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/used-boats/yachts-for-sale-three-of-the-best-sailing-boats-on-the-market/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is She has had just one private owner since new and?",
    "answer": "She has had just one private owner since new and is now offered for sale with a great performance-cruising inventory",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/used-boats/yachts-for-sale-three-of-the-best-sailing-boats-on-the-market/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ventura?",
    "answer": "com\nMOODY DS 41 |  VENTURA\nVentura\nis the first of the sought-after Moody DS 41s to come up for sale in the UK and is a very good, highly specified example with only 155 hours on the clock",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/used-boats/yachts-for-sale-three-of-the-best-sailing-boats-on-the-market/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is She was launched and commissioned for the 2022 season and the brokers report that she?",
    "answer": "She was launched and commissioned for the 2022 season and the brokers report that she is \u2018nicely presented for sale\u2019",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/used-boats/yachts-for-sale-three-of-the-best-sailing-boats-on-the-market/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is This particular Moody \u2013 also known as the Moody 41 DS and Moody Deck saloon 41 \u2013?",
    "answer": "This particular Moody \u2013 also known as the Moody 41 DS and Moody Deck saloon 41 \u2013 is the shallow draft keel version, and has plenty of features including twin forestay upgrade, electric winches, full Raymarine navigation suite, heating system, electric loo and more",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/used-boats/yachts-for-sale-three-of-the-best-sailing-boats-on-the-market/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As they headed towards the Doldrums, weighing up when to utilise their motor (60 hours of which?",
    "answer": "As they headed towards the Doldrums, weighing up when to utilise their motor (60 hours of which is allowed in the race instructions to minimise risk of being stranded and impacting the race schedules downstream), the team held off for as long as possible, using the remaining wind to the final moment",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/races-and-regattas/tales-from-the-clipper-race-2025-jts-journey-to-the-equator/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What Is the Secret to Sunsail's Success?",
    "answer": "What Is the Secret to Sunsail's Success",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/what-is-the-secret-to-sunsails-success/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sunsail?",
    "answer": "Author\n:\nSam Jefferson\nPublished Date:\n5 August 2025\nSHARE THIS ARTICLE\nCroatia \u2013 a popular Sunsail destination  |  Photo credit: Sunsail\nSunsail is a charter industry global leader and has plenty to celebrate",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/what-is-the-secret-to-sunsails-success/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A half-century of helping adventure-lovers explore the world from the deck of an award-winning yacht?",
    "answer": "A half-century of helping adventure-lovers explore the world from the deck of an award-winning yacht is no mean feat",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/what-is-the-secret-to-sunsails-success/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In this exclusive interview, we delve into Sunsail\u2019s origins, its milestones and where it?",
    "answer": "In this exclusive interview, we delve into Sunsail\u2019s origins, its milestones and where it is heading next",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/what-is-the-secret-to-sunsails-success/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It\u2019s no coincidence that Dee Caffari?",
    "answer": "It\u2019s no coincidence that Dee Caffari is one of Sunsail\u2019s contemporary ambassadors",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/what-is-the-secret-to-sunsails-success/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Listening to our guests?",
    "answer": "Listening to our guests is key \u2013 they help us find that sweet spot where comfort, performance and sociability meet",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/what-is-the-secret-to-sunsails-success/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sunsail\u2019s journey from a humble flotilla in the Saronic Gulf to a global sailing holiday pioneer?",
    "answer": "\u201d\nSunsail\u2019s journey from a humble flotilla in the Saronic Gulf to a global sailing holiday pioneer is more than a business success story \u2013 it\u2019s a celebration to a vision dedicated to a genuine love for life on the water",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/what-is-the-secret-to-sunsails-success/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As the brand looks ahead to the next 50 years, one thing?",
    "answer": "As the brand looks ahead to the next 50 years, one thing is certain \u2013 the spirit that launched seven Snapdragons in 1974 still guides every voyage today",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/what-is-the-secret-to-sunsails-success/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is William Shakespeare?",
    "answer": "Author\n:\nSam Jefferson\nPublished Date:\n6 January 2026\nSHARE THIS ARTICLE\nLeopard 46\nWilliam Shakespeare is generally noted for being a bit of a sage",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Omitted, all the voyage of their life?",
    "answer": "Omitted, all the voyage of their life is bound in shallows and in miseries",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is At present, Leopard?",
    "answer": "At present, Leopard is the third biggest manufacturer of multihulls in the world and the largest in the southern hemisphere",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One thing led to another and Robertson and Caine\u2019s Leopard Catamarans are now ubiquitous not just in the Moorings fleet but also Sunsail\u2019s which?",
    "answer": "One thing led to another and Robertson and Caine\u2019s Leopard Catamarans are now ubiquitous not just in the Moorings fleet but also Sunsail\u2019s which is part of the same group",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Now, that?",
    "answer": "Now, that is all very well but it has meant the Leopard catamarans can end up getting a bit pigeonholed as pure charter vessels, and this is far from the truth",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The 46?",
    "answer": "The 46 is a tad bigger and, as with all manufacturers these days, the aim seems to be to offer more space and comfort while not compromising performance",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The launch of the 46 also finds the company looking to diversify and underline that it has a product that?",
    "answer": "The launch of the 46 also finds the company looking to diversify and underline that it has a product that is well cut out for private ownership",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is That, I guess,?",
    "answer": "That, I guess, is where I come in",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Well, it\u2019s clearly a pure cruising catamaran \u2013 there are stub keels as opposed to daggerboards \u2013 so this?",
    "answer": "Well, it\u2019s clearly a pure cruising catamaran \u2013 there are stub keels as opposed to daggerboards \u2013 so this is a boat built to compete with the likes of\nLagoon\n, Bali and perhaps\nFountaine Pajot",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Weighing in at 17,000kg, this?",
    "answer": "Weighing in at 17,000kg, this is not a particularly light boat but, as with all cruising cats these days, you can expect performance to be respectable",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As with all Leopards, the design?",
    "answer": "As with all Leopards, the design is by Simonis and Voogdt who have a lot of experience in this sector",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In terms of construction, the boat?",
    "answer": "In terms of construction, the boat is something of a break from the norm for the manufacturer",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Whereas previous models used three separate moulds for the hull components then glassed them together, this new boat?",
    "answer": "Whereas previous models used three separate moulds for the hull components then glassed them together, this new boat is built in one single mould which should aid stiffness",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Whereas previous models used three separate moulds for the hull components then glassed them together, this new boat is built in one single mould which should aid stiffness?",
    "answer": "Whereas previous models used three separate moulds for the hull components then glassed them together, this new boat is built in one single mould which should aid stiffness",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sailing around the world?",
    "answer": "Sailing around the world is far from mission improbable; it has been done many times",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is By the same token, don\u2019t expect too many thrills; your Lagoons and Leopards etc are competent performers but, ultimately, the autopilot?",
    "answer": "By the same token, don\u2019t expect too many thrills; your Lagoons and Leopards etc are competent performers but, ultimately, the autopilot is your friend",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is These are an optional extra and are supplied by Alternative Energies, a company that?",
    "answer": "These are an optional extra and are supplied by Alternative Energies, a company that is actually a subsidiary of rival boatbuilder Fountaine Pajot, which has taken the laudable step of making its units available to anyone in an effort to boost innovation and drive costs down",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The first thing you notice?",
    "answer": "The first thing you notice is the huge bathing platform which doubles as storage for the tender",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is They are clever but both heavy and elaborate and it\u2019s no surprise that this?",
    "answer": "They are clever but both heavy and elaborate and it\u2019s no surprise that this is an optional extra; electric davits are standard",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Two steps up and you\u2019re into the cockpit that\u2019s kept completely rope free and?",
    "answer": "Two steps up and you\u2019re into the cockpit that\u2019s kept completely rope free and is reasonably enclosed with a big L-shaped seating area to port which is ideal for dining in warm weather",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is To starboard are the steps up to the fly bridge and there?",
    "answer": "To starboard are the steps up to the fly bridge and there is a fridge set into this, while the barbecue is integrated into the coamings to port",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is It looks neat and?",
    "answer": "It looks neat and is well hidden but is not that well sited as I\u2019d anticipate that smoke from the barbecue would tend to blow into the cockpit",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Leopard wanted to retain defined indoor and outdoor spaces so, even though there?",
    "answer": "Leopard 46\nLeopard wanted to retain defined indoor and outdoor spaces so, even though there is a large sliding patio door, there is still clear definition between the spaces",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Nevertheless, in warm weather, the cockpit itself?",
    "answer": "Nevertheless, in warm weather, the cockpit itself is a wonderful living space, with the solid Bimini which runs all the way aft, adding protection",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As mentioned, the fly bridge?",
    "answer": "As mentioned, the fly bridge is accessed from the starboard side of the cockpit although there are also steps up from the starboard side deck",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The fly bridge?",
    "answer": "The fly bridge is the nerve centre of the 46 and all the sail controls are led here meaning that in theory the boat can be singlehanded with minimum amounts of stress and no need to leave your seat",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In the 46, there?",
    "answer": "In the 46, there is a decent connection between the two areas, as the steps up are quite open and offer a clear line of vision if the skipper looks down into the cockpit",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Once installed at the helm, the seat?",
    "answer": "Once installed at the helm, the seat is very comfortable and also sociable as two can sit alongside each other without any stress",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The set-up?",
    "answer": "The set-up is good with all lines leading back to three powered winches all situated close to the helm",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is To port of the helm?",
    "answer": "To port of the helm is a bridge deck which, once again, is all about the lounging space",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Right aft?",
    "answer": "Right aft is the mainsheet on a traveller",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The mainsail?",
    "answer": "The mainsail is at a good height for stowing but it is worth noting that you need to brief crew not to stand on the solar panels which, being the rigid type could get damaged if you tread heavily on them",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The foredeck?",
    "answer": "The foredeck is semi solid with only a small trampoline area",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The seating area?",
    "answer": "The seating area is in a recessed well with loungers on deck in front and decent storage underneath",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The galley?",
    "answer": "The galley is to starboard and set well forward with the double sink set against the forward bulkhead latitudinally, and the electric cooker and drawer fridge set longitudinally almost the length of the cabin, only interrupted by the descent into the forward and aft cabins",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Descend down into the starboard hull and the master cabin?",
    "answer": "Leopard 46 interior\nDescend down into the starboard hull and the master cabin is set aft with a good sized king sized bed set fore and aft and a heads with separate shower stall",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Forward of this and still to starboard?",
    "answer": "Forward of this and still to starboard is another double set latitudinally with a narrow heads/shower set right forward",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The double bed?",
    "answer": "The double bed is well raised up which can be a pain to get into in a seaway but this does give you a nice view through the port light",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The port hull has a double aft which?",
    "answer": "Leopard 46 interior\nThe port hull has a double aft which is a good sized bed with partial walkaround access and plentiful light",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Forward of this?",
    "answer": "Forward of this is a corridor with a washing machine set into the storage units on the starboard side",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is On this boat there?",
    "answer": "On this boat there is a utility room which seemed a bit superfluous but good for storage \u2013 particularly as it linked to the bow storage compartment",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In standard configuration, the 46?",
    "answer": "Electric Motors\nIn standard configuration, the 46 is powered by twin 45hp Yanmar diesels although these can be upgraded to 57hp",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "However, from our point of view, the hybrid electric option on the test boat was of far greater interest?",
    "answer": "However, from our point of view, the hybrid electric option on the test boat was of far greater interest",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Power regeneration?",
    "answer": "Power regeneration is accomplished via shore power, the diesel generator, 1,600 watts of solar panels on the Bimini, and hydrogeneration via the two 18in propellers spinning when under sail",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The key statistic here?",
    "answer": "The key statistic here is that the electric motors give six hours of autonomy at half speed",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is That sounds a touch disheartening but it\u2019s worth bearing in mind that the generator?",
    "answer": "That sounds a touch disheartening but it\u2019s worth bearing in mind that the generator is more efficient than a pure diesel motor as it will always run at maximum efficiency for the conditions and requirements of the battery",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The cost of the hybrid electric version?",
    "answer": "The cost of the hybrid electric version is circa 200,000 Euros which seems quite a lot but it is worth bearing in mind that you get the whole kit; generator and upgraded lithium ion batteries for this price and these items alone are costly if you take them from the options list but stick with a diesel engine",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Under power the boat?",
    "answer": "Under Sail\nUnder power the boat is eerily silent when leaving the dock and it is a real pleasure not to have the rumble of the diesel engine in the background",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The steering?",
    "answer": "The steering is cable driven as opposed to hydraulic which gave it a decent amount of feel but it was still relatively uninspiring and the autopilot is definitely your friend",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In part this was because the generator on the 46?",
    "answer": "In part this was because the generator on the 46 is in the storage area in front of the saloon meaning that you are generally well away from the motor",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Performance?",
    "answer": "Performance is good as opposed to exhilarating but that really isn\u2019t what these cruising catamarans are all about",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The pricing?",
    "answer": "The pricing is very attractive, and if you are interested in shared ownership, then the strong relationship the company has with\nSunsail\n/The Moorings makes this a really enticing option",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/boats-gear/boat-tests/leopard-46-boat-test-how-to-cruise-in-comfort/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Go Racing in the Caribbean: Chartering for All Skill Levels\nThis article contains affiliate links?",
    "answer": "How to Go Racing in the Caribbean: Chartering for All Skill Levels\nThis article contains affiliate links",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If however, holiday time?",
    "answer": "If however, holiday time is limited, you may want to return to your favourite haunt with events like\nSt Maarten Heineken Regatta\n, the\nBVI Spring Regatta & Sailing Festival\n, or\nAntigua Sailing Week\nsome of the most popular",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is While many companies offer crewed or bareboat charter options, a growing sector?",
    "answer": "While many companies offer crewed or bareboat charter options, a growing sector is individual berth charter",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Another popular company?",
    "answer": "\u201d\nAnother popular company is LV Yachting which specialises in race yacht charters across the Caribbean, and is passionate about connecting teams with high-performance yachts \u2013 from Volvo Ocean 65s and ORC winners to multihulls and top-tier racer cruisers",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Second Star Sailing, which participates in events such as Grenada Sailing Week, RORC 600 Caribbean, St Maarten Heineken Regatta, and St Barths Bucket also specialises in women\u2019s sailing, and?",
    "answer": "\u201d\nSecond Star Sailing, which participates in events such as Grenada Sailing Week, RORC 600 Caribbean, St Maarten Heineken Regatta, and St Barths Bucket also specialises in women\u2019s sailing, and is particularly keen to promote its Women at the Helm in the Caribbean",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Second Star Sailing\u2019s Aliya Brown commenting on this popular programme said: \u201cThrough our all-women race team programme, Women at the Helm, Second Star Sailing?",
    "answer": "Second Star Sailing\u2019s Aliya Brown commenting on this popular programme said: \u201cThrough our all-women race team programme, Women at the Helm, Second Star Sailing is happy to support women in competitive sailing",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Our two-week package?",
    "answer": "Our two-week package is meant to give female sailors more confidence and skills",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is During the second week, we will be on the water for Antigua Sailing Week, racing with a crew that?",
    "answer": "During the second week, we will be on the water for Antigua Sailing Week, racing with a crew that is excited to share their knowledge",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Finally it\u2019s worth remembering that access to the Caribbean with direct flights from the UK to many islands makes chartering a yacht a good option particularly if leisure time?",
    "answer": "\u201d\nFinally it\u2019s worth remembering that access to the Caribbean with direct flights from the UK to many islands makes chartering a yacht a good option particularly if leisure time is more restricted",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/how-to-go-racing-in-the-caribbean-chartering-for-all-skill-levels/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The aim was to examine the seabed by way of transects, that?",
    "answer": "The aim was to examine the seabed by way of transects, that is in straight lines starting from the shore to 50m out, by snorkeling where necessary",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/cruising/cruising-stories/cruising-greece-to-malta-bob-shepton-heads-to-the-med-with-environmental/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The marina?",
    "answer": "Author\n:\nSue Pelling\nPublished Date:\n18 August 2025\nSHARE THIS ARTICLE\nThe marina is sheltered and well appointed",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As far as locations go, the Premier Falmouth Marina?",
    "answer": "Credit: Premier Marinas\nAs far as locations go, the Premier Falmouth Marina is one of the most picturesque you\u2019ll find",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The vibrant and historic town of Falmouth in Cornwall, which?",
    "answer": "50\u00b0 09\u201990N, 005\u00b005\u201902W\nThe vibrant and historic town of Falmouth in Cornwall, which is located within an area of outstanding natural beauty is one of the most desirable places to visit when cruising the west country",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The main Falmouth harbour, as you enter from the Channel \u2013 Carrick Roads \u2013?",
    "answer": "The main Falmouth harbour, as you enter from the Channel \u2013 Carrick Roads \u2013 is one of the world\u2019s largest natural deep-water harbours and extends northwards as far as the River Fal",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Falmouth Marina?",
    "answer": "Falmouth Marina is within easy walking distance to the main hub which is home to a vast array of independent shops, restaurants and attractions such as Discovery Quay, the National Maritime Museum, and Pendennis Castle",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you arrive at the marina you can be sure of a warm welcome by Premier\u2019s staff who are on hand 24-hours a day to assist you with your berthing, and any help you require with facilities?",
    "answer": "When you arrive at the marina you can be sure of a warm welcome by Premier\u2019s staff who are on hand 24-hours a day to assist you with your berthing, and any help you require with facilities",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As with all Premier Marinas, Falmouth Marina?",
    "answer": "As with all Premier Marinas, Falmouth Marina is well designed and laid out for ease of use",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The channel?",
    "answer": "The channel is buoyed and the general approach to the marina is straightforward but it is, however, advisable to consult up-to-date charts, and check notes to mariners at the time of arrival in case of any changes",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The access channel?",
    "answer": "The access channel is to the southwest of the east cardinal mark",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you arrive, moor at the visitors\u2019 hammerhead pontoon and call up reception on VHF Ch80 or using the pontoon telephone for berth allocation?",
    "answer": "When you arrive, moor at the visitors\u2019 hammerhead pontoon and call up reception on VHF Ch80 or using the pontoon telephone for berth allocation",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If you are intending to venture further afield to places like the Isles of Scilly, which?",
    "answer": "If you are intending to venture further afield to places like the Isles of Scilly, which is approximately 60nm away, or across the Channel, it\u2019s an ideal safe, sheltered base",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is One of the most delightful places just south around the headland?",
    "answer": "One of the most delightful places just south around the headland is the Helford River",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/destinations/premier-falmouth-marina-guide-and-cruising-grounds/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Whether it?",
    "answer": "Whether it is in the magazine itself, on our website, or through our email and social media subscribers, advertising your company to our ever increasing and passionate audience could not be easier",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/magazine/advertise-with-us/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How to Win the Endeavour Trophy\nSailing Start Line Tips: How To Avoid a Bad Race Start\nHow to Reduce Drag: A Keelboat Masterclass from Niall Myant\nProtesting in a sailing race - how the process works\n<<\n<\n1\n2\n3\n4\n>\n>>\nAdvertisement\nBack to top ^\n\u00a9 The Chelsea Magazine Company 2025\n\u00a9 Telegraph Media Group Holdings Limited 2025\nFOLLOW US\nPrivacy Policy\nCookie Policy\nTerms & Conditions\nTelegraph?",
    "answer": "How to Win the Endeavour Trophy\nSailing Start Line Tips: How To Avoid a Bad Race Start\nHow to Reduce Drag: A Keelboat Masterclass from Niall Myant\nProtesting in a sailing race - how the process works\n<<\n<\n1\n2\n3\n4\n>\n>>\nAdvertisement\nBack to top ^\n\u00a9 The Chelsea Magazine Company 2025\n\u00a9 Telegraph Media Group Holdings Limited 2025\nFOLLOW US\nPrivacy Policy\nCookie Policy\nTerms & Conditions\nTelegraph",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/racing-skills/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is On 21st-22nd February 2026, Farnborough International?",
    "answer": "Author\n:\nMilly Karsten\nPublished Date:\n19 December 2025\nSHARE THIS ARTICLE\n2026 RYA Dinghy and Watersports Show  |  Photo credit: RYA\nOn 21st-22nd February 2026, Farnborough International is set to host the UK\u2019s biggest celebration of dinghy sailing and watersports",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/boat-shows/2026-rya-dinghy-and-watersports-show-what-to-expect/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What to Look Forward to at the 2026 RYA Dinghy and Watersports Show\nFrom new boats and cutting edge tech, to expert coaching sessions from leading names in the sport, this year\u2019s show brings you a weekend of innovation and inspiration?",
    "answer": "What to Look Forward to at the 2026 RYA Dinghy and Watersports Show\nFrom new boats and cutting edge tech, to expert coaching sessions from leading names in the sport, this year\u2019s show brings you a weekend of innovation and inspiration",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/boat-shows/2026-rya-dinghy-and-watersports-show-what-to-expect/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The 2026 programme?",
    "answer": "The 2026 programme is jam packed with exciting talks, demos, simulators and interactive displays and, this year, the show welcomes wingfoiler and presenter Rafferty Read to the hosting line-up",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/boat-shows/2026-rya-dinghy-and-watersports-show-what-to-expect/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The brand new feature we are looking forward to?",
    "answer": "RYA Dinghy and Watersports Show  |  Photo credit: RYA\nThe brand new feature we are looking forward to is the NextGen Zone, a designated space for young sailors and watersports lovers to get stuck into workshops and sessions designed to build the next generation\u2019s confidence and skills",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/boat-shows/2026-rya-dinghy-and-watersports-show-what-to-expect/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cWhat makes the RYA Dinghy & Watersports Show so special?",
    "answer": "\u201cWhat makes the RYA Dinghy & Watersports Show so special is how it unites the whole community",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/boat-shows/2026-rya-dinghy-and-watersports-show-what-to-expect/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is From trying the trapeze rig and wing, and experiencing sailing simulators or the on-the-water 360 virtual reality, to boat repair workshops and grabbing some brand new kit, the 2026 RYA Dinghy and Watersports Show?",
    "answer": "RYA Dinghy and Watersports Show  |  Photo credit: RYA\nFrom trying the trapeze rig and wing, and experiencing sailing simulators or the on-the-water 360 virtual reality, to boat repair workshops and grabbing some brand new kit, the 2026 RYA Dinghy and Watersports Show is one you won\u2019t want to miss",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/boat-shows/2026-rya-dinghy-and-watersports-show-what-to-expect/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As in years before, the show?",
    "answer": "For the Family\u2026\nAs in years before, the show is a perfect weekend activity for the whole family",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/racing-events/boat-shows/2026-rya-dinghy-and-watersports-show-what-to-expect/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the company do, and how did it get started?",
    "answer": "What does the company do, and how did it get started",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is your role within VentureSail, and how did you get started in the role?",
    "answer": "What is your role within VentureSail, and how did you get started in the role",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Although this?",
    "answer": "Although this is a fairly niche business, we have now expanded into European markets and work with operators from all over the world",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the challenges and rewards of working in this sector of the marine industry?",
    "answer": "What are the challenges and rewards of working in this sector of the marine industry",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Of course, when your business?",
    "answer": "Of course, when your business is determined by weather, there are naturally challenges, with fast-paced decisions that have to be made to ensure guests have the best experience",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A particular reward for us?",
    "answer": "A particular reward for us is having so many first-time customers who get completely hooked on sailing and have continued on to cross the Atlantic",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is From hopping over the English Channel to sailing the length of the UK and crossing the Atlantic, time away from it all with no digital connection?",
    "answer": "From hopping over the English Channel to sailing the length of the UK and crossing the Atlantic, time away from it all with no digital connection is becoming more popular",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you see the state of the industry at present?",
    "answer": "How do you see the state of the industry at present",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sailing in some areas of Europe and the world has become a paperwork nightmare for charter sector operators, and it\u2019s getting increasingly difficult for the historic fleet to make ends meet with so many cost increases, which?",
    "answer": "Sailing in some areas of Europe and the world has become a paperwork nightmare for charter sector operators, and it\u2019s getting increasingly difficult for the historic fleet to make ends meet with so many cost increases, which is worrying for their futures",
    "source_url": "https://www.sailingtoday.co.uk/sailing-charter/charter-tips/the-state-of-the-charter-industry-insights-from-venture-sail/",
    "domain": "sailingtoday.co.uk",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "sailingtoday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Content presented under the \"BOAT Presents\" logo?",
    "answer": "Content presented under the \"BOAT Presents\" logo is an advertising feature and Boat International Limited has been paid to include this content",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/boat-pro/news/ferretti-group-yachts-partnership-aaa-uae-oman",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The deal, which?",
    "answer": "The deal, which is subject to regulatory approval, includes a 301-berth marina for vessels up to 45 metres",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/boat-pro/news/blackstone-acquisition-hamilton-island-australia-marina-yachts",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The main focus of the model?",
    "answer": "The main focus of the model is found in the stern",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/baglietto-flagship-yacht-model-dom-155",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Also on the main deck?",
    "answer": "Also on the main deck is the owner's suite, which spans the yacht's full beam and is fitted with a walk-in closet, a master bedroom with a California king-size bed and a spacious his-and-hers en suite with a \"walk-through\" shower",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/baglietto-flagship-yacht-model-dom-155",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Four en suite guest cabins are located on the lower deck, forward of which?",
    "answer": "Four en suite guest cabins are located on the lower deck, forward of which is accommodation for a crew of eight in addition to a crew mess and laundry area",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/baglietto-flagship-yacht-model-dom-155",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is As such, the project?",
    "answer": "As such, the project is particularly appealing to the American market, of which the La Spezia\u2013based shipyard notes as one of its most important markets",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/baglietto-flagship-yacht-model-dom-155",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \u201cThe DOM155?",
    "answer": "\u201cThe DOM155 is the result of listening carefully to our clients and, more broadly, to the market, which has enthusiastically welcomed both the 35- and 41-metre models but has repeatedly expressed interest in larger dimensions,\u201d explained Baglietto\u2019s chief commercial officer, Fabio Ermetto",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/baglietto-flagship-yacht-model-dom-155",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Why Panama?",
    "answer": "Talk to your yacht: Sirena introduces voice-controlled AI across its fleet with Vanemar and Garmin\nExploring Asia: The new luxury ocean travel experience setting sail in 2027-2028\nUninterrupted internet at sea: A complete guide to hybrid superyacht connectivity\nWhy Panama is the superyacht destination you\u2019ve been overlooking\nThe luxury entertainment brand every superyacht owner should know\nSponsored listings\nMISS MICHELLE\nHorizon\n\u2022\n37",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/baglietto-flagship-yacht-model-dom-155",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Major technical and interior milestones have now been completed and the superyacht?",
    "answer": "Major technical and interior milestones have now been completed and the superyacht is on track for her scheduled 2026 delivery",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/sirena-118-36m-flagship-yacht-construction-update",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Rover?",
    "answer": "Rover\nis the brain behind the model's customisable interior design, which is said by the yard to be \"contemporary-styled\" and \"highly elegant\"",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/sirena-118-36m-flagship-yacht-construction-update",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Accommodation?",
    "answer": "Accommodation is for up to 12 guests and seven crew on board, with the guest accommodation comprising a VIP suite and four guest cabins on the lower deck",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/sirena-118-36m-flagship-yacht-construction-update",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The shipyard has dedicated significant attention to the owner's area, which?",
    "answer": "The shipyard has dedicated significant attention to the owner's area, which is located forward on the main deck and can extend across two decks in a \"loft\" option",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/sirena-118-36m-flagship-yacht-construction-update",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Rover and Germ\u00e1n Frers,?",
    "answer": "Rover and Germ\u00e1n Frers, is bringing this new flagship to life in a way that truly reflects the spirit of Sirena",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/sirena-118-36m-flagship-yacht-construction-update",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Turkish yard?",
    "answer": "\u201d\nThe Turkish yard is also working towards the completion of its flagship yacht \u2013\u00a0created in collaboration with\nLuca Vallebona\nand\nHot Lab\n\u2013 which is currently under construction in Yalova, Turkey, with delivery also scheduled for 2026",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/yachts/news/sirena-118-36m-flagship-yacht-construction-update",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The first series of the guide?",
    "answer": "The first series of the guide is dedicated to yachting activities, offering a clear and practical end-to-end pathway for a yacht\u2019s journey from arrival to departure",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/boat-pro/news/saudi-red-sea-authority-coastal-tourism-guide-launch",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \"Its launch?",
    "answer": "\"Its launch is the result of intensive coordination efforts led by the Authority in collaboration with relevant entities to ensure role integration, foster an attractive tourism and investment environment, support the\u00a0sector\u2019s accelerating growth and align with the objectives of Saudi Vision 2030",
    "source_url": "https://www.boatinternational.com/boat-pro/news/saudi-red-sea-authority-coastal-tourism-guide-launch",
    "domain": "boatinternational.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "boatinternational"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Training?",
    "answer": "Training is at the core of the business, STS make sure their team is using the most accurate techniques and the best equipment",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is All of their team are multi-skilled; this flexibility allows them to direct their efforts to wherever it?",
    "answer": "All of their team are multi-skilled; this flexibility allows them to direct their efforts to wherever it is needed to fulfil their orders on time",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Understanding every aspect of the business in intimate detail?",
    "answer": "Understanding every aspect of the business in intimate detail is key to maintaining their track record of 100% reliability, delivered on time",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A single failure in this industry can result in the loss of hundreds of thousands in lost revenue per day if your system?",
    "answer": "A single failure in this industry can result in the loss of hundreds of thousands in lost revenue per day if your system is down",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sea Talk Systems business model?",
    "answer": "Sea Talk Systems business model is 100% inspection of piece parts, kits and equipment",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/quality-control",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is All their inspection equipment?",
    "answer": "All their inspection equipment is located in dedicated temperature controlled environments to aid in achieving these high standards",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/quality-control",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Sea Talk\u2019s role?",
    "answer": "Sourcing and procurement\nSourcing and procurement\nSea Talk\u2019s role is to provide a sourcing and procurement facility to supply parts which range from small to high precision mechanical piece parts to equipment, at competitive costs and to the highest quality",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/quality-control",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Every manufactured part, without exception,?",
    "answer": "Every manufactured part, without exception, is subjected to a 100% inspection process, which includes dimensional checks, hardness tests, threads and finish, to drawing requirements",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/quality-control",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Jointing equipment?",
    "answer": "Jointing equipment is fully assembled and checked prior to despatch",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/quality-control",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is A list of approved suppliers?",
    "answer": "Supplier management\nSupplier management\nA list of approved suppliers is maintained from information obtained from supplier questionnaires, historic data and delivery / quality performance",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/quality-control",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is STS electronically store all inspection and manufacturing records to ensure there?",
    "answer": "STS electronically store all inspection and manufacturing records to ensure there is full traceability of kits and piece parts for 25 years",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/quality-control",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is In this policy, unless it?",
    "answer": "Cookies - Sea Talk Systems Ltd\nClose\nHome\nQuality Control\nProcesses\nInspection Equipment\nUJ & UQJ Kits\nContact\nEn\nEnglish\nFran\u00e7ais\n\u65e5\u672c\u8a9e\nSEA TALK SYSTEMS ARE THE INDEPENDENT APPROVED SUPPLIER OF UJ AND UQJ KITS, EQUIPMENT AND TOOL KITS TO THE UJ CONSORTIUM MEMBERS\nCookies Policy\nIn this policy, unless it is obvious that they have some other meaning, the words \"we\", \"our\" and \"us\" refers to\nwww",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/cookies-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why and how do we use Cookies?",
    "answer": "Why and how do we use Cookies",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/cookies-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The Web?",
    "answer": "Cookies from third-parties\nThe Web is an integrated place",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/cookies-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is An example of this which?",
    "answer": "An example of this which is widely used across the Web is social media buttons which allow users to like, share and comment about what they find on websites and may result in Cookies being set",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/cookies-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is For the purpose of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) (GDPR), the data controller?",
    "answer": "For the purpose of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) (GDPR), the data controller is Gary Ritchie",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/privacy-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is The data we collect about you may include, but?",
    "answer": "The data you provide may include:\nYour name\nYour email\nYour contact details\nThe data we collect about you may include, but is not limited to:\nYour IP address\nInformation about your browser and operating system\nInformation about your visit, this may include, but is not limited to, pages looked at, visit duration, errors encountered and interaction with the pages",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/privacy-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Any personal information we collect from this website?",
    "answer": "How we use your information\nAny personal information we collect from this website is used in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679) and other applicable laws",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/privacy-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How we use your information\nAny personal information we collect from this website is used in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679) and other applicable laws?",
    "answer": "How we use your information\nAny personal information we collect from this website is used in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679) and other applicable laws",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/privacy-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Your data may be kept if it?",
    "answer": "Your data may be kept if it is required for legal or accounting reasons",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/privacy-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How long do we keep your data\nWe will not retain your personal information longer than necessary?",
    "answer": "How long do we keep your data\nWe will not retain your personal information longer than necessary",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/privacy-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If legally required or if it?",
    "answer": "If legally required or if it is reasonably necessary to meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our Terms and Conditions, we may also retain some of your information for a limited period of time as required, even after it is no longer needed to provide services to you",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/privacy-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is If an access request?",
    "answer": "If an access request is deemed by us to be unfounded or excessive we may charge a reasonable fee",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/privacy-policy",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Each kit?",
    "answer": "Each kit is uniquely serialised to ensure full traceability from top level to each individual part within the kit",
    "source_url": "https://www.seatalk.com/processes",
    "domain": "seatalk.com",
    "confidence": 0.75,
    "tags": [
      "insurance",
      "marine",
      "seatalk"
    ]
  }
]